[JUGHEAD] Previously on Riverdale...
I'm so glad that you're home
safe and that the babies are okay.
- He's transferring to Southside High.
- I'm not a Serpent, okay.
It might be my dad's life, but not mine.
[ARCHIE] You get shot.
Ms. Grundy's murdered.
What if some crazy person is going
after the people that I care about?
[JUGHEAD] Every fairy tale
comes with the same warning:
Good children should never
go into the woods alone.
Stray from the path and who
knows what you'll encounter.
A hungry wolf.
A handsome devil.
Or maybe something worse.
[GUNSHOTS]
[MIDGE] Help! Help! Help me, please!
Help! Help!
Oh, I can take that in to Daddy.
I wanna ask him something, anyway.
Your father and I have
business to discuss.
- You know the rules about his study.
- Mom, those were the old rules.
[HERMIONE] Which still apply, Veronica.
I thought I heard my two
palomitas out here chirping.
Is that my café con leche?
Thank you, corazón.
[VERONICA] Tonight's the season
premiere of The Matchlerette.
I would love to have my friends over.
- [HIRAM] Who exactly?
- Inner circle only.
Hmm.
You can watch with us.
They're dying to meet you.
- They're welcome to come over, mija.
- Thank you, Daddy.
- [HIRAM] Mm-hm.
- Mwah.
[PLAYERS CHATTERING]
Are we gonna start or
what? Where's Coach Clayton?
- At the hospital with Moose and Midge.
- What?
- Hey, guys!
- [REGGIE] I only know what coach told me.
Moose got shot multiple times
by some lunatic at Lovers' Lane.
- Oh, my God...
- No, Arch, he's alive. So's Midge.
He, like, shielded her with
his body. She didn't get hit.
Practice is canceled.
[ETHEL] You don't think they're
targeting students, do you?
Should we be worried?
Like, what's going on?
[KELLER] It was full-on Carrie.
Midge covered in Moose's
blood, screaming like a banshee.
It was insane.
Kev, what were you even doing there?
You could've been shot, too
[KEVIN] I was just night-jogging,
you know, as one does,
and suddenly, I hear gunshots.
Can we agree there's
a killer on the loose?
- With terrible aim.
- Jughead, he murdered Ms. Grundy.
We don't know these
three crimes are related.
Guys, can we focus on what matters here?
Midge and Moose are alive.
Archie's dad survived.
The Matchlerette starts tonight.
You're coming over to watch.
There's a shooter terrorizing the town.
You really want us to
watch a gross dating show?
What I want is for you guys
to meet my dad officially.
Back in New York, my dad
was always in his study,
doing bad things, as it turns out.
I'm tired of closed doors.
I need to know my dad's life
and he needs to know mine.
- Well, we'll be there, V. Can't wait.
- Thank you.
Hey, Andrews, we're going to the
hospital to see Moose. You coming?
Yeah, for sure. I'll
see you tonight, Ronnie.
I better go. Was supposed
to meet my peer mentor
- at Southside High half an hour ago.
- Wait, are...?
Are you sure you can't
just keep going here?
I'll be fine.
[BETTY] Bye.
Okay, it's just us now. Night-jogging?
Yeah. I'm trying to get
in shape for wrestling.
Okay, fine, I was cruising Fox Forest.
I'm going out for wrestling. I
had to tell my dad I was jogging.
- He believed you?
- Yeah. He wants to believe me.
Hey, look, I get it, you're
post-Joaquin, but cruising?
Come on, Kev, you know I hate that.
Why can't you use Grind'em
like every other gay guy?
[KEVIN] Nobody's who
they say they are online.
At least in real life, what you
see is what you get,
there's no surprises.
[BETTY] Moose and Midge were shot
literally 300 yards from Fox Forest,
and the person who did
it is still out there.
Tell me you won't go
back until he's caught.
Okay, fine. I will not
go back. Scout's honor.
[BELL RINGS]
If I wasn't such a big slab of
beef, Midge might've been hit.
You saved her life, bro.
Your nurse is hot. What if you
pop a boner during a sponge bath?
And it wasn't a ski mask? He was
wearing a black hood for sure?
Anything else you remember
about how he looked?
[MOOSE] His eyes.
They're green, right?
[MIDGE] They were blank.
Like there wasn't a person behind them.
He was like Michael Myers.
He had the devil's eyes.
[MIDGE SIGHS]
[METAL DETECTOR BEEPING]
- It's the pins on my hat.
- Take it off, go again.
Forsythe Pendleton Jones III.
Uh... it's Jughead, actually.
I'm Toni Topaz.
I was supposed to give you
the full animatronic tour,
but some robots went insane
and started killing the guests,
so, we'll just wing it.
Classrooms don't have Wi-Fi,
bathroom stalls don't have doors.
What about the Red and Black?
Yeah, it no longer exists. Censorship?
Budget cuts? Take your pick.
You'll find a glimpse of jingle-jangle
being consumed in its natural habitat.
[JUGHEAD] I'm sorry, "jingle-jangle"?
This place is crawling with the JJ.
A highly addictive total gutter drug.
So, let's not touch that.
Jingle-jangle.
Fascinating.
[TONI] All right. Here in the cafetorium,
Ghoulies sit over there.
Rival gang, drug dealers, street
racers, rumors of cannibalism.
Don't ask.
And we sit over there.
With the Serpents.
You're a Southside Serpent?
Why do you think that I
volunteered to give you the tour?
Actually, I'm gonna sit alone.
Just, you know, finish
my book and brood.
I'm confused. Aren't you
like a Serpent by blood?
The son of FP Jones?
Yeah.
So, I self-identify as a
loner, not a pack animal.
I'm just gonna put my head down
and try and get through this, okay?
Hey, you wanna get through this,
you should hang with the Serpents.
If the Ghoulies get a whiff that
you're alone, or vulnerable,
they'll make you their bitch faster than
you can say American History X.
Moose and Midge described him. Same
guy that shot you, same hood, eyes.
Well, maybe and maybe not.
Dad, it's him.
If Sheriff Keller's not gonna take that
seriously, I think we should... be ready.
Like, maybe we should buy a
gun, just be armed in case...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy, okay? Ease up on that. We're
gonna let the cops do their job.
"Armed"? What the hell
are you talking about?
Archie, this is not the Wild West.
We don't keep guns in this house. Okay?
So, just cool it.
Why don't you sit down
next to me, loverboy?
- Archie?
- I'm sorry. This thing with Moose...
It's like nobody cares. Dad keeps
saying, "Leave it to Sheriff Keller."
I'm like, "Yeah, he did a great
job of catching Jason's murderer."
Oh. Wait, I'm sorry, that was us.
Inside voices, please?
[JUGHEAD] No, don't stop him.
Archie going Travis Bickle
is my favorite Archie yet.
Doesn't it feel like he's
targeting us? I mean, specifically?
I don't want anyone else getting hurt.
When we had a getaway on the Cape,
all of us got together and hired
private security to keep out the riffraff
- as an added layer of protection.
- [HIRAM] I loved that house.
- [VERONICA] Daddy.
- We're on our way to dinner at the club.
I wanted to meet your friends first.
Great. Thank you.
- This is Betty Cooper.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
[VERONICA] And Jughead Jones.
- Hi.
- [HIRAM] Hey.
- You know my dad.
- [HIRAM] I do. He's a good man.
He values family.
I hope his return comes
sooner rather than later.
- Yeah, so do we.
- [VERONICA] And, Daddy, this is...
Archie Andrews. The boy who's
captured my daughter's heart.
- Daddy.
- Uh, it's nice to meet you, sir.
Ah, please.
Call me Hiram.
I couldn't help but overhear
your discussion and I, um...
I understand your frustration
with Sheriff Keller.
As for someone who's had his own
share of run-ins with the law...
[CHUCKLES]
I can say that the police
aren't always the solution.
Sometimes we need to take
matters into our own hands.
- We need to protect ourselves.
- [HERMIONE] We're gonna lose our table.
Oh, yes, of course.
Hey, it was nice to meet all of you.
- Oh, and Archie.
- Yes.
[HIRAM] Why don't you
come over for dinner this weak?
I look forward to seeing what you
come up with... to save Riverdale.
[CHUCKLES]
♪ Your eyes ♪
♪ They can't seem to
understand What I've realized ♪
♪ Realize ♪
♪ This isn't just a dream
Stuck on a bad repeat ♪
♪ Fightin' the air to breathe
You can't touch me now ♪
♪ I'm a bad man ♪
♪ Ain't my fault It's all I got ♪
♪ It's so bad, man ♪
♪ Now I am who I am ♪
♪ You can't change me
'Cause you made me ♪
♪ I'm a bad man ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
About Archie coming over for dinner...
I wouldn't push that if I were you.
I'm not. Daddy invited Archie.
- Mm-hm.
- Daddy wants to please his little girl.
And you want your father's approval.
Mija...
you want everything to change overnight.
You want him to be
friends with your friends.
And that will happen.
Just no need to rush it.
No need to be so thirsty, Veronica.
I'm off to school. Here.
- What's that?
- I don't know. It was on the porch.
Guys, we're under attack.
And by "we," I mean our
friends, our families.
This time, it was Moose and Midge.
Next time, it could be you...
your girlfriend, your family.
It's time to do something about it.
I want us to start a watch group.
Not to canvass the town,
that's not workable,
but to focus on Riverdale
High, its students,
its faculty and staff, its parents,
where we all hang out, an extra
circle of protection around it.
You want us to take it to
the streets, kick some ass.
That was my first thought, too, Reg.
But no, no weapons, no violence.
I'm talking about a patrol, an extra
set of eyes and ears for the police.
And what if we run into the killer?
Then we call Sheriff Keller.
We're not vigilantes. We're watchdogs.
- We're the Watchdogs.
- We're not called the Watchdogs, Reg.
We're called the Red Circle.
We hold the line.
We're not waiting for the next
attack. We're protecting our own.
- Whoo! Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
[STUDENTS CHEERING]
[PHILLIPS] Fahrenheit 451,
by one of my favorite
authors, Ray Bradbury.
Let's start with the title.
Can anyone tell me its significance?
What? Damn it!
People, there's a
burning book on the cover.
Fahrenheit 451 is the
temperature at which paper burns.
"It was a pleasure to burn."
Indeed.
Thank you, Mr... Jones.
And welcome to hell.
[BELL RINGS]
Uh, hi, Mr. Phillips?
[PHILLIPS] Mr. Jones.
Toni was telling me you used
to advise the school paper.
I was wondering what happened.
Drugs and gangs came to Southside High.
Trying to get students
interested in the school paper
was an exercise in futility.
I'm interested. I have experience.
At Riverdale High, I wrote
for the Blue and Gold.
I'll put in the work.
Your articles online?
Mm-hm.
I'll take a look, let you know.
[JUGHEAD] Thanks.
Hey. What happened last night?
You said you were coming to Veronica's.
Yeah, something came up.
Something in the woods?
Betty, don't take this the wrong way,
but how many years did I listen to
you go on about Archie and Jughead?
Did you ask my permission to date them?
No. You didn't need it.
And I don't need yours.
- [BETTY] Dating is one thing. This is...
- It's none of your business.
I'll, uh, catch you later.
Kev. [SCOFFS]
So, button-down Kevin Keller
has a sex-drive. So what?
So, it's putting him in
danger. Why won't he just stop?
Oh, Betty. How little you
know of the human psyche.
Kevin used to be a lonely,
awkward fat boy with acne.
Now he's a smoke-show.
And?
In his mind, he's still
that unattractive Pugsley.
Kevin wants validation, connection,
even if he has to find it in the woods.
Even with a killer on the
loose. Even if you don't approve.
[VERONICA] I have
incredible news, Archiekins.
You are invited to dinner with
my parents, chez moi.
- Oh, Ronnie, this week's crazy...
- I don't care.
Archie, this is nonnegotiable.
That drive-by he did
was a kind gesture,
but this, this is like... I don't wanna
call it a test, though it kind of is.
- What am I being tested for?
- Not you, my father.
Can he just be a dad for one night?
No agenda other than getting to
know someone who's important to me.
- In that case, I'll be there for you.
- I don't have time to teach you Spanish,
but I've selected phrases for
you to memorize and practice.
And can we not talk about that
private army you're starting? Okay?
Thanks.
[BETTY] Hey.
- Hey. [SIGHS]
- [BETTY] What's wrong?
Your mother got some fan mail.
He calls himself the Black Hood and
he wants us to publish this letter.
He wants everyone to know
that he shot Fred Andrews
and Moose and Midge...
and murdered Geraldine Grundy.
Are you sure that this is real?
[ALICE] Oh, it's real, all right.
[KELLER] "This is the Black Hood.
I am the man who shot
the adulterer at Pop's.
I killed the child predator in Greendale.
I shot the drug- and sex-addicted
teenagers at Lovers' Lane.
Riverdale is not innocent.
It's a town of hypocrites,
degenerates, criminals.
My wrath is the price of your
lies, your secrets, your sins.
I will not stop. I cannot be stopped.
I am the wolf. You are the flock.
This is the blood-letting.
You will hear from me again."
Well, Tom, how real is this threat?
Well, it's definitely
Fred Andrews' wallet.
These sunglasses, I'm
checking with Greendale P.D.
Alice, in the spirit of public
safety... Tom, tell me if you disagree.
It's important to not give
this lunatic an audience.
Mayor McCoy, it is our responsibility
to let the public know he's out there
targeting his next victim.
If you print this,
you're gonna cause panic.
I want a media blackout for 24
hours on this letter, at least.
And I'll be taking it into Evidence.
I'll send you a copy.
[ALICE] Oh, no need, sheriff.
We made one right before
we sent it to the printer
for tomorrow's front page.
Mr. Jones, I read your
work. I'm impressed.
So much so that I'll consider
reopening the Red and the Black
on two conditions:
One, no gangs. Two, no jingle-jangle.
Write about them. If I see you
trafficking in either, we're done.
That will not be a problem for me.
Did you think I'd let
teenagers form a militia?
We're trying to help, sheriff.
- People are scared.
- A lynch mob won't help that.
- Sheriff Keller.
- We have a big problem here, Waldo.
You see, your student has
formed his own private army.
The Red Circle is a school club.
You endorse this?
[WEATHERBEE] Archie has
shown tremendous initiative.
You can't fault students for
wanting to protect each other.
Morning, Waldo.
[ARCHIE CHUCKLES]
[COUGHS]
Well, it's no New York Times.
But, hey, kudos on finding
your safe space, snowflake.
Yeah, all I need now is a
photographer with an amazing eye
and a hunger for social justice,
and I think I'll be set.
[DOOR OPENS]
Topaz. Let's bounce.
Jones, wanna come with?
We're going to the quarry.
Uh, I don't have my beach bod yet.
What? You'll ask for help from the
Serpents, but you won't hang with us?
Don't come crawling to us, hat in hand,
when some Ghoulie decides to earn his
stripes by taking out FP Jones' kid.
Duly noted. Thank you, Sweet Pea.
I appreciate what you and the Serpents
have done for me and my dad. I do.
But I'm done. Okay?
No more favors coming your way.
Hey, hey, he made up his mind, okay?
Take the hint, Sweet Pea.
He's just not that into you.
Let's motor.
Catch you later, Jones.
- I'm going. I'm leaving Riverdale.
- You'll give the babies whiplash.
[POLLY] I've called the
farm. They still have room.
Farm? What farm?
The farm Jason and I were running
to before my life fell apart.
Honey, let's just talk about
this. Why are you leaving?
Ask Mom. She's the one baiting a killer.
- A killer targeting sinners.
- Polly, you're not a sinner.
I'm an unwed mother
carrying my cousin's babies.
I am the poster child for sin.
That's it. Over my dead body are
you gonna run off to some farm
and give birth in a trough, no doubt.
It might be over your dead body, Mother,
but it won't be over mine or my babies'.
Polly!
I'll talk to her.
Midge wanted to thank
you... for saving my life.
[SCOFFS]
You're like her new hero now.
[SIGHS]
Hey, so, what were you doing
out there in the woods, anyways?
[CHUCKLES] What were you doing out
there with Midge? Besides drugs.
That was her idea. She likes
to get a little crazy sometimes.
I like Midge, a lot.
Sometimes I'm not sure
we're that great a match.
Kevin, are you okay?
I haven't been making
great decisions lately.
Lying to my dad, sneaking
around and going into the woods.
I know it's dangerous,
but I can't stop myself.
It's like I don't even
care. What is that?
I don't know, but guys like us?
Like you?
In a town like Riverdale?
We don't have a lot of options.
So, even if something bad
could happen, we go for it,
'cause what if for ten minutes...
or maybe even just for two
minutes... we're not alone?
[CHUCKLES] I'm glad you're
okay, Moose. Midge, too.
Kevin.
You don't have to go.
Or you can come back, whenever.
If you wanna hang out... or talk.
You're playing with
fire, I want you to know.
I'm polishing cutlery, Mom.
In advance of my parents getting
to know my boyfriend over dinner.
That may be your agenda, but it's
not necessarily your father's.
He's making an effort,
I'm making an effort.
The only person not
making an effort is you.
- I'm trying to warn you.
- About what, Mom?
What do you think Daddy's gonna do?
Please, God, enough of
these veiled threats.
Tell me you think he's dangerous.
Say it to my face or
forever hold your peace
because we're never having
this conversation again.
Can't do it, can you?
Just remember, you're the
one who welcomed him back.
[SCOFFS]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
- Huh. I thought no weapons.
- I've had this bat since I was 10.
Check out the backseat.
Old-school.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh...
- [JUGHEAD] Betty.
- So, this is the Red and Black.
You cannot be here at
night unless you are armed.
Well, I am.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay, honestly? I hit pay dirt.
Do you remember how
no one could explain
the local component of Clifford
Blossom's drug pipeline?
That jingle-jangle, the stuff Moose and
Midge were on? It's coming from here.
My dad said that Serpents never deal
in hard drugs, but the Ghoulies do.
Well, is it wise to be writing
about gangs and drugs while
you're going to school here?
You worried about me?
Well, yeah, Jug.
I thought you liked me reckless.
[DOOR CREAKS]
Oh, sorry, guys. I didn't
see the sock on the door.
It's okay. Heh.
Hey, Toni. Ah...
Betty, this is Toni. She is the
photographer for the newspaper.
Oh.
- This is Betty. This is my girlfriend.
- [BETTY] Hi, Toni.
- Huh. You are not at all what I pictured.
- Really? What did you picture?
[TONI] Uh, Emily the Strange.
Winona Ryder from Beetlejuice.
Hey, look what Betty got us.
Great minds.
Well. Perfect timing. Zip me up?
Of course.
You know, the one thing about this
apartment is that sound carries.
Even in my study, I could hear you
and Veronica in the dining room...
as if we're all together.
If you wanna burn your
relationship with our daughter,
that's your business.
But... don't ever try
to poison her against me.
Clear?
- Of course.
- Yeah.
You look nice.
[ON JUKEBOX] ♪ Close
your eyes, now, baby ♪
- [KEVIN] Thank you, Delores.
- [DELORES] Anytime.
Have a good run, Kevin.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES]
Oh, Kevin.
You precious, beautiful,
compulsive piece of trash.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, this is Archie.
Okay, slow down. I can
barely... Are you sure?
No, don't. Don't do that.
Just get somewhere safe, okay?
Turn back to Hastings Street.
Stay calm. We're on our way.
[ENGINE REVS & TIRES SQUEAL]
- [ARCHIE] This is where she said she was.
- Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure. Ethel? Ethel?
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[ETHEL] Archie!
Archie.
- Ethel, what happened?
- [ETHEL] I was walking home
and this van just pulled up
and it circled back three times.
- [ARCHIE] Did you see him? Recognize him?
- No. No, I'm sorry.
- Are you okay?
- [ETHEL] Yeah, I'm fine.
[TWIG SNAPS]
- [BETTY] Where do you think he is?
- [VERONICA] I don't know...
Oh, my God. What are
you guys doing here?
Cheryl called me, said you were going
for a jog, headed towards Fox Forest.
Fact.
You said you weren't
gonna do this anymore.
For God's sake, Betty, what
do you want from me?
I want you to have more respect
for yourself than this.
- [KEVIN] Respect for myself?
- Yes.
We have been friends a long time,
but you still have no idea...
Well, then tell me, Kev, please.
You act like we've got the same
set of options, but we don't.
You live in this pale-pink world
of milk shakes and first kisses
and "Am I gonna date Archie or Jughead?"
Except for when she's Dark Betty.
[KEVIN] Right, right. Except for when
you're exploring your BDSM sexuality,
which again, you're allowed to
do, but I'm not, because why?
This is what I've got,
Betty. Me, these woods.
So, please don't come here
and tell me it's disgusting.
If you can't accept what I do,
whatever I do, then we're just...
We're not really friends.
[DOOR SLAMS IN DISTANCE]
[MAN] Jughead.
Jughead.
[JUGHEAD] Wait!
[JUGHEAD GRUNTING]
[FRED] How's the war on terror going?
[SIGHS] It's going.
Oh. So, listen, um, about
this dinner with the Lodges.
Hiram is more than just
your girlfriend's dad.
He's my business partner.
Ronnie and I get that. Even if things
with us change, I'll be a gentleman.
I won't do anything to offend her
or Mr. and Mrs. Lodge. I promise.
Problem is, Hiram, he's
the kind of person who...
Well, he'll find a way to be
offended if that's what he wants.
- Just be careful, okay?
- Yeah.
[BETTY] Can't you just take a day off?
It's not that bad.
Just some cuts and bruises.
I told you that
motorcycle was risky, Jug.
You promised you were
always gonna wear a helmet.
[JUGHEAD] It was just around the block.
Don't blame me, all
right? Blame the pothole.
I thought you were gonna say that
you got jumped by those Creepies...
Ghoulies. But, no, the
Serpents won't allow that.
They got Jughead's back.
Even though he's not a member.
It's just family loyalty.
Great, well... I've gotta go to school,
try and fix this mess with Kevin.
- Toni, will you keep an eye on him?
- All over it.
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
Don't tell Betty.
She doesn't need to know.
We warned you about the Ghoulies.
You'll take them more seriously now.
Yeah.
I will now.
[ARCHIE] The posole was
really great, Mrs. Lodge.
Glad you liked it.
So, Veronica tells me you
rescued the Muggs girl.
Yeah, but the creeper got away.
We need to be faster
with our response time.
Yeah, because you'd like to be
ahead of the threat. I understand.
So, tell me, have you ever had rum?
Rum? What, like the alcohol?
Yeah, there's a signature
Lodge family label. It's...
I have some in my study.
Would you like to try it?
Of course he would.
Oh, palomita, would you mind if
Archie and I had a little chat, man-to-man?
Okay. Sure, Daddy.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
Poor little princess.
The king will always
keep her at arm's length.
She'll never be allowed
in his private throne room.
Cab's waiting.
[BETTY] Polly, are you sure
this is how you wanna leave?
Without even telling them goodbye?
- I know Mom's sorry.
- She's always sorry.
Until she does the next thing.
I'll be fine.
- I'll call you. I promise.
- Okay. [SNIFFS]
[HIRAM] I like having her up
there, looking over my shoulder.
Keeps me honest.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Yeah.
Not the sort your father
approves of, is it?
Uh, rum? No, not... Not really, sir.
No, I meant about your Red Circle.
[ARCHIE] He's still trying to wrap his
head around it, I guess. Me too still.
[HIRAM] You know, Archie...
I hope we can respect each other.
You know, moving forward.
Yeah. Yes. Of course, Mr. Lodge.
No more sneaking into
my daughter's bedroom.
Ever.
You know, and, uh, never...
ever... hurt Veronica.
You know, I do have a thought
about your Red Circle, actually.
You know, it's a noble idea.
But evil, Archie, has no regards
for nobility or good intention.
You know, sometimes, defending
yourself, it's not enough.
You need to, uh, strike
back. Go on the offensive.
This Black Hood, he's waging
a war based on terror and fear.
Those are his weapons.
They should be yours, too.
[LINE RINGS]
It's Kevin. Leave a message, if
people still do things like that.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hey. How's it going?
- [MAN] Kind of late to be out here.
- I'm waiting for someone.
Is it me?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
I could give you a ride. Drop
you somewhere. Come on, get in.
[KEVIN GRUNTS]
[BETTY] Moose and Midge were shot.
Tell me you won't go back there.
- You know what? That's okay.
- What, you're playing hard-to-get?
- Come on, get in.
- No, I'm not.
Get in the damn car, you little tease.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[KELLER] It's late.
Hi, Dad.
Where have you been?
Betty had this thing.
Don't lie to me, boy.
Betty was here earlier, looking for you.
We had a talk about...
what you've been doing.
With everything that's going on
right now, I need to know you're safe.
You hear me?
I know that, uh...
there are certain things
that we don't talk about.
Maybe it's time that we start trying.
Okay?
Okay, son.
[KEVIN CRYING]
[KELLER] It's okay.
Oh, I know that smile.
- I've been thinking...
- Oh, boy.
I want a more active
role in Lodge Industries.
I am a shareholder, am I not?
That's an honorary title, Veronica.
[VERONICA] Let's make
it a real one, Daddy.
I wanna get my hands dirty.
I wanna be in the room where it happens.
Unless there's a reason
why I shouldn't be involved.
Get a peek behind the curtain?
No. None at all.
Of course you should be involved.
You're a Lodge, after all.
[HIRAM CHUCKLES]
♪ Oh, Father, tell me ♪
♪ That we get what we deserve ♪
♪ Oh, we get what we deserve ♪
Is this seat taken?
[JUGHEAD] Those kids in the fairy
tales who go into the woods...
they don't come back the same.
They're always changed
in some fundamental way.
Sometimes for the better.
More often for the worse.
That's the common misconception
about fairy tales.
They very rarely... have a happy ending.
[ARCHIE] Doiley, is it recording?
This is a message for the coward
calling himself the Black Hood.
You think you can attack
us from the shadows.
But Riverdale is a lot stronger
than you. And we're not afraid.
See, there's only one of you.
But we are legion.
We're called the Red Circle.
And we're coming for you.
We will find you.
We will hunt you.
And we will end you.
♪ Way down we go ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --