[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
[Toni] You wanna get through this?
Hang with the Serpents.
You think you can come to my house
and there wouldn't be payback?
[Alice] I'm wondering
when you're gonna actually address
the real problem in Riverdale,
the Southside.
[Fred] We need to be united.
If we let the fear take over, we're dead.
I want a more active role
in Lodge Industries.
Of course. You're a Lodge, after all.
- Everybody needs to leave.
- The Black Hood is coming.
This is from the Black Hood.
He says he's doing it for me.
- Hello?
- [man] Hello, Betty.
This is the Black Hood speaking.
How...?
How do I know this is real?
- "I will strike next where it all began."
- Were you there?
- At the Town Hall?
- Oh, yes.
But you didn't hurt anyone?
Tonight was all about you.
What do you want?
The same as you.
To set Riverdale
on the righteous path again.
To cleanse it of sinners.
- Isn't that what you want?
- Not by killing people.
Only the ones who deserve it.
People like your sister.
I know about
the sin she carries in her womb.
I also know she's at a farm
two hours north.
If you try to warn her, I'll know.
If you tell the police we've spoken
or your mystery-loving boyfriend,
I'll carve her like a jack-o'-lantern.
Please, don't hurt her.
- Who are you talking to? It's late.
- Then don't you deny me.
- It's Jughead, wasn't it?
- Yeah.
I gave him the benefit of the doubt.
Now he's living on the Southside
amongst criminals and degenerates.
He's showing his true colors. No doubt
inspiring your stunt at Town Hall.
- Pulling the fire alarm?
- I didn't know what else to do.
Given the letter the Black Hood sent.
If he even wrote it.
Sheriff Keller says something seems off.
He's gonna have it analyzed
with the one I got.
In the meantime, I want you home
straight after school. Are we clear?
Yeah. Sorry, Mom.
[Archie] I did what Weatherbee asked.
Wrote an apology
and posted a new video
apologizing some more.
So, this, uh, Red Circle business,
it's over?
I'm happy to hear it.
I've been missing my son.
[phone chimes]
I need to tell you something,
but you can't tell anyone else.
Not Veronica, not Jughead, not your dad.
Just no one. You promise me?
Yeah, sure. I promise.
The Black Hood called me.
- What?
- No, keep walking.
Wait. The Black Hood called you?
Yes, it's risky for me to be telling you,
but we're best friends.
We live right next door.
Us walking to school together
would look normal
to anyone watching, including him.
- You think he's watching us?
- He could be.
- I know it sounds crazy, but it was him.
- Tell the police, even if it's not him.
It is him. He told me if I went
to the police or told Jughead...
God, he knows where Polly is, Arch.
- If he calls, I have to answer.
- I won't let you go through this alone.
"This most recent incident confirms
that the real threat is not the Black Hood
but the Southside
and its corruptive forces.
Developer and ex-con Hiram Lodge
boasts his SoDale project will revitalize
the forsaken neighborhood,
but this reporter speculates Hiram Lodge
doesn't want to fix our problems,
merely profit from them."
Right before our open house.
Thank you, Alice Cooper.
We can't let anything derail this project.
Not Alice, not the Southside gangs,
not some hooded psychopath.
Well, right now,
our biggest problem is capital.
We're running out of it and fast.
I've invited investors to the open house.
The St. Clairs from New York.
Wait. They are? Nicky included?
I haven't seen Nicky in forever.
Yeah, he's a budding music producer now.
And his father is King Midas rich.
We get him to invest, others will follow.
You wanted a seat at the table.
Nick has his father's ear.
Help us close this.
Show him all the good things
Riverdale has to offer.
With pleasure.
[indistinct chatter]
[Fogarty] Sweet Pea. Take care of this.
- Nice article your girlfriend's mom wrote.
- I saw that.
Dilton Doiley was stabbed
and you jumped him?
The idiot stabbed himself
with his own knife.
[Sweet Pea] We didn't jump him.
There was a fight.
Bulldogs versus Serpents. See this?
Andrews gave it to me before
his girlfriend shot a gun into the air.
- What happened?
- And, of course,
Northsiders get off scot-free,
the rest of us are hauled in by police.
- It's payback time.
- What are you guys talking about?
What is...? What is that?
Is that a pipe bomb?
Fogarty's cousin served in the Army.
He's gonna build us something.
We'll do it after hours.
It'll shut the Riverdale Register down.
You think blowing up
a building will make things better?
- Can't get any worse.
- Yeah, Sweet Pea, it can.
- Let me talk to Archie, figure this out.
- That's your answer for everything. Talk.
We don't know who you stand with.
Us? Or them?
You can't be half a Serpent.
Great. So, Archie started World War III.
Northside has been
dumping on us for years.
Your dad tried to keep the peace.
Avoid bloodshed.
Now that he's gone, idiots like Sweet Pea
think there's one path and solution.
Violence.
Nick and I were the
"will-they-or-won't-they" of our jet set.
He's an outrageous flirt,
but we never dated.
We'd hop from club to club,
go on these madcap adventures,
stay up all night.
- Who's this now?
- Oh, Archiekins, don't be jelly.
It's just a ghost
from my bad-girl past, Nick St. Clair,
breezing to town for the open house.
You have nothing to worry about.
I think this Northsider's lost.
I'm not.
I'm over being half a Serpent.
Wow. You'll do anything to protect
your Northside buddies.
My father was a Serpent.
He led you.
I wanna stand with you guys.
Tall Boy was the one
who gave me this jacket.
It's finally time I start wearing it.
So, now you wanna be a Serpent, huh?
Let's see if you survive
the initiation first.
["Lollipop" playing on phone]
♪ Lollipop ♪
"Unknown."
♪ Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop, oh, lolli-lolli... ♪
[phone beeps]
- Hello?
- [Black Hood] Your mother's at work.
Yes, she and my dad are.
I know. I'm looking at them
through a big picture window.
Are you alone?
I am.
She's a thorn in our sides, your mother.
We can't have her looming over us.
- Wait, if you're suggesting...
- Check your e-mail.
Publish what I've sent.
Then I'll know you're loyal.
I want something in return
to prove your loyalty.
How about...
you do this for me,
and then you get to ask me a question.
And I have to answer.
You have until tomorrow night.
[Archie] Oh, my God. Is that...?
That's my mom.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
- What the hell?
- [man] Your initiation begins now.
With you assuming guardianship
of the Beast.
- You gotta be kidding.
- [Toni] What do you think of the Beast?
He stinks. And he barks all the time.
He's got no boundaries.
Every new recruit has to care of Hot Dog.
It's tradition. This is our third Hot Dog.
Oh, Hot Dog the third.
- It's getting borderline ridiculous.
- Oh, kind of like Forsyth the third?
[both chuckle]
Mom went after the Black Hood hard.
No surprise he wants to humiliate her.
We can't do it.
It'd destroy her credibility.
And build yours with the Black Hood.
Anyway, what credibility?
Your mom's always going after our friends.
It would blindside her.
We can't publish it.
[Veronica] Mr. and Mrs. St. Clair.
Nicholas. On behalf of my mother
and father, welcome to Riverdale.
While you're in town,
think of me as your corporate concierge.
Anything you need, ask away.
How about a better hotel, to start?
Now, now, Nicholas.
It's not the Waldorf, nor the Plaza,
but the Five Seasons,
like all of Riverdale, has its charms.
One charm.
Veronica Lodge...
as lovely as ever.
We sent the letters to two specialists,
but the handwriting wasn't a match.
Whoever wrote your letter was a copycat,
or pranking you, or...
Or something more banal,
like a teenager acting out
to get attention.
You think I wrote it?
The cipher was cribbed
from a Nancy Drew book of all places.
Mom, what possible reason could I have
for making this up?
Maybe you and your Serpent boyfriend
cooked this up because you were bored.
We're not gonna rule anything out yet,
not until we know what we're dealing with.
[grunts]
[phone chimes]
[Jughead] A Serpent never shows cowardice.
If a Serpent is killed or imprisoned,
their family will be taken care of.
Serpents, uh...
Come on. Focus.
You need to take this seriously.
Okay, I am, Toni. I swear to God I am.
It's just...
- First the Beast and now these laws?
- Why the change of heart, anyway?
Why go from conscientious objector
to full-fledged member?
Because of something you said.
My dad was the only one
keeping idiots like Sweet Pea in line.
Someone needs to step up...
to keep an all-out war from erupting.
I am taking this seriously, Toni.
So, from the top.
What is the fourth law?!
No Serpent is left for dead!
What is the fifth law?!
A Serpent never betrays his own!
What is the sixth?!
In unity, there is strength!
[all] In unity there is strength!
[rock music playing over speakers]
You know the laws.
Now it's time for the next trial.
Retrieve the knife.
What?
A rattlesnake, Toni.
A rattlesnake bit me and drew blood.
One that had
its venom glands removed, okay?
The important thing is you showed no fear,
grabbed the knife,
and remembered the laws.
Which means you're almost a Serpent now.
My regular, Pop. Thanks.
I don't judge you, Alice.
- It was years ago.
- What are you talking about?
["Chances" playing over speakers]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ What are the chances? ♪
Who gave you this article?
Because I know that I ripped it out
of every public archive.
Maybe it was one of the thousands
of Southsiders you attack in your paper.
I mean, really, Mom.
You talk trash about FP,
Jughead, the Serpents,
when you yourself were one.
Why would you publish that?
Revenge.
Plain and simple.
No, Mom. Not revenge.
Justice.
Against you
and your holier-than-thou attitude.
Betty, that is enough.
I'm so glad you two are
getting this chance to meet.
Although your brown-nosing at dinner
was over-the-top, Nicky.
How dare you? I love your mother's flan.
Although, I still have room
for more dessert.
Here.
No, thank you. I'm full.
Veronica Lodge turning down a bump.
What a brave new world it is.
How about it, Big Red?
So, what is it that you country mice do
for fun up here?
Catch lightning bugs with Mason jars?
- No, we...
- Basically.
Ronnie.
What kind of kink is this?
I wear them when playing
with Josie and the Pussycats.
- You're in a band called the Pussycats?
- Mm-hm.
Just when I thought you
couldn't possibly get any sexier.
[chuckles]
["Lollipop" playing on phone]
♪ Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop, oh... ♪
Hello?
[Black Hood] How does it feel, Betty?
Knocking your mother off her high horse?
We had a deal.
What's your question?
And it can't be my name.
The face under the hood...
would I recognize it?
Yes.
Do you feel closer to me now?
I do. I feel as if we're friends.
But I'm selfish, Betty.
I don't like sharing you
with other people.
I need you to cut them out of your life,
or I will my way.
Let's start with that daughter
of a philanderer
and an embezzler,
complicit in her father's crimes.
Veronica's not...
She's innocent.
Oh, Betty. You don't really believe that.
[line clicks]
["Count On Me" playing over speakers]
[door opens and bell jingles]
Betty Cooper.
You are a sight for sore eyes.
Thanks for coming to meet me.
♪ When you're needing rest ♪
♪ From the road ♪
God, I've missed you.
I've just been feeling...
I don't know.
- Unmoored.
- Me, too.
- I wanted to make sure you were alive.
- What do you mean?
That exposé that you published
about your mom,
- that article that you wrote.
- Oh, um...
That's a long story, yeah, pretty intense.
What happened to your hand?
Oh, I'm dog-sitting.
Do you remember Hot Dog, that mutt?
Don't worry. He's got his shots.
♪ Everybody needs a pick-me-up
You can count on me ♪
♪ Come what may come what might
Everybody falls down ♪
I wish we could just go.
Just hop on a motorcycle
and just leave Riverdale.
Go someplace where there's
no Northside, or Southside...
or Serpents, Ghoulies.
No...
crazy moms, no Black Hoods.
Like Romeo and Juliet,
but we live happily ever after instead.
[applause]
You Pussycats are pearls
before the swine of Riverdale.
You have to come to the party I'm hosting
tonight in your honor. Let's say 10:00?
My room at the Five Seasons.
Did somebody say party?
Hi there.
I'm Riverdale's resident it-girl,
Cheryl Blossom.
You must be Veronica's old-school chum.
Nick St. Clair.
Now that's a name I can get behind.
Ten o'clock, you said?
I'll be there at 11.
Betty.
- What's up?
- I, uh, went by your house this morning,
to walk you to school,
but your mom said you'd already left.
Did he call you again?
No. He didn't.
Betty.
My old friend Nick here is having
a little soirée at his hotel tonight.
Will you come?
Betty is my bestie and the best.
I won't take no for an answer.
I wouldn't miss it.
Then we walk into the Gilded Lily,
and there's Gal again.
[laughs]
- Gal?
- Gadot. Keep up, Archie.
Archiekins, a refill, s'il vous plait?
Forget teetotaling. Let's move
to something with more kick.
- Is that...?
- Jingle-Jangle? Why, yes, it is.
- I hooked him up.
- Tasters? Who's up first?
- We're not doing...
- Don't take this the wrong way,
but you are an epic buzzkill.
[pop music playing over speakers]
- Come on, V. Like back in the day?
- [chuckles]
Aren't you supposed to be showing me
a good time, per Daddy's orders?
Down, Nicky.
I'm just getting going.
And now that you mention it,
I, in fact, wouldn't mind
a little sugar to spice up this party.
What? Every other night
it's burgers and milkshakes.
Can't we just cut loose
and pretend we're normal for once?
- I'm in.
- Me, too.
Kevin?
[Nick] Pussycats, care to partake?
- Betty?
- No, thanks.
- It'll be fun.
- I said no, V.
Okay, relax, Betty.
This is strictly voluntary.
Perhaps we should decamp to the bedroom,
to not corrupt the country mice.
I changed my mind. I'm in.
Bravo, Archie Andrews.
There's that good, strong Riverdale stock
I've been jonesing for.
[chuckles]
♪ It feels good to be running
From the devil ♪
♪ Another breath
And I'm up another level ♪
♪ It feels good
To be up above the clouds ♪
♪ It feels good for the first time
In a long time now ♪
[girl whoops]
Come on, Betty.
Don't be such a wallflower.
You're boyfriend-less for a night.
Have some fun.
Like you, you mean?
You're making a fool out of yourself,
just acting like some privileged,
shallow, airhead party girl.
- [scoffs] Excuse me?
- Yeah.
I mean, it's all just recycled banter...
and plunging necklines,
and throwing shade to distract us all
from the fact that there's
nothing going on underneath.
- Betty, what are you saying?
- What we're all thinking.
That the only reason Veronica
hangs out with us is circumstance.
She's not our friend.
The minute someone
from her trashy past shows up,
she starts using us for drugs,
or music, or distraction.
And why should we be surprised?
Like father, like daughter, right?
- You better shut it down, Betty.
- Or what, Veronica?
You'll have your dad put a hit on me?
Or maybe you'll do it yourself.
Because you may have
fooled all of them, but not me.
Try to reform all you want,
but you're a bad person, Veronica.
You'll always be a bad person.
Why don't you go then,
if I'm such a monster.
[door closes]
- Veronica...
- I'm fine.
Obviously, she's not.
Wanna go after her? Be my guest.
I'll be damned if I'm chasing Betty down
after that... Whatever it was.
In fact, Reggie?
Turn the music up, will you?
What's up?
Jughead, I, um...
I came to warn you, I guess.
If you're having any second thoughts...
now would be the time to back out
because the final trial...
is on a whole other level.
The Gauntlet, you mean?
If it's anything like the Beast,
I'll be fine.
- It's whatever.
- No, Jughead, it's not whatever.
You join us,
you gotta be willing to die for us.
Because we will for you.
And your Northside friends,
your girlfriend?
You're gonna look up one day,
and they'll all be gone.
Because that's what happens
when you join a gang.
The Serpents are no exception.
Consider me warned.
Thank you, Toni.
Never has one of my parties
fizzled out so spectacularly.
I don't know what got into Betty.
She's my best friend, believe it or not.
Those things that she said,
you're not a bad person, Veronica.
In fact...
you're incredible.
You're smart, vivacious.
And you're sexy.
Nick, I'm sorry if I gave you
the wrong impression.
I'm with Archie.
Oh, come on, V.
You barely looked at that hayseed yokel.
You were all over me.
Nick, we're friends.
- Old friends.
- No.
Nick. Nick, I mean it. Stop!
Same old Veronica, huh?
You flirt and you tease.
But, in the end...
you think you're better than me.
You're a pig.
With the power to implode this deal
your father's trying to make happen.
Unless you want that to go away,
I'd think of ways
you might start showing me appreciation.
If you need any help...
I can suggest a couple.
[door closes]
[sighs]
["Lollipop" playing on phone]
♪ Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli... ♪
[phone beeps]
I did it.
But now I want my question.
What will make you stop?
[Black Hood] You. As long as you continue
showing me your devotion.
I can't keep doing this.
Sure you can.
Jughead, the son of a Serpent.
- No.
- He's not worthy of your love.
Cut him out of your life.
Or I will.
[line clicks]
What the hell was that last night?
- Betty?
- I lied to you.
When you asked me
if the Black Hood called again, he did.
[Betty sighs]
And he told me
to cut Veronica out of my life or he...
And now he wants me
to do the same with Jug.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- You'd try to talk me out of it.
You're right.
It's my mistake.
Archie, put the phone...
Put the phone down!
Listen to me.
He hasn't attacked or killed anyone
since we started talking.
I think this is distracting him.
Betty, he's torturing you.
Making you hurt your mom,
Veronica, and now Jughead?
How are you gonna put him
and yourself through that?
I was hoping maybe you would do it.
What?
Maybe you could tell him...
that we just need to stay away
from each other for a while.
Something, anything,
to just keep him away,
to appease the Black Hood.
- Betty.
- It doesn't have to be cruel.
Just enough to make Jug believe it.
- We can walk it back later.
- You hope we can.
No. We can.
And we will.
Please, Arch.
Don't quit on me now.
[indistinct chatter]
[lounge music playing over speakers]
Hey. So nice to see you.
Thank you for coming.
Glad to see you.
If this turnout doesn't convince
the St. Clairs to invest,
- I don't know what will.
- Yeah.
Hey, mija. How'd it go with Nick?
- Did he say something?
- No, haven't seen him.
From all reports,
your charm offensive is paying off.
Good work.
Oh, there's Nick now.
Uh-oh. Looks like
we're running low on canapés.
Excuse me while I go quietly yell
at the caterer.
[Hermione]
And I have a partner to wrangle.
Yeah.
The point of this open house
is to socialize.
I figured I'd leave that to the pros.
You're not without your charms,
Fred Andrews.
We're glad you're back at work.
"We," huh?
Hiram Lodge.
- Been a long time, buddy.
- Hey, Hal.
- Glad you could make it.
- My pleasure.
Where's Alice?
Well, between us,
that mug shot took a toll on her.
We decided it would be better
if I covered the event alone.
Yes. We would love to have you
standing with us up on that stage.
Hell, you built it.
That's true.
Oh, my God.
♪ Thunder, thunder ♪
♪ Th-thunder, thunder ♪
♪ Thunder, thunder, thun... ♪
♪ Thunder, th-thunder
Thunder ♪
♪ Thunder, feel the thunder ♪
♪ Lightning and the thunder ♪
♪ Thunder, feel the thunder
Lightning ♪
- Alice...
- Shove it, Hal.
You're gonna need to top those off.
Thank you.
Before you throw a drink in my face...
I'm sorry.
I crossed a line.
You obliterated a line.
I strongly concur.
And it's not an excuse...
but over the last three months,
I've been...
in and out of rehab.
It's been...
a struggle, obviously.
[inaudible dialogue]
Last night was... messy.
But... we've all been there.
So, why don't we start over
with two glasses of ginger ale?
I'll drink to that.
- Archie?
- We gotta talk, Jug.
Uh, now's really not a good time. Okay?
You need to leave. You gotta go.
- What's going on?
- I'm serious.
- What do we have here?
- [Jughead] He was leaving.
Wait, you're friends with these thugs?
It's not what you think.
- Are you joining the Serpents?
- If he survives.
- Go ahead and call us thugs one more time.
- These are the guys who attacked me.
Who attacked Reggie,
Veronica, Dilton, your friends.
Wait, is this why you're here?
- To warn me?
- No.
I came to tell you
to stay away from Betty.
She doesn't want to see you anymore.
Screw you.
I just saw Betty yesterday. She...
- She was fine.
- No, dude.
She's been wanting to break up with you.
She's been agonizing over it.
Since you crossed the dark side.
She couldn't bring herself to do it.
So, she sent you?
Betty would never do that.
If you don't believe me, call her.
Feel free to tell her
you're a Serpent now.
I bet she'll love that.
She saw where you were headed, Jughead.
We all did. And she knows
you can't be with them and with her.
Come on, man.
You know it, too.
Tell Betty I got the message.
Yeah.
What?
Did you enjoy the show?
Show hasn't even started yet.
[lounge music playing over speakers]
- We didn't get a chance to talk.
- I'm choosing to blame Betty's meltdown.
- Heh.
- I'll let you make it up to me.
[speaking in French]
[Hiram] Ladies and gentlemen,
a new story begins in Riverdale tonight,
a story about reinvention and aspiration.
This building is the first chapter
of that story.
Luxury apartments, shopping,
and even a golf course.
The Southside as we know it will be gone,
replaced with a new Eden.
So, let's raise our glasses
to a brighter tomorrow.
Today,
let's celebrate with a little music.
[Josie] ♪ What's the time ♪
♪ Well, it's gotta be close to midnight ♪
♪ My body's talking to me ♪
♪ It says, "Time for danger" ♪
[Veronica]
♪ It says, "I wanna commit a crime" ♪
♪ Wanna be the cause of a fight ♪
♪ I wanna put on a tight skirt ♪
♪ And flirt with a stranger ♪
♪ I've had a knack from way back ♪
♪ At breaking the rules
Once I learn the game ♪
♪ Get up
Life's too quick ♪
♪ I know some place sick ♪
♪ Where this chick will dance
In the flames ♪
[Josie] ♪ We don't need any money ♪
♪ I always get in for free ♪
♪ You can get in, too ♪
♪ If you get in with me ♪
[Josie] ♪ Let's go out tonight ♪
Meow.
You all right?
I'm fine. I'm just...
I need... I need some air.
Okay.
[grunting]
Is that all you got?
♪ You wanna play, let's run away ♪
♪ We won't be back
Before it's New Year's Day ♪
♪ Take me out ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
Get off of her!
♪ In the evening I've got to roam ♪
♪ Can't sleep in the city
Of neon and chrome ♪
♪ Feels too damn much like home ♪
♪ When the Spanish babies cry ♪
♪ So, let's find a bar ♪
♪ So dark, we forget who we are ♪
♪ Where all the scars
From the nevers and maybes die ♪
♪ Let's go out tonight ♪
♪ Don't forsake me ♪
♪ Out tonight ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
["Lollipop" playing on phone]
♪ Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli, lollipop ♪
[phone beeps]
[Black Hood] Is it done?
Yes.
Ask me your question.
There's only one I care about now.
You wanna know who I am.
Well, there's an abandoned house
on the edge of Fox Forest,
at the end of the service road.
You'll find your answer there.
[line clicks]
["Lollipop" playing on phone]
♪ Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli... ♪
[phone beeps]
I'm here.
[Black Hood] Do you see it?
Yes.
It's the answer to your question.
Put it on.
Why?
Put it on and you'll see.
It's on.
Now turn around.
Why are you doing this to me?
To show you that we're the same.
[floorboard creaks]
- [phone beeps]
- [Archie] Hey.
- [static hissing]
- Archie?
I can't...
Come to the Pem...
Cheryl... Something bad...
What?
If you hadn't come when you did...
Where the hell is he?
You can put your cape away.
The Pussycats already saved me.
I feel so sick about this.
Nick's a monster.
There's no way he hasn't done this before,
probably under my nose.
- It's not your fault, Veronica.
- [Cheryl] I wanna press charges.
I want Nick to pay.
To suffer.
To burn in hell.
[crying]
["Sign Of The Times" playing]
Welcome to the Serpents.
Officially.
You're gonna have a hard time
hiding that from Betty.
I think that's a non-issue now.
♪ Hope you're wearing your best clothes ♪
♪ We never learn, we been here before ♪
♪ Why are we always stuck
And running from the bullets? ♪
["Lollipop" playing on phone]
♪ Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
- ♪ Lollipop, lolli... ♪
- [phone beeps]
I wasn't sure if you would call again.
[Black Hood]
There's one piece of unfinished business.
[sighs]
What's that?
The fact that you've been telling Archie
about our chats.
Betty, I've been watching you.
- You never said I couldn't tell Archie.
- You broke the rules.
- And now your sister will pay.
- Please, don't hurt her.
Then give me another name.
- Right now.
- What?
If you wanna save your sister,
give me another name.
The name of someone guilty.
Come on, Betty. One little name.
I won't. I can't do that.
Then I'll kill your sister,
and your mother,
and your father,
and everyone you hold dear.
Nick St. Clair.
He's staying at the Five Seasons.
I told you, we were the same.
Subtitles by explosiveskull