Previously on Riverdale...
[GUNSHOT]
[ALICE] He calls himself the Black Hood
and he wants us to publish this letter.
[SHERIFF] My wrath is
the price of your lies.
He sent it to the printer
for tomorrow's front page.
I'm gonna protect you. Nothing like
this is ever gonna happen to you again.
I swear it.
No!
- It's me.
- Are you freaking insane?
Sometimes, defending
yourself, it's not enough.
You need to go on the offensive.
We're called the Red Circle, and
we're coming for you. We will find you.
We'll hunt you and we will end you.
[JUGHEAD] Everyone's afraid to say it,
so let me be the first.
There is a serial killer amongst us.
San Francisco had the Zodiac.
New Orleans had the Axeman.
Texarkana, Texas, had the Phantom Killer.
The list goes on and on.
Add to their ranks Riverdale's
very own psychopath,
the Black Hood.
Are these research for school?
Research... But not for school.
It's a terrible thing,
what's going on in this town.
Who would've thunk it?
A serial killer in Riverdale?
I'm not just talking about him.
I'm also talking about that
awful video those boys put out.
[JUGHEAD] There it was. Terror was
seeping into the bedrock of Riverdale...
A Town Hall Meeting had
been set by Mayor McCoy.
_
People were afraid to
walk the streets alone,
especially as dusk approached.
Shops closed early, locks
were added to doors,
suspicions between the North
and South side deepened,
fanned into flames by Alice Cooper...
[BOTTLES CLATTERING]
As everyone wondered what
danger lurked in the dark.
When would we hear from
the Black Hood next,
and how far into darkness
would Archie go on his quest
to avenge his father...
And to stop the Black Hood?
To be honest, I had no idea
what Archie was thinking...
He didn't say anything
to you about this video?
- Am I my boyfriend's keeper?
- Basta, mija,
this isn't something you
should be joking about.
- It's a video, Mom...
- Yes, threatening violence.
Daddy, can you please tell
Mom she's overreacting?
On this matter, Veronica,
I stand with your mother.
Which means you are done
dating Archie Andrews.
This isn't Amish country, Mom,
I can date who I want to date.
And I'm not jumping to any conclusions
until I hear Archie's side of the story.
What are you smiling about?
The Black Hood, the Red
Circle, a Town Hall meeting,
so much chaos and confusion.
How could you do this
to me, Elizabeth? To us?
Polly asked for my help, Mom.
To run away, and you agreed?
We know where she is.
And frankly, thank God she's out of
Riverdale and away from that psycho.
And you think that that
guarantees her safety?
- Polly was scared.
- And you don't think that I am?
I'm terrified.
Every time that you walk out that door.
Every time that I call you, and
you don't pick up the phone...
My heart stops. But how am I
supposed to protect you two girls?
Right, when you go and do this.
And then you try to make me the monster.
[SOBBING]
[RECORDING] There's only one of you, but
we are legion. We're called the Red Circle.
So, what did you think,
that I wouldn't see it?
Dad, I was pissed off.
We were all pretty pissed off.
We were trying to send a
message, scare the Black Hood.
It's more likely you'll
antagonize this maniac
and become a target yourself.
Take it down right now, while I can see.
I already did, the original
post, but people keep sharing it.
Good grief, Archie.
My mom's spiraling. Do you think
you can come over during lunch...
Betty, I have to try and at least maintain
a semblance of being a student here.
Crap.
Uh, I gotta go, Betty, okay.
Hey, I'll talk to you later.
Hey. I'm guessing we're not
watching funny cat videos.
Check this out.
Some sick-in-the-head Northsider
posted a crazy-ass video,
- and we were just talking...
- About what?
Fogarty wants to earn
his Serpent stripes.
I say bring us the head of
that Northsider, and you're in.
I'm down with that.
No, guys, don't.
What, Jones?
I know this guy, he's a milquetoast.
He's a football player. It's kind
of a lame target, is all I'm saying.
You wanna prove something?
Why don't you go after the Black Hood?
And why would we do that?
The Black Hood's targeting Northsiders,
who do nothing but blame the Southside
for everything that's
wrong with this town.
And we're sick of it. The Black
Hood's doing our work for us.
He's a hero.
[ARCHIE] Black Hood. Black Hood.
We're called the Red Circle
and we're coming for you.
We will find you.
We will hunt you. We will end you.
Black Hood.
My parents want me to break up with you.
They basically think you're
the teen American Psycho.
Since when do you care about
what your parents think?
I don't, except when I
happen to agree with them.
Can't you just support
me on this, Ronnie?
On what?
Is this part of some master plan?
'Cause if it is, please enlighten me.
You know, to be honest,
I don't see why your dad's got
such a problem with it, Veronica.
He pretty much gave me the idea. In his
study, he basically told me I should...
Line up a bunch of semi-naked boys
straight out of Lord of the Flies
put them in red ski masks
and deliver some Unabomber-like manifesto?
Is that what he said you should do?
Fight fire with fire.
Fight terror with terror.
That's what he said.
[WEATHERBEE] Mr. Archie Andrews,
please report to the principal's office.
"We will find you. We will hunt you.
And we will end you."
These are your sentiments, Mr. Andrews.
And they are hardly comforting.
Principal Weatherbee, you have my word,
there's only one person who
should be scared by that video.
You're off the football
team, Mr. Andrews,
effective immediately.
In fact, there is no football team.
Not until this Red
Circle insanity is over.
If, by week's end, you
haven't written a signed letter
apologizing to the entire
Riverdale High community
and disbanding the Red Circle,
your suspension will begin,
and will continue until you've complied.
Care to re-think your position?
It's a crazy time, sir.
We all have to do
what we think is right.
Betty, okay.
So, telling my dad about me
cruising the woods? Not cool.
He even told my mom about it.
Also, I've re-upped my online
membership to redstatemeat.com,
so there'll be no cruising
for the foreseeable.
Betty? What? What is it?
I was going through the
Blue and Gold's mail...
And I got a letter from
the Black Hood killer...
He says he's doing it for me.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
"Betty, your words at
the Jubilee inspired me.
The town's sinners must
show their contrition.
If not, there will be more
suffering and bloodshed.
Enclosed is a cipher. It details
where I will punish the next sinner.
It is a test. Only you
may solve it, Betty."
[SIGHS]
My speech... Inspired him.
That stupid speech I wrote.
So the Black Hood was at the Jubilee.
The entire town was there.
We have to give this to my dad.
The cipher, yeah, sure,
but not the letter,
This is just...
For me. We can't tell anyone about it.
It's evidence.
Kevin, if we give this
letter to your dad,
he will tell my mom, and she will
make damn sure I'm nowhere near this.
- Good.
- No.
This is a test.
He said so himself. What if...
The start of the test
is to see what I do
with the letter? Do I share it? Or not?
Am I strong?
Or am I weak? Am I... Worthy?
He's a psychopath, Betty, and you
are in high school, not the FBI.
Isn't it better for people to be focusing
on the cipher, rather than the letter?
How would that even happen?
Mom, I'm so scared.
I didn't know what to do or who to call.
Oh, baby, please tell me what's
going on so I can make it better.
I got this envelope at the Blue and Gold.
Not another letter from the Black Hood.
No, not a letter.
Was there anything else
in the envelope? A note?
Not according to Betty.
Why a code this time,
and not another letter?
And why did he send it to
your daughter and not you?
Well, it's obvious, Sheriff.
He needs a platform to grandstand on,
and he's terrified of me.
Well, there's a cryptologist over in
Centerville. I'll get it over to him.
- In the meantime...
- I've already published it, Sheriff.
The entire town should be
trying to crack this code.
Don't you think?
Damn it, Andrews.
I told you we shouldn't
have made that video.
And now Weatherbee's suspended the team?
What if he comes after us next?
That's why you're wearing hoods,
Reggie, so that all the heat falls on me.
But it's not.
It's falling on all of us.
So please, bro, sign the letter.
No.
We disband the circle now, what
message does that show the Black Hood?
That we're weak, helpless.
No, we wanna force his hand.
By doing what exactly?
By going to his home
turf, the Southside.
What? Are you insane?
[ARCHIE] No, I've gone over this.
Mrs. Cooper is convinced the Black Hood
is a Southsider with an axe to grind,
which makes sense when you think
about the people he's attacked
My dad. A Northsider.
Moose and Midge both Northside kids.
- Grundy was in Greendale.
- Yeah, But before that, she taught here, Doiley.
Everyone has seen our video
and is riled up as hell, right?
We can only assume
the Black Hood is, too.
If there's even a chance that
he's a Southsider, us going there
into his territory, making our
presence known, could draw him out.
And the hunters become the hunted.
That's one way to find him.
Nope, I'm done.
We're done. Come on, guys
And then there was one.
Which is what you wanted, right?
You and the Black Hood,
mano a mano, to the death.
What the hell are you
talking about, Doiley?
I know you have a certain
item in your possession.
The Red Circle was just your
way to draw the Black Hood out.
And now you wanna go into his territory.
Maybe. Yeah.
You're gonna need a few things.
There's a place, on the
edge of town, they can help.
Go after dark.
Daddy?
When Archie came into this room...
Yeah.
What did you guys talk about?
Don't remember, to be
honest. Why do you ask?
I was just thinking. You know, one
of the things I love about Archie is
how earnest he is.
Not in a bad way, more in
an innocent sort of way.
Trusting. Kind.
Of course, that simplicity
also makes him...
Impressionable.
Vulnerable to certain forms of attack.
What are you going on about?
Manipulation.
If someone were to, say, pour poison
into one of his cute-as-a-button ears...
Some dark notion might
take shape in his mind.
Say... The Red Circle.
- If you're suggesting...
- I'm not suggesting anything, Daddy.
I'm asking, what did you
and my boyfriend talk about?
And I've already told
you I don't remember.
Now, if you'll excuse me, the
Swiss banks are about to close,
and I have a call with
the Lodge Charitable Trust.
Trust.
Right. Got it.
Have a nice call, Daddy.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES]
So... What are you reading?
[SIGHING]
Beware the Zodiac.
It's decent, though I prefer
Robert Graysmith's definitive books
- on the subject.
- [CELL BUZZING]
Are you gonna get that?
I can call her back later.
Jones, Jones, Jones. You disappoint me.
If serial killers are your
jam, might I suggest Ted Bundy,
Albert Fish, Aileen Wuornos.
They don't fit the profile.
Right. Unlike most serial
killers, our guy wears a mask.
Well, a hood, when he kills.
Suggests someone consumed
with self-loathing.
Conversely, he sends letters
and cryptos to the press.
Do you think he's narcissistic
or a Batman villain?
I'm a true crime junkie.
True crime is my crack.
I figured. And that's
why I'm seeking you out.
The Register took a break
from bashing the Southside
to post the Black Hood's cipher.
You wanna help me crack it?
Sure.
[SIGHS]
_
[KNOCKING]
Hey, I was just on my way out.
What's up?
- Okay.
- There.
That's my way of apologizing to you
for raining on your Red
Circle parade earlier today.
I wanna support you
and your comely crew,
even at the risk of enraging my parents.
Especially my father. Which
is just what he deserves
after playing mind games with you.
Ronnie, I really gotta go,
and anyway, it's too late. The
Red Circle fell apart this morning.
Wait, what? It's over? Already?
For the other guys, yeah,
but it's fine. This is my battle.
No one else needs to fight it.
No, no, no. If it's
yours, then it's mine, too.
And it can't just be you
against an armed madman.
No, Riverdale needs the Red
Circle to expand, not contract.
- Yeah. But the guys...
- Are spineless cowards, clearly.
Lucky for you, I'm not.
Hi. I'm hoping to get a
few things. I have a list.
You got ID?
Yeah.
I'll be paying cash
for those items, too.
Just be a sec.
Ammo, holster, Kevlar vest.
You, uh... You going hunting?
Yeah, yes. That's
exactly what I'm doing.
[KNOCKING]
Betty? What time is it?
7:15. I wanted to
catch you before school.
I'm sorry. I have morning breath.
You want coffee or something?
No, I'm actually on
my way to the library.
I asked Ms. Paroo to set aside all the
books she has about
cryptograms and ciphers.
I thought it might help us
crack the Black Hood's code.
Which I'm hoping is something
we can do together, Chuck.
Um...
Actually, funny enough,
Toni of all people and I,
we started working on that
yesterday at the Red and Black.
I can show you what we've
got so far, if you want.
Toni, because let me guess...
She loves serial killers.
She does have an affinity for
the darker side of things, yeah.
In that case, why don't
we all work on it together?
You, me, Toni, Kevin.
- Kevin?
- Yeah, it'll be like a little
code-breaking party.
So fun! You can host.
[VERONICA] There you are.
I have a surprise for you.
It meant burning the midnight
oil and calling in a few favors,
- but... Ta-da.
- Ronnie, you can't wear that.
Are you saying I'm not
rocking this scoop-neck look?
No, I'm saying you can't walk around
with a friggi" target on your chest.
You'll stick out like a sore thumb.
Oh, Archie, it's adorable
when you underestimate me.
Come, come.
[ARCHIE] Oh, my God.
[VERONICA] Let Weatherbee do his worst.
The Red Circle is no longer
a fringe band of radicals,
it's a movement with style and panache.
These symbols look so familiar to me.
It's like I've seen them before
and it's driving me crazy
I can't figure out where.
Maybe if you loosened your ponytail.
What? That was a joke, guys.
Betty's ponytail is
iconic and beyond reproach.
Kev... It's fine.
And at this point, I'm
willing to try anything.
Per Mrs. Paroo's books,
I'm looking for common
letter associations like
T-H, A-N, I-N-G.
I'm looking for doubles. Double
L and four-letter words like kill.
- That's morbid.
- We don't know if this thing's even in English.
Guys, I mean, this could be an angram.
I'm literally on the top of my brain...
All right. Let's go back to the basics.
What do we know about
this guy? Who is he?
He's a white male, in his 40s.
Like almost every serial killer ever.
No, I mean like why...
Why is he killing people?
Or at least, why now?
We know the Hood's obsessed with cleansing
the town of sinners and
hypocrites, right?
And he seems to be attacking
anyone with ties to the Northside.
Here we go with the fake news again.
You Northsiders and your privilege.
All you do is demonize the Southside
so of course you think the
Black Hood's from there.
It's not demonizing,
Toni. It's stating facts.
There's way more drugs and gangs and...
The drugs you mean which were sold
primarily to Northside crackheads?
And what about the Northside Neo-Nazis?
The Red Circle? [SCOFFS]
The Red Psychos, you mean.
Hell, Betty, I'm surprised you
haven't just come out and said it yet.
Said what?
That you think the
Black Hood's a Serpent.
We all know how much you hate us.
- Okay, Toni...
- I don't hate the Serpents.
Oh, yeah? Then why is it
that your boyfriend here
lies about the fact that
he sits with us at lunch?
I'm gonna go.
Yeah, you know what? I'm
gonna get outta here, too.
Okay. I can walk you home.
Or you can walk me home.
Um, bye, guys.
Listen, Betty, I sit with the Serpents
purely for reasons of survival.
It's okay, Jug, let's just keep working
on the cipher, okay? The clock's ticking.
What clock? I mean, this
could be his laundry list.
Or his kill list.
[DOG BARKING]
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
- Back off. I'm not herefor you.
- Oh, yeah...
Then who's this message for, huh?
Aw, hell, don't tell me
it's for the Black Hood.
You believe this guy?
And people say we're the troublemakers.
Whoa.
Southside's Serpent country.
You can't come here and tag our turf.
So why don't you get your
ass back to the Northside
before someone gets hurt?
Get out of my way,
or someone will get hurt.
You just made a big mistake.
- Who made a mistake? Who made a mistake?
- What the hell?
Come on, let's go. Come on, man!
[CELL BUZZING]
- Ow, my neck.
- We fell asleep.
How did we fall asleep?
Exhaustion. It's not easy being us.
Oh, my God, she's gonna
kill me. I have to go.
What?
My mom, she's gonna kill
me. I have to go, okay.
I'll call you later.
[KNOCKING]
Sorry to interrupt, Dr. Phylum,
but Sheriff Keller and I need to
see Archie Andrews in the hallway.
I'm sorry Principal Weatherbee but the
T-shirts were my idea, not Archie's.
This is not about T-shirts,
Miss Lodge, please sit down.
It's okay, Ronnie. There's
nothing to worry about.
Got a tip from a bodega
owner on the Southside
who said that a Riverdale
High School student
was waving a gun around
in front of his shop.
Said it looked like he had red hair.
I was in my garage last
night, working on some songs.
Okay, well, nevertheless, given your
behavior over the last several days,
we think that it's
prudent to have a look
in your locker for any
weapons or contraband.
Weapons? Don't you need a
warrant for that or something?
- No, I do not.
- Maybe we should call my dad.
I did. He's informed.
Open the locker or I will.
[SIGHS]
I don't know what you think
you're gonna find, Sheriff.
This is interesting.
What? There's no gun.
Where did you get this hood?
[SIGHS] I can explain that.
The hood's not mine, it's Reggie's.
He came by as a joke, wearing
it, trying to scare me, Dad.
I don't know what to say.
I'm at a loss, Archie.
Keller and Weatherbee, they think you're a
threat, so they bar you
from school property,
and I can't tell them any different.
I was shot.
The man who shot me is still out there,
playing some kind of weird
cat-and-mouse game with this town.
And he scares me.
But not as much as you do right now.
Because I have no idea what
is going on in your mind.
I don't know what you're gonna do next.
Wait, Dad, come on.
Can we talk about this?
Yeah, when I get back from the
Town Hall we can talk about this.
If you're ready to be honest with me,
and let me back in.
Nice T-shirt.
Will you still be wearing
it when Archie's arrested
for reckless endangerment
or something worse?
Archie would never, Mom.
He's being railroaded.
And you can say that,
with absolute certainty,
after watching that video?
Maybe you can.
Or maybe you're just being loyal.
But let me tell you
something about loyalty.
There's nothing more honorable than it.
Noble, even.
But blind loyalty?
That's a stupid and dangerous thing.
I pray that's not the
case with you and Archie.
[JUGHEAD] When you left this morning,
you forgot some of your books.
Your notebooks.
Look, I wasn't snooping,
believe it or not, but...
It just fell out.
What did?
Your letter, from the Black Hood.
Jug.
I'm assuming that it
came with the cipher.
Betty, why haven't you told anybody?
I, I did, I told Kevin.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you've been
at Southside High, running
around with the Serpents.
Betty, I'd been gone for two days.
And yeah, it sucks that we don't
go to the same school anymore.
But that's not the reason you're sitting
on the fact that the Black
Hood has sent you a letter.
- So why is it...
- Because of what it says, Jughead!
Because of what he wrote.
That I...
Inspired him.
I inspired all of this... Madness.
You think people are
gonna blame you for this?
Not people, just one person.
Archie?
For what?
For writing a speech that this lunatic
has twisted around in
order to mess with you
and mess with the town?
Yeah, Archie's definitely shook,
but he knows who the bad guys are,
and you're not one of the bad guys.
You're Betty Cooper.
Like Nancy Drew meets
Girl with the Dragon Tattoo.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
In his letter, the Black Hood said that
I'm the only one who
could solve the cipher
like he created it specifically for me.
Maybe using one of my touchstones, Jug.
If I'm right, I think I
know how to decode this.
Let's go.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
Archie? What the hell is going on?
Are you okay?
[ARCHIE] I need you to get
something for me, Ronnie.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
At least you were smart enough
not to keep it in your locker,
but a gun, Archie?
Why? For what?
To protect myself.
Against the Black Hood?
Archie, that video,
the gun... If I'm following you,
I need to know where, I
need to know the truth.
I want him dead, Veronica.
I want the Black Hood dead,
and I want to be the one who does it.
I want to be the last
thing that he sees.
Spoken like a true vigilante.
No, you wanted the truth.
I made that video and showed
my face so the Black Hood
would make me his next target.
I went to the Southside
hoping he would come after me.
So you find the Black Hood and
you shoot him and then what?
You go to jail or you miss
him, and he kills you, Archie.
- It doesn't matter what happens to me.
- Yes, it does. It matters to me,
and your dad, Betty, Jughead.
Meanwhile, like an idiot,
I'm trying to support
you by designing T-shirts.
I didn't ask you to do that.
No, you just asked me
to fetch your loaded gun.
And by the way, in case
you're wondering where it is,
I threw it in Sweetwater River.
What?
And you can be mad at me now,
but you'll thank me for it later.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
Wait. Veronica, wait, what if it's...
Reggie?
Can we come in?
[MAYOR MCCOY] Parents of Riverdale,
I've heard your concerns.
I share them.
As your Mayor, my top priorities
are ensuring the safety of our town,
and our children.
The purpose of this Town Hall
is to answer your questions.
And, if I can, to ease your minds.
To what do we owe this unexpected honor?
Archie could have told
Weatherbee the hood was mine,
but he didn't.
In the Book of Reg, that makes
you a top-tier loyal badass.
And, uh. We were
talkin' today and decided
if you wanna keep the
Red Circle going...
We're here for you, dude.
And not a moment too
soon. Archie. Trouble.
How stupid are you Northsiders?
You really think you can come to
my house, stick a gun in my face
in front of my boys,
and there wouldn't be any payback?
You have crap timing, bro.
Bulldogs eat Serpents for lunch.
We'll see about that.
And the more, the merrier.
Hey, chill.
Veronica, stay here.
What? Archie, no...
Veronica, after my dad,
I made a promise to
protect him and this house.
You stay here.
If you wanna fight, we'll fight.
- What about your gun?
- What about your knife?
How about no weapons?
If you troglodytes insist on doing this,
there are gonna be rules.
Or should I call Sheriff
Keller to be referee?
When I was a kid, I used to
check out this book obsessively.
Betty...
The budget is tight, we're
uh... Putting together a helpline
that you can call to report
any suspicious activity.
Sounds an awful lot like the
Red Circle's hotline to me.
Did you have a question, Alice?
I'm wondering when you're gonna actually
address the real problem in Riverdale,
the Southside.
[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
All in due time, Alice.
But we're here to talk
about the Black Hood.
Now Sheriff Keller has a
plan he's putting in place,
beginning with a town-wide curfew...
Curfew?
We need to show strength, not cower.
Let's start by closing down
that drug-ridden Southside High,
and use that money to
bolster our police department.
Hire more deputies, who can
actually protect our children.
[APPLAUDING]
Just a sec.
Oh, my God.
"I will strike next where it all began."
Your speech... The Town Hall.
- My mom.
- Come on.
That neighborhood is a blight of
empty storefronts and vacant lots.
A pit of violence, waiting to erupt.
Just ask Fred Andrews, himself a victim
of a vicious, insane
Southsider's bloodlust.
You talk about this town being divided.
Alice, you're the one
holding the cleaver.
The Southside is not the issue.
The issue is there is a guy out
there with a gun and a hood.
And he's bringing out
the worst in this town.
Pitting it against itself.
[ALL GRUNTING]
Of course, Fred Andrews turns
the other cheek, as usual.
I can't say much about your son Archie,
but at least he's out
there, throwing elbows.
[GRUNTING]
We have to be united
in this fight, okay?
If we let the fear take over,
start demonizing each other,
that's when we're dead.
[APPLAUDING]
I told you Fred was gonna be a problem.
Oh, no...
The town loves and trusts him.
That could work in our favor.
Everyone needs to leave, right now.
The Black Hood is coming here.
He said this is his next target.
What are you talking about? What do
you mean the Black Hood's coming here?
The cipher says he's
coming to the Town Hall.
What?
Everyone, stay calm and in
your seats. We'll sort this out.
[ALARM BELL RINGING]
Dilton!
[GROANS]
Okay, you guys, let's
go! Let's get out of here.
Help me!
When they ask you at the hospital...
Say I was minding my own business
when a bunch of Southside Serpents
jumped me for no reason.
Well, Elizabeth, we're waiting.
This is from the Black Hood.
It came with the cipher.
And you've been keeping this from us?
Ah!
Sorry.
No. I deserve it.
Tonight was really messed up, Ronnie.
Things got so out of control.
At least Dilton's going to be okay.
Yeah, but only because of you.
You saved him, Ronnie.
And me.
[VERONICA] These are
fraught times, Archie.
No one's thinking straight.
We have to... Hold on to each other.
Right?
I'm sorry I lied about
getting rid of the gun.
I was freaking out.
God, Ronnie, if I'd had it tonight...
I don't wanna think about
it, honestly, I might've...
But you didn't.
And...
I don't believe you would've.
Even if you'd had it.
You're not a killer.
Mmm.
- Wait?
- What?
We have one more thing
we need to do tonight.
[JUGHEAD] And so the young lovers
went back to where it all began,
Sweetwater River,
to try and end the cycle of violence.
We'd come to think of that night,
the night of the rumble,
the night of the Town Hall,
as a turning point.
Riverdale would no longer
be the town with pep.
From now on, it would be known
as the town that dreaded sundown.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- [MAN] Hello, Betty.
This is the Black Hood speaking.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com -