[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
[gunshot]
[Pop] This man,
his goal was something else.
It was like the angel of death
had come to Riverdale.
[gasping]
- Hello, Dilton.
- Somebody has to teach them
to stand their ground.
[woman]
Your father's facing serious jail time.
[man] Serpents take care of their own.
We got your back.
Smithers, would you describe my father
as a good man?
- I'd rather not say, miss.
- I told your father
you were conflicted about helping him.
"If you do not testify, your mother
might be drawn into this mess."
Whether Sheriff Keller
finds the person who did this or not,
you don't have to worry.
I'm gonna protect you, I swear it.
[Jughead] Behold, Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe.
For decades, the heart of Riverdale.
What the hell?
[Jughead] Now the latest casualty in the
town's ongoing battle against darkness.
- Pop?
- [Pop] Did you see?
Did you see what they wrote
on my Chock'lit Shoppe?
[Archie] No, no, no.
- [Fred] Ahem. We need a fire extinguisher?
- What are you doing up?
- I was gonna bring you breakfast.
- I appreciate it,
but I gotta get to moving around sometime.
- Little early for that, isn't it?
- No, I'm good.
The only thing you need
to worry about is getting better.
[phone ringing]
Crap. I gotta take this. I gotta go. Bye.
Hi, Sheriff Keller?
No. No, deputy, I've been leaving messages
for the sheriff.
I need him to call me back
about my dad's case.
[sighs]
- TTFN, Smithers.
- [Smithers] Wait, Miss Veronica.
You might wanna take the side exit.
Why?
[door opens]
Yeah, why, Smithers?
Because she might bump into me
- coming in from an early run?
- [Veronica] Good morning, Father.
Mija, you leave before breakfast,
you come home after your mother and I
have had dinner.
I can't remember the last time
we had a meal together.
I can. It was at the Dakota.
The day you got arrested.
Well, perhaps we should talk
about that tonight, at dinner.
- The three of us.
- Unfortunately, I have plans.
To quote that New Yorker cartoon:
"How about never, Dad?
Is never good for you?"
[Jughead]
It's another win for the bad guys.
No one was there. His entire staff quit.
He's not sure how long
he'll be able to keep the doors open.
Maybe not even a week.
It's because of what happened to my dad.
People are freaking out.
I gotta be honest.
I don't see myself going back soon.
Wait, I'm sorry.
Am I hearing acceptance?
I'm not letting one psychopath with a gun
dictate what happens to our place.
Jug, you went crazy
trying to save the drive-in.
I can't take on any more social issues
right now.
My hands are full.
With your dad, of course.
And he should be your priority.
- I'll take point on helping Pop Tate.
- [Veronica] I'll help.
Anything to get me away
from my parents, I'm in.
Another B and V team-up?
They should make a video game
about you guys. I gotta jet.
I'm off to meet my dad's court-appointed
joke of a lawyer at the sheriff's station.
Let me come. I gotta drop some flyers off
for Sheriff Keller.
[Betty] Bye.
[door opens]
[Keller] Thanks.
[Archie] Sheriff Keller.
Archie, how's your dad holding up?
He'd be better
if you caught the guy who shot him.
- We're doing everything we can.
- Me, too.
I'm out here handing out flyers,
talking to neighbors,
tracking my dad's credit cards.
His wallet is still missing.
Which means this guy
has all of our information,
including where we live.
And we were witnesses.
If your guys are out patrolling,
let me go with them.
- I can help.
- Well...
[woman over radio]
Code 2, incident 5106. RD-6 took it.
In Greendale? All right, copy that.
Give me a sec.
Let us do our job.
You take care.
Let's talk about the damn deal.
[man] First, to review the charges
you're facing,
arson, destruction of evidence,
making a false confession,
obstructing justice,
not to mention this whole nasty mess
of dumping a dead kid in the river.
I know what I did.
What's the deal?
- What are they offering?
- You're gonna wanna take it.
I've been doing this a long time.
It's a strong deal.
How many... damn... years?
[boards rattling]
Whoa, whoa. Whoa.
[Archie] Jughead.
- Are you insane?
- You're the one that looks
like a Dream Warrior
from Nightmare on Elm Street 3.
What did the lawyer say?
I've been walking around trying
to wrap my head around how bad it is.
It's bad.
My dad is facing 20 years, Archie.
Crap, Jughead. I'm sorry. That sucks.
The lawyer thinks he should take the deal.
If he doesn't and the case goes to trial,
he could be facing 40 years.
I'm just really, really scared.
Yeah, me, too.
About what?
[gunshot]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
I couldn't sleep last night, Jug.
I kept thinking about your dad and Pop's
and how maybe we can kill two birds
with one stone.
We can...
Can you meet me at the mayor's office?
Okay, great. I'll get it set. Um...
- Right now I need to call...
- Hey, B, what's up?
[knock on door]
I know you haven't been sleeping
in your room,
so, where exactly
have you been spending your nights?
- [Archie] So, Betty.
- [Veronica] Yes, Betty.
Since you and your dad got home
from the hospital,
she's noticed your room has been
unusually empty and quiet. Why?
So I can... watch the doors.
So I can make sure no one comes in.
I know it sounds crazy,
but the guy who shot my dad
is still out there, Ronnie.
And I'm scared he's gonna... come back
and finish the job.
Archie, you went through something
deeply traumatic.
- Can I make a suggestion?
- Please. Anything.
When I lived in New York,
I saw a therapist once a week
to help me get through all sorts
of Park Avenue drama.
Now, I'm not saying
to go see a therapist, Archie,
but maybe the school counselor could help?
- Mayor McCoy.
- Betty, Jughead, what can I help you with?
So, the Chock'lit Shoppe
is on the verge of closing,
and we want Pop Tate to know
that the town is rallying behind him.
We were thinking that you could make
the building a landmark
or declare a Pop's Day in support.
What if I endorse Pop's
and someone else is shot there?
My priority, as a mayor and as a mother,
is keeping this town safe.
If we have to close Pop's, I'm all for it.
Are you also all for shipping my dad off
to prison for a murder he didn't commit?
What is this, an ambush?
I know you have an in
with the state attorney.
If you could call him
and get my dad a better lawyer?
Your father made some mistakes.
- I'm sure he'll get a fair hearing.
- [Jughead] Mayor McCoy?
Remember this moment.
This is the moment you turned your back
on both Pop Tate and my father.
Midge Klump.
- The Klumpster.
- Reggie.
What do you know about jingle-jangle?
I know you shouldn't say it so loud
on school property.
And that I can score you some.
Who's it for?
- Me and Moose.
- Let me see what I can do.
What's on your mind, Andrews?
Girl troubles? Scabies?
Why are you seeking guidance
from Ms. Burble?
- I'm not.
- Maybe you should.
You look like my nuts
after football practice.
Hey. Do you have anything
that can help keep me awake?
Many things.
Amphetamines, baclofen,
modafinil, jingle-jangle.
Jingle-jangle?
That'll keep you up for days,
in more ways than one.
Why do you need uppers, Wonder Bread?
Until the guy who shot my dad is caught,
I wanna be on high alert.
- Can you help me or not, Reggie?
- I got you, Andrews.
[Betty] We can't let the terrorists win.
We need to host an event at Pop's
that reminds the town of simpler times.
A throwback to when the Shoppe
first opened its doors.
Betty... I like a good milkshake
as much as any girl,
and Pop's puts Serendipity 3's to shame,
but why this hill to die on?
Orange freezes with my mom
and Polly after ballet.
Chicken noodle soup with my dad
after ice-skating.
Grilled cheeses with Archie
on the last day of summer vacation.
[Betty] It's where I met you
for the first time, V.
It's where I met you for the first time.
Also...
Jug.
He may lose his dad...
but maybe I can save this one place
for him, for all of us.
[knocking on door]
Hey, Veronica.
May I speak to you?
Daddy?
- Daddy?
Every day I was in prison, I thought
about getting back to you and your mother.
I knew it wouldn't be easy.
I knew it would take time.
Meet me halfway.
Don't you think I want to, Daddy?
Don't you think I want everything
to go back to the way it was?
The three of us
walking into some fabulous gala or ball,
you with your two favorite girls.
But... I can't.
The blindfold's off.
I can't put it back on.
I'm sorry.
- I should get back to my friends.
- Yeah. Hey, so...
- are you, uh, planning a dance in there?
- An event to keep Pop's from closing.
- If I can help...
- I'll let you know.
I tried going the legit route.
I talked to the mayor.
It feels like the system is rigged
against us.
What's FP saying? Is he taking this deal?
Not if I can help it.
Tall Boy...
what if we bust him out of jail
before he gets transferred to state?
It's doable. The sheriff's station has
worse security than Riverdale High.
Once he's out,
it's a straight shot up Sweetwater River
until the Canadian border.
You've seen Escape From Alcatraz
a few too many times, kid.
Your dad needs a snake handler.
Someone whose livelihood
depends on snakes,
who's used to dealing with them.
I got someone you should meet.
Humpty and Dumpty.
Just in time to meet our newest recruit.
In addition to my duties as a Pussycat.
And I just wanna say, girls,
I'm so excited to work on my moves
and to be a team player,
as long as I'm in the front.
Wait, Cheryl, does that mean
you're taking the Vixens back from me?
But really, Veronica,
were they ever yours?
Cheryl, we were wondering
if maybe the Vixens would help
at an event to save Pop's.
Oh, Betty, I did not emerge
from the frozen depths of Sweetwater River
nor the flames of Thornhill
to allow my Vixens to sling milkshakes
at some death-cursed diner.
The answer is a double-cherry-on-top no.
[bell rings]
Okay.
Good talk.
[Weatherbee]
May I have everyone's attention?
I have some...
tragic news to share.
Ms. Grundy...
who was a teacher here last semester,
was found...
- murdered in her Greendale home.
- Oh, my God.
[Weatherbee] I know some of you
were students of hers...
and that this news
will be difficult to process.
[inaudible]
[gunshot]
Mr. Andrews?
[Archie] First you get shot.
Then Ms. Grundy is murdered.
All within a matter of days.
What if some crazy person
is going after people I care about?
[sighs]
- What? You think I'm nuts.
- No, son, I think you're scared.
Understandably so.
Truth is, we don't know anything
about what happened to Ms. Grundy.
She's dead. She was killed...
right across Sweetwater River.
I know.
It was a horrible thing.
Don't you wanna find out who did this?
Who's doing this?
I'm, uh...
here for Penny Peabody?
Forgive the office space,
but I'm a firm believer in low overhead.
- Plus, I like being close to my clients.
- Your clients being the Serpents?
Well, I was and still am a Serpent.
They put me through college.
Law school.
Right. Serpents are often
on the other side of the law,
so, having one of their own
on retainer helping out, it's clever.
FP always bragged that you were smart.
Oh, yeah, I know your dad.
And I also know,
from our, um... mutual friends,
the deal he's been offered.
It's garbage.
- Can you help?
- I know the loopholes.
In this case, there are none.
But if you get the victim's family
to forgive him
in front of a judge,
that might shift things in FP's favor.
Instead of 20 years,
he can get time served with parole.
- Oh, that's great.
- Yeah.
Thank... Uh...
Am I... supposed to pay you, or...?
We're friends.
I do you a favor,
one day, maybe you do me a favor.
Let me know how it goes, will you?
Tell your dad to wear a tie.
You're twitching, Archie,
which means this must be serious.
I think the person who shot my dad
may have murdered Ms. Grundy.
My, my. We've come a long way
since dances at the gym
and varsity football tryouts, haven't we?
You were the first to know anything
about Jason's autopsy.
- Archie's wondering if...
- I can get details on Ms. Grundy's death
and see if they line up
with the attack on Fred.
It would be really helpful
to put Archie's mind at ease.
Fine. I'll reach out
to my ghoulish friend.
Thank you, Mrs. Cooper. Thanks, Betty.
I should go.
I'll call you, Arch.
Spreading ourself thin
as the patron saint of lost causes,
aren't we?
You can cross saving Pop's off your list.
Haven't you heard?
Pop Tate is selling the Shoppe.
What? To who?
To, and you'll love this,
an anonymous buyer.
Ring any bells?
[phone ringing]
- Miss Veronica, I'll take those.
- Oh, thank you, Smithers.
Hey, girl.
What?
Are you buying Pop's
the way you bought the drive-in?
Anonymously?
And are you doing this just to buy me?
Yesterday did you think,
"Veronica's working so hard
to save the Chock'lit Shoppe,
I'll save it for her."
Veronica, I'm not buying Pop's.
Now, please, lower your voice and sit...
so we can speak civilly.
- You wanna talk, Dad?
- That's all I've wanted. A fair hearing.
To explain myself.
Okay.
Let's talk about Mr. Andrews.
Mom asked him to sell his portion
of the SoDale project.
And the day after he rejected the offer...
he was shot in Pop's.
- Was it your doing?
- [Hermione] Veronica.
- First you accuse me, then your father?
- No.
No.
I didn't shoot Fred.
Nor did I hire someone to do it.
I was your fiercest protector, Dad.
Ask Mom. Whenever somebody called you
the devil incarnate, I defended you.
I kept telling myself, "He's not that bad.
You can forgive him."
And then you sent me this.
A letter threatening you, Mom.
That's the kind of man
you're letting back into our lives.
[Hermione] Veronica...
your father didn't write this.
I did.
I don't understand.
I needed you to testify
on your father's behalf.
So, I wrote this letter
threatening myself, not your father.
[Hiram] Yeah.
She did it for us...
to survive.
So we can be a family again.
You two deserve each other.
[Jughead]
It's not exactly downsizing, is it?
[knocking on door]
Hobo.
Bride of hobo.
Welcome to Thistlehouse.
Mother's in the conservatory. Follow me.
Thank you for sitting down with us.
Of course, Betty. You're family.
[Jughead] Okay.
The reason we're here...
FP's lawyer thinks that if the family
of the victim shows mercy...
Mercy.
That's why you're here?
Well, it's an appeal for leniency
from you...
to reduce my dad's sentence.
Where was your father's mercy
when I spent those nights
walking Thornhill in agony,
obsessing over what was happening
to J.J., imagining the worst?
Where was it
when I slept under the same roof
- as a killer night after night?
- Cheryl.
FP didn't kill Jason.
Okay? That was your dad.
You saw the video.
If it were up to me,
I'd watch FP fry in the electric chair.
We need this sordid chapter
closed forever,
and FP is the last loose end to tie up.
I will not have a living,
breathing reminder
of the darkest chapter of my life
walking the streets of Riverdale.
What do we do now
that Cheryl's gone full Poison Ivy?
Blackmail, extortion.
If they weren't literally an orphan
and a widow, I would do it.
[man] Lacerations on the neck.
Her trachea's crushed.
Broken veins in her eyes,
and the skin tears suggest brutality.
This is a crime of passion.
Hatred. He wanted to feel her struggle
as she died.
Tell me, Mrs. Cooper,
did you know the victim?
No.
[man] Give me your wallet!
[grunting]
[Reggie] Stop it.
Stop!
It's me.
- Are you insane?
- What are you doing here?
Delivering your uppers.
Clearly the last thing you need.
- You've lost it, Andrews.
- You're the one here wearing this hood.
It's called a prank.
I didn't expect you to attack me.
What if I had been the guy, huh?
- You would have just tackled him?
- Yeah. Damn right.
He has a gun, Andrews.
He's shot people.
Only a dumb-ass lunatic
brings a bat to a gunfight.
There was no sign of forced entry,
which probably means she knew her killer.
The police don't know
if any of her belongings were taken.
How, uh...?
How did Ms. Grundy die?
The autopsy showed
that she was strangled...
with something the killer grabbed on hand.
A cello bow, of all things.
There was a struggle. She fought back.
But, Archie, this was a crime of passion,
in another town,
with a completely different murder weapon.
The likelihood of these two crimes
being connected seems slim.
Son?
If I say what I'm thinking,
you'll think I'm crazy.
Probably Mrs. Cooper is right.
Probably they're not connected.
So, why'd you do it? Did they make you
an offer you couldn't refuse?
- Who's buying it? Do you know?
- [Pop] It shames me to say...
- ChugMo.
- The liquor-store chain?
- Could I make a request for a last supper?
- Anything you want.
It's not for me. It's for my dad.
He's facing 20 years
of that weird meat loaf
that they serve prisoners.
So, barring an 11th-hour miracle, I was...
hoping, for his last meal in Riverdale,
that you could make his favorite.
Fried chicken, corn bread, onion rings
and orange freeze, if memory serves.
That's very Rain Man of you, Pop.
Been doing this a long time.
Thought I'd be doing it
until the day I die.
[Betty] This is...
unacceptable.
- What?
- Just everything.
- Have you officially sold the diner?
- The contract's being drawn up.
Do not sign it.
Okay? Do not give up. Either of you.
I can fix this, all right?
I will fix this, okay?
Bye.
[door closes, then Cheryl gasps]
- Give a girl a warning, will you?
- You want closure.
- I wanna help my boyfriend's dad.
- I told you...
And I'm telling you...
to help FP or...
Or what?
Or I wide-release the video
of your father shooting Jason.
Try having closure
with that out in the world.
I thought you, uh, gave that
damn thumb drive to Sheriff Keller.
No, not before I saved a copy
onto Jughead's laptop.
One click and the darkest chapter
of your family's twisted psychodrama
becomes a viral sensation.
Are you threatening me?
This?
No.
No, this is... fun girl talk.
You could save a man's life.
Think about that.
A nice ending to a sad story.
If I testify, you're giving me that video
and a guarantee that all copies
in your possession will be erased.
You have my word.
Also...
I need the Vixens for Retro Night.
You're a stone-cold bitch, Betty Cooper.
I don't have red hair and broad shoulders.
Or a blond ponytail, for that matter.
Do you wanna talk?
You were ready to walk away from your dad.
And now you're crusading for his freedom.
What changed?
He did.
He made an effort.
Took another swing at being a good dad.
But don't you think...
some people can't change?
Like it's just in their DNA to be bad?
I'm not gonna presume to know
what lies in your father's heart.
But Archie's dad almost died.
And my dad is going away for 20 years.
If there's even a 0.0001 percent chance
that your dad is trying...
I get it.
Thank you, Jughead.
Sheriff, I believe the man who shot my dad
is the person
that killed Ms. Grundy,
and I think I know who it is.
Well, that's quite a statement, Archie.
Ms. Grundy had an abusive ex-husband.
She moved to Riverdale to get away.
She kept a gun in her car
in case he'd come back.
And how do you know all this?
Because she and I were...
We were close.
And I'm thinking he found out about me.
Ms. Grundy was killed with a cello bow.
I gave her one before she left Riverdale.
I'm betting it's the murder weapon.
Can't you see? He's sending me a message.
Your theory's wrong, Archie.
My counterparts at Greendale
already brought in her ex.
And he has an airtight alibi.
Maybe everyone's right.
Maybe I am going crazy.
[Kevin] Hey, has Betty called?
Not yet.
Let's pray Cheryl comes through for them.
[man] Ms. Blossom,
you may proceed with your statement.
Your Honor, I speak for myself
and my mother when I say...
we forgive FP Jones for the part he played
in covering up my brother's murder.
And we humbly ask the court for leniency.
FP's guilt has been blown
out of proportion
to satiate what my father's suicide
denied us.
Closure.
As much as I sympathize, I can't ignore
the quality of Mr. Jones' crimes.
There were no extenuating circumstances.
My father threatened him.
I overheard them talking in Daddy's study.
Daddy said he'd hurt Jughead
if FP didn't comply.
Is that extenuating enough?
[judge] In light of these revelations,
I suggest that we take a step back
and reevaluate certain aspects
of the case.
At which time, we will revisit sentencing.
Adjourned.
Is that a win?
It's a delay, so, yeah.
No one's here.
No one's coming.
It's still early, okay?
Mom.
- Did you come to gloat?
- Don't be so cynical, Elizabeth.
I came to write my next story
over one last root-beer float.
I'm calling it "Requiem for Pop's."
Can I get a quote, dear?
You're a fiend, mother.
But this is one obituary
you're not gonna write.
All right.
Two strawberries, one vanilla,
and one chocolate with extra malt.
[clears throat]
Why did you broadcast
all over social media
that the Pussycats would be doing
a free concert here?
I knew if I asked, you would have said...
No. If my mom even hears
that I set foot in this place...
Josie, you care about this place.
I know you do.
I see you here all the time.
Betty, even if I wanted to help,
I'm down a Cat.
- Valerie has norovirus.
- I don't mind stepping in.
If you can be a River Vixen,
Josie, I can be a Pussycat.
As long as it's a cover,
I'll know the lyrics.
You do love your cheese fries.
Fine. Fine.
[Pussycats] ♪ My milkshake
Brings all the boys to the yard ♪
♪ And they're like
It's better than yours ♪
♪ Damn right, it's better than yours
I can teach you, but I have to charge ♪
♪ My milkshake
Brings all the boys to the yard ♪
♪ And they're like
It's better than yours ♪
♪ Damn right it's better than yours
I can teach you, but I have to charge ♪
♪ I know you want it ♪
♪ The thing that makes me
Oh ♪
♪ What the guys go crazy for ♪
♪ They lose their minds ♪
♪ The way I wind ♪
[Veronica] Hey there, Daddy-o.
You made it.
- You feeling okay?
- Yeah.
Just taking deep breaths.
I'm proud of you.
Come on.
You take a booth,
and I'll get you a shake.
I'm not here to fight.
I'm here to be supportive.
Dad, Mom.
I've been thinking.
Tonight is a new beginning for Pop's,
and maybe it can be for us, too.
That's up to you.
If that's what you want.
Let's try.
- But, you guys, total transparency, okay?
- Yes. Of course.
From now on. In the spirit of that,
I propose that Lodge Industries
make a charitable contribution.
Relax, Betty.
I'm sure they're just here to enjoy
Pop's world-class burgers and service.
Just like me.
Ugh, you two are like chimps in captivity,
grooming and picking lice off each other.
Mark this day in your diary.
I lied under oath for you.
- Thank God I'm quick on my feet.
- Cheryl...
thank you.
Honor your promise to me.
Hi, Midge, Moose.
I've got your jingle-jangle.
[camera clicks]
[Pop] I gotta put her on the spot.
It's thanks to this young lady here
that Pop's gets to stay open tonight,
tomorrow, as long as you folks
keep coming.
[cheering]
Thanks also to the Lodge family
for a donation they just made
that gives us a little cushion
to weather any storm that might come up.
[cheering]
I didn't know
we were in the charity business.
Oh, we're not.
As of five minutes ago,
we, uh, own this diner.
In exchange for his silence,
I told Tate he could stay on as manager.
Nice to have you back, Hiram.
Thank you for saying
you wrote that letter.
Veronica never would've forgiven me
for that.
Once again, your loyalty knows no bounds.
Ronnie, should I introduce myself
to your dad?
You've faced enough dragons for one night.
Next time, Archiekins.
[Betty] So, I guess tonight is a win
for the good guys.
A rare win, but yes.
Thanks to you, Betty.
You okay?
I'm here with you guys.
So, yeah, I think so.
[Cheryl] I have a present for you.
The video of Daddy and Jason.
All cued up.
It might bring you peace.
[man] Evening, Mr. and Mrs. Lodge.
- You must be Veronica.
- I am. Where's Smithers?
He didn't he tell you?
His mother fell ill.
He went overseas to care for her.
Did he leave a forwarding address?
- I'll try to track one down, sir.
- Thank you, Andre.
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- You went to see Penny Peabody?
- [FP] You asked her for help?
- Dad. Hey.
Uh, yeah. We didn't have a choice.
Is something wrong?
Did you...? Did you pay her?
- No, she said it was a favor.
- [FP] Jughead, listen to me.
Do not contact her again.
If she reaches out, don't respond.
You do not wanna be in bed
- with the Snake Charmer.
- [Jughead] Why...?
Dad?
You do know that several drug deals
went down here tonight?
- What?
- And if you think Hiram Lodge,
Riverdale's answer to Scarface,
helped Pop Tate for altruistic reasons,
- I have a bridge to sell you.
- Mom...
The Serpents have now officially
crossed the tracks
and have a toehold on the Northside,
so, congratulations.
You're almost single-handedly responsible
for giving crime a haven in Riverdale.
[Jughead] And far from the glow of Pop's
neon sign, on Sweetwater Bridge,
Archie Andrews had arranged
a secret rendezvous with Dilton Doiley.
Hey, Dilton.
Hey, Archie. I got what you asked for.
I'm not crazy.
The guy's still out there.
It's for protection.
Sure, Archie.
Whatever you say.
[Jughead] That night, for the first time
in weeks, Archie would sleep...
before waking up the next morning
to a living nightmare.
[Midge] Bottoms up.
♪ And when I look in my window ♪
♪ So many different people to be ♪
♪ That it's strange ♪
♪ So strange ♪
Wait, wait.
I think there's something out there.
No, Midge.
♪ You've got to pick up every stitch ♪
[gunfire, then Midge screams]
♪ Must be the season of the witch ♪
♪ Must be the season of the witch, yeah ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull