FATHER: We never pass by
a lemonade stand
without stopping first.
Isn't that right, Christian?
CHRISTIAN: Never.
Thank you.
- Would you like a straw?
- Uh, yes, please.
KIM: [LAUGHING]
Yes, two pitchers already.
It's the cutest thing.
Oh, but a terrible business model.
I must have spent £30
on lemons and cups.
[CHUCKLES]
♪♪
KIM: Yeah, honey, hold on a sec.
Ethan? What are you doing?
It's snowing
What? Honey, it's...
ETHAN: Mummy, it's snowing!
♪♪
[CHILDREN YELLING AND PLAYING]
- [LAUGHS]
- Yay! [LAUGHS]
♪♪
Ow, my eye!
Mum, my eye. It burns.
♪♪
FATHER: Ash.
This is ash.
[RUMBLING IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
Everyone, inside right now!
Get inside now!
Get inside the house!
Go, go!
[ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER,
INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪♪
MAN: [OVER RADIO] Baker 24.
We're moving to that location.
ETA 15.
Can we get another, uh...
♪♪
Tell me everything.
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
TOM: Liz, what happened?
Nik's d-dead.
What?
[VOICE BREAKING] He was strangled.
They found his body in an empty lot...
...miles away from home or any hospital.
What? How? Do they know?
The last thing he said to me was
he never wanted to see me again.
♪♪
Liz, what...
Do they know what happened?
No, but we do.
- Reddington.
- He had him perform a surgery,
and then Nik said he was out.
Reddington probably thought
he was a liability,
- that he knew too much.
- You don't know that.
Nik was good. He was decent.
The only indecent thing in his life
was Reddington and me.
You didn't... You didn't do this.
Would Nik be alive
if I weren't in his life?
♪♪
[CRYING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
You're not my type, okay?
But if you were even
remotely in the ballpark,
I would have your child.
RED: Do you have a count?
The mailman gave us two lists.
Each list had 22 people
who wanted their mail held
while on vacation.
That's 44 empty apartments.
We rented 18 for 5 nights each
at $500 a night.
That's $45,000 for the week
off two lists.
By next week, we should have eight.
Did you hear that?
I just dropped an egg.
While I appreciate your enthusiasm,
we have cash but no business
to run it through.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
- Elizabeth.
- Could you excuse us, please?
Oh, I'm way ahead of you, sister.
No offense, but when I get
too close to a Fed,
I tend to chafe.
[WHISPERS] Nik Korpal was murdered.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I want to believe you.
♪♪
I suppose it's possible Nik was killed
by someone with a connection to me,
but I have no idea who
or what that connection might be.
I want a name.
I'll do what I can to find you one.
In the meantime,
a riddle to keep you occupied.
♪♪
The chemical-plant explosion in Leeds?
Ilyas Surkov claimed credit for that.
What's the riddle?
Why did that terrorist
take credit for a crime
he didn't commit?
And how do you know he didn't commit it?
Because Ilyas Surkov is dead.
Dead? How long?
According to Reddington, 15 months.
RESSLER: And no one knows this?
Was there any HUMINT on Surkov?
No, he was like a ghost.
One month, he claimed credit
for a subway bombing in Lisbon,
and the next,
the kidnapping of
three journalists in Crimea.
If he did die, no one would know.
But Reddington would?
He knows the best off-market
doctors on every continent.
One of them treated Surkov
for end-stage pancreatic cancer.
ARAM: Okay, hang on.
Okay, Mr. Reddington says
it's been 15 months.
Well, in that time,
Surkov has taken credit
for three attacks...
a downed plane on a humanitarian mission
to Boko Haram victims,
a Paris café demolished
by a C-4 suitcase bomb,
and yesterday's chemical-plant attack.
He's pretty busy for a dead guy.
Or people acting in his name.
COOPER: We won't know which
until we find the bomber.
I'll reach out to MI6.
Ressler, Keen, get to the bomb site.
Talk to local authorities,
see what they know.
[SIREN WAILING]
GLADSTONE: Liam Gladstone, MI6.
We spoke on the phone.
RESSLER: Agent Ressler, Keen.
May not look like it,
but we were incredibly lucky here.
Had a few minor leaks,
but none of the tanks
with the really nasty stuff went up.
EA just cleared us.
Did you ask your task force
about our copycat theory?
Doesn't hold water.
This is the work of Ilyas Surkov.
What makes you so confident?
You know what taggants are?
Chemical markers that are
imbedded into explosives
- to trace their origin.
- MI6 has been working closely
with the CIA's Surkov Task Force,
and we identified
a construction and demolition
company in Belgrade
we believe is diverting
legitimately purchased C-4
to Surkov for his bombs.
To test our theory, we planted a taggant
in C-4 we sold to the company.
You found traces of that taggant.
So, who's your suspect?
Raqaan Ghaffari,
a foreman at Lignes D'Avenir
Construction.
If you have any doubts,
they'll be put to rest
when Surkov hits again,
which he will.
I can assure you, the man
is very much alive.
[SPEAKING ARABIC] _
_
♪♪
[DEVICE BEEPING]
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN] _
_
[SPEAKING ARABIC] _
♪♪
ARAM: Raqaan Ghaffari.
He's in charge of demolition
for Lignes D'Avenir,
a mid-sized contractor in Belgrade.
LIZ: We know the explosives
used by Surkov in his last three attacks
came from Lignes D'Avenir.
So, what's the plan? We have
no authority in Belgrade.
I'll reach out to Serbian
officials, get clearance.
But if we want this guy to lead us
to whoever is acting in Surkov's name,
we're gonna need to get creative.
MI6 had Ghaffari under surveillance.
It didn't yield any actionable intel,
but Ghaffari proves to be quite
the creative of habit.
Yeah, Ghaffari eats lunch
every Friday at the Brutka Club.
So that's where we make contact.
Ghaffari is a Moroccan immigrant.
He speaks French and Arabic.
Surveillance logs gave us
what we believe
is Ghaffari's code name for Surkov.
Samar can use that
to establish her credibility.
♪♪
ARAM: All right,
you'll have us on comms,
but to pick up Ghaffari, this mic...
well, it's gonna need to be close.
All right? So...
There.
I'll let you, you know...
It's going to be fine.
I know.
If you did, you wouldn't
have come all this way.
♪♪
Please, just, uh...
...be careful.
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Heads up.
She's about to make contact.
♪♪
[CONVERSING IN ARABIC] _
_
- Aram, are you getting this?
- ARAM: Loud and clear.
This is definitely our guy.
_
♪♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
_
♪♪
[DOOR CREAKS]
TOM: I think Nik was killed
by a guy named Pete McGee.
Nik asked him to I.D.
a skeleton I'd given him.
He got a DNA sample
and ran it against the federal database.
Now, I know the I.D.
is extremely valuable,
because Reddington wants
to keep it secret.
[CHOKING]
But I didn't know
that people would kill for it.
Now Nik's dead, McGee is gone.
And the only lead
I have on him and that I.D.
is the clinic he worked at...
a place where experimental drugs
are tested on human guinea pigs.
Yeah, I know. Not much of a plan.
- If you got a better one, I'm all ears.
- [BABBLES]
Don't look at me like that all right?
Rose is gonna be here
to take care of you,
and we both know she's your favorite.
And no, I am not lying to Mommy,
all right?
- [WHIMPERS]
- I want her to know the truth.
That's why I need to I.D. these bones
without anybody knowing.
[SIGHS]
[CELLPHONE DIALING]
It's not a lie.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- It's just... delayed honesty.
Hi, I'm calling about
the clinical trials.
Yeah. I want to sign up.
Have you ever done
an in-patient clinical trial before,
Mr... Lembeck?
First time. Be gentle.
I'll need a copy of your I.D.
Sure.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Uh, how much am I getting, by the way,
to rent my body to science?
- $200 a day.
- Lucky me.
We'll need a full medical history
and an emergency contact
for when you have an adverse reaction.
When? Not if?
[DOG PANTING]
Get in the car.
Whoa, buddy, what... whatever it is...
Mr. Reddington wants to talk.
Reddington Reddington?
Bring the dog, leave the poop.
Rosie Cavendish had a bulldog.
Franklin, named after her great-uncle.
Poor guy had eczema,
dermatitis, seborrhea...
one skin condition after the next.
The dog, not the uncle.
Please, sir, I-if I did something...
Given the lesions on her inner folds,
I'd say she has pyoderma.
What are you doing to treat it?
Topical ointments or pills?
I need to be better with her check-ups?
I need to borrow some evidence, Lou.
You know my name?
The personal effects
of a homicide victim
that are currently in evidence control.
- I don't know if I could do that...
- You are the clerk
- in evidence control...
- Yes.
...the man responsible for
checking in and out evidence?
Well, that's true, but...
The deceased's name is Nik Korpal.
You have 24 hours.
That should give us
enough time to get...
Coco.
...to get Coco the spa day
she so desperately deserves.
Yeah, you're gonna have fun!
[LAUGHS]
[DOG MURMURS]
♪♪
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
[SPEAKING ARABIC] _
_
♪♪
[CROWD MURMURS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
♪♪
Oh, my gosh. No.
Who are these guys?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Crap, crap. No!
Stop. Wait!
- [TIRES SQUEAL, ENGINE REVS]
- FBI!
LIZ: Who the hell is that?
She had him!
♪♪
Aram, what are you doing?
I don't know how to drive.
Get out! Move!
[TIRES SQUEAL, ENGINE REVS]
♪♪
Agent Ressler, m-maybe you could
slow down a little bit?
♪♪
Uh. there's an alley.
Alley! Alley ahead!
Alley ahead!
[TIRES SQUEAL]
- [GUNSHOT]
- Gun!
Oh. Oh, God.
- [GUNSHOTS]
- Watch out.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[GUNSHOTS]
Hold on.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Watch out. Watch out.
♪♪
Come on!
[ENGINE REVS]
[TIRES SCREECH, METAL CLANKS]
They crashed. They crashed.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Oh, God.
♪♪
Drop the gun! Down! Put it down!
Back away, or we will fire!
Drop your weapon!
Not happening!
RESSLER: All right, all right!
Easy. Easy.
Nobody's gonna fire.
You. You look like you're in charge.
I'm gonna reach into my pocket.
Slowly!
Donald Ressler, FBI.
FBI?
Who the hell are you?
Name's Reuther.
We're CIA.
CALHOUN: Yevtukh Roofing Company...
safe house front owned by the Agency.
You want confirmation,
call the station chief.
LIZ: Why no deconfliction protocol?
Because we're part of
the Clandestine Service.
- Who are you?
- I can't answer that.
- All I can tell you is we're...
- Black book.
Langley-verified.
- Apology accepted.
- No, it's not.
Look, I don't care who you are
or why you're operating on foreign soil.
I was just doing my job.
- I would've done the same, Agent Coburn.
- It's Calhoun.
I'm a N.O.C.
Navabi. Slightly injured.
- Are you sure you're all right?
- Yes.
This is Duke White,
Defense Intelligence.
Omar Kabinov, FSS.
I'm Tobias Reuther, Clandestine Service.
We're gonna need to talk
to Ghaffari alone.
That's not gonna happen.
He's officially in our custody.
We're handling the interrogation.
If you don't like that,
you can take it up with the boys in D.C.
I don't care who gets him to talk.
As long as you can get him
to tell us what he knows,
we're happy to sit this one out.
Okay.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[DOOR BUZZES]
LENA: Congratulations.
Your stipend was increased to $250.
Hm, fantastic.
What did I do to earn that raise?
You got approved for a riskier study.
Very exciting.
Can I ask what's with all the security?
I mean, we're volunteers, not prisoners.
Lot of drugs around here.
A lot of drugs attract
a lot of drug users.
Makes sense.
So, how much riskier is this?
Several patients in the previous group
developed temporary
neurological problems.
Lie down.
They must have modified
the medication since then, no?
I assume so.
I just run the tests.
That's reassuring.
- Who's the heart for?
- My grandfather.
My brothers and I got drunk
after his funeral,
decided to get tattoos.
He loved cards,
so my three brothers
are the spade, diamond, and the club.
And you're the heart.
That's cute.
So, aside from brain damage,
what fun side effects
should I be expecting?
I honestly don't know.
That's what the study is for.
I keep forgetting...
I'm just the guinea pig.
♪♪
REUTHER: Look, Raqaan,
I don't know why you don't
feel like talking.
The Feds have you on tape
admitting you're supplying Surkov.
MAN: [SPEAKING ARABIC]
You know that.
You must also know that you're not here.
This place doesn't exist.
- [SPEAKING ARABIC]
- No lawyers...
- [SPEAKS ARABIC]
- No diplomats...
- Just us.
[SPEAKS ARABIC]
♪♪
[SIGHS]
[MAN GRUNTING IN DISTANCE]
He'll crack.
They always do.
[GRUNTING IN DISTANCE CONTINUES]
There are other ways
to get people to talk.
You don't know Surkov.
How long have you been
searching for him?
Six years.
Since before I left the Agency in 2015
to start a family.
Reuther reached out a year later.
He lives and breathes Surkov
and convinced me to get back
into the hunt.
And the family?
♪♪
That didn't turn out like I thought.
But it's okay.
[SIGHS]
I've got Surkov.
He's my family.
My white whale.
♪♪
[DOOR OPENS]
Anything?
Give him 20 minutes to simmer.
Okay. You've tried your way.
We're gonna try ours.
Samar?
Hey, hold up. What are you doing?
♪♪
Can I ask you a question?
If their task force is so intent
on finding Surkov,
why haven't we ever heard
from them before today?
♪♪
The hell is she doing?
[HANDCUFFS JINGLING]
Okay, he's ready to talk.
RED: Look closely.
What do you see?
A lot of dander, saliva, and urine,
all of which I'm allergic to.
So maybe if there's a point here,
you might want to make it
before I start to wheeze
like a chinchilla.
Our liquidity crisis has been solved.
By doggy day care?
These are rescue dogs...
picked up at shelters,
given a bath
and a professional grooming,
then given back to the shelters
primped and proud
and ready for adoption.
They supplement their business
with regular grooming.
But it's basically a labor of love
and a 501C3.
- A non-profit. That is good.
- [CHUCKLES]
Even the most ruthless
IRS agent would hesitate
before auditing the books
of such a noble enterprise.
And that's good,
if we can run enough money through it.
I mean, the rents are throwing up
nearly 200K a week.
Well, most of their business is mobile.
They have a fleet of vans
that go from shelter to shelter
in 10 different cities.
It's 100 vans,
a dozen or more dogs a van,
25 bucks a dog.
- You do the math.
- [LAUGHING] I just did.
And my hand to God,
if I found you
a little bit more attractive,
I would birth you a litter.
I mean, like, seven pups...
Boom! Right here on the floor.
Fiona, you're an artist.
Coco's an angel.
Just needed a little TLC.
I have some ointments for you.
Ah. And how much do I owe you?
$150,
- which, of course, is tax-deductible.
- RED: Yes, of course.
And how much for the store?
- The store?
- And the vans.
- All of them.
- [COUGHS, SNEEZES]
- Bless you. Bless you.
- Sorry.
They're not for sale.
At the right price,
I've found everything is for sale.
Think about your price
while I let Coco find a blade of grass.
Come on, sweetheart. That's it.
[LAUGHING] There we go.
[COCO PANTING]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[DOOR BUZZES]
♪♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
COX: Harold.
You're a tough man to pin down.
Thank you for seeing me.
Well, when I heard there was
an FBI task force
running an unsanctioned op overseas,
my interest was piqued.
We received a tip from a credible source
that Surkov is dead.
The attacks attributed to him
may, in fact, be the work of a copycat.
[SPEAKING ARABIC]
SAMAR: He never met Surkov
in person, only video calls.
COX: And your team?
Do they have a lead on his bomb maker?
Ghaffari?
[SPEAKING ARABIC]
He recently asked him
to smuggle a device
into a locker in Virginia.
I don't understand.
Ghaffari's in Belgrade?
Yes, being held and questioned
in a CIA facility outside Pancevo.
Does he know the specific target?
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
SAMAR: [SPEAKING ARABIC]
[SPEAKING ARABIC]
Surkov specifically asked him
to create a weapon
that could penetrate
3.5 centimeters of Kevlar.
I'm sitting here with
the CIA Director of Operations.
COX: Listen to me...
the Surkov team is in London.
There is no team or safe house
in Pancevo.
They claim otherwise.
Well, I don't care what they claim.
Whoever you're with, they are not CIA.
♪♪
[GUNFIRE]
- Go.
- Cover me!
RESSLER: Move, move, move.
LIZ: Give it up.
Hand it over.
You said you were CIA.
Who the hell are you?
♪♪
RESSLER: You hungry? You tired?
Hey, there's a steak and a bed
waiting for you
as soon as you tell us
where your boss is.
I told you. I don't know.
Just like you didn't know his real name.
- His name is Tobias...
- Reuther.
Yeah, he doesn't exist.
The Agency has no record of him.
No, they disavow him.
Him, not you or Duke White
or Omar Kabinov.
They gave us your file.
We've confirmed you resigned
from the Agency in 2015.
And then Reuther recruited me
to come back.
There's nothing about that
or the ghost squad whose designation
is so conveniently top secret
that you never had direct contact
with anyone at the Agency.
We got our orders from Reuther.
Reuther got his from
the Office of the Director.
No one at the Director's Office
has ever heard of your task force.
Because it doesn't exist,
and when we found out,
he started shooting at us.
Looked to me like
you were shooting at him.
Reuther is pretending to be Surkov.
That's ridiculous.
When you found us,
we were hunting for his weapons maker,
looking to interrogate him
to find Surkov.
Do you know how I got Ghaffari
to talk so quickly?
I told him Surkov was dead.
No proof, just the word of my source.
The minute I told him,
he knew it was true.
RESSLER: Agent Calhoun,
there's a bomb somewhere in Virginia
waiting to be detonated
in Surkov's name.
We believe Reuther
is going to detonate it.
Tobias Reuther is a patriot...
- He's a terrorist.
- He loves his country.
If you don't tell us where to find him,
he's gonna commit
an act of terror on U.S. soil.
♪♪
Do you trust your intel on Surkov?
100%.
And Ghaffari's weapon?
We're working with Virginia State Police
and local law enforcement,
but it's a big state
- with a lot of lockers.
- What about Calhoun?
RESSLER: She thought she was working
for an Agency task force.
She had no idea that the man she admires
is the devil she thought
she was hunting.
I always thought Surkov's death
would be cause for celebration.
But if he is dead
and a group of CIA-trained assets
- has taken his place...
- [KNOCK ON DOOR]
ARAM: Sir?
Uh, Director Cox. Hello.
Uh, the only prints they could pull
from the safe house in Pancevo
were partials,
but... we got a match.
Uh, the man we're looking
for, Agent Reuther,
uh, his real name
is Agent Brian Osterman.
Does that name mean anything?
♪♪
Director Cox, who is Brian Osterman?
[SIGHS]
[COCO PANTING]
Cheer up, Lou. I'm in your debt.
LOU: A lot of good that'll do me
if anyone finds out I did this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Giving me this evidence is vital
and much appreciated.
- Giving?
- But what Coco and I have been up to
- is a revelation.
- I need to get that back
- before anyone knows it's missing.
- She's always welcome
to come in for a grooming,
free of charge.
- You really got to return that.
- Oh, and her ointments.
- Ointments?
- Ointments. Funny word.
Twice a day,
three times on her inner folds.
Coco, the pleasure was all mine,
sweetheart.
[COCO BARKS]
[COCO PANTING, WHIMPERS]
♪♪
[KEYS JINGLE]
RED: The suitcase key.
So Kate entrusted it to Nik.
But who did Nik entrust it to,
and why did he get killed for it?
♪♪
And who might you be?
[DOOR OPENS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
[FOLDER HITS DESK]
Brian Osterman was one of our own...
one we no longer consider
a trusted asset.
He was part of a black-book operation
tasked to I.D. threats
to U.S. counterintelligence,
but in '08, he broke from the Agency,
- and we issued a burn notice.
- No, that's not possible.
He became disillusioned, went dark.
He's been off the grid
for the past six years.
If Surkov is, in fact, dead,
and Osterman is now carrying out
missions in his name,
then we're dealing with
a very dangerous man...
one whom you have assisted
in carrying out attacks
against this country.
No, Reuther, he had HUMINT,
and, uh, funding.
- He had...
- Pilfered from a black-ops slush fund
that went missing.
♪♪
The... the others, the team...
He recruited us to the Agency.
COOPER: He lied to you,
to get you to help him attack the U.S.
You and your team are Ilyas Surkov.
You just didn't know it.
But you do now,
and you can help us stop him.
We have a staging area in Ivy City.
I can take you there.
♪♪
[MAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[MAN SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
MAN ♪1: There's another door.
CALHOUN: I don't believe this.
MAN ♪2: Nothing here.
MAN ♪3: Bring your team back.
♪♪
The safe house has been scrubbed.
Nothing on Osterman or his team?
Just an empty file stamped "Cyclone."
That's it.
You sure that name means nothing to you?
Osterman? Nothing.
Well, he's in the wind
with a lethal weapon we can't find
and a target that could be anywhere.
That's what you don't know.
Focus on what you do.
We know the weapon was designed
to pierce Kevlar,
plus the "Cyclone" files.
It could be a... code name,
a mission, a person...
Any point of intersection?
Kevlar, Cyclone.
Where they happen? Costal cities?
Law enforcement in those areas
that wear Kevlar?
What else? Cyclone.
If it's not a person or place...
It's a target.
Not law enforcement, but military.
A target hard enough
to design a weapon to penetrate it.
Not steel, but Kevlar.
Good.
A military hard target
made of a composite material.
♪♪
I need to call you back.
Aram, I need you to run a search.
Any ships in the Navy,
the Coast Guard...
whoever the Pentagon has build ships...
with the name "Cyclone"
that are made of a composite material
similar to Kevlar.
All right, hang on.
Okay, I have
a Cyclone-class patrol ship.
- Tell me about them.
- ARAM: 14 ships...
10 are deployed in the Persian Gulf,
3 are doing drug interdiction
off the coast of Florida,
and this last one...
Okay, yeah, the U.S.S. Parnell
is at its home port.
Where is that?
Norfolk.
Virginia.
♪♪
Dry toast, huh? That's it?
All most people can keep down.
Probably 'cause most people
take the full dose.
Mr. Lembeck, a clinical trial must be...
I'm not here for the trial.
- If it's drugs you're after...
- Not drugs.
I'm here for information
about Pete McGee.
♪♪
Um, you'll... need to sign
a discharge form.
He had a lot of family photos
in his office,
but only one placed
where he could always see it.
And I didn't think there
was anything special about it
until I realized
that it was taken by someone
very special to him.
- It's not what you think.
- I can't help you. I need to find him.
He took something from me
that doesn't belong to him...
something that is only
gonna bring him trouble.
What is it?
Something I was willing
to put whatever that is
in my veins to get back.
I need it back.
- I'm sorry.
- I came here
because I thought I could find
what he took from me
or at least get a lead
on where he went, all right?
But I didn't. All I found was you.
And I'm asking you, I need your help.
And if I'm right,
I think Pete does, too.
♪♪
A discharge nurse should be in shortly.
[SIRENS WAILING]
♪♪
Aram, we're on site. Talk to me.
All right, I've notified Port Authority
and Naval Installations Command.
They're initiating a Level 4 lockdown
and emergency evac protocols
for all non-essential personnel.
- Any word on Osterman or his team?
- Nothing yet.
I am still waiting to get approval
from Security Command
to share their CCTV feeds.
Matthew O'Neil, NCIS.
- What do you know?
- Look, there's a threat against
one of your coastal patrol ships,
the U.S.S. Parnell.
We got to lock this down,
clear all this air traffic.
Easier said than done.
Transport runs a flight
every six minutes.
ARAM: Um, Agent Keen?
I think I might have something here.
NCIS just got a ping on an alias
that Calhoun was able to confirm
was one of Osterman's.
It appears access has been granted
to a Human Resources office
between Powhatan Ave and Pier 11.
♪♪
LIZ: Stand down, Osterman.
You have no idea
what you're in the middle of.
We know about you, Osterman.
We know about Surkov, your team.
- It's over.
- Surkov's dead,
but I'm not using him as cover.
- The CIA is.
- I said stand down.
When an asset reported Surkov
had died from cancer,
Cox thought we could use his name
to do America's dirty work.
- Cox?
- I was on board at first.
Pretty soon it became clear
the jobs we were doing,
we weren't doing America's dirty work.
We were doing Cox's.
That he'd turned.
Tried to plug the plug,
but Cox discredited me
and convinced our superiors
to issue a burn notice.
Did I lie to my team?
Did I lie to you?
Yes.
Because none of you
would believe the truth.
Cox has to be stopped.
Step away from your weapon.
DUKE: Got him. He's at your 11:00.
It's him.
See that man down there
with the black backpack?
He's a CIA asset here to plant the bomb
Cox bought from Ghaffari.
My team is here to stop him.
You have a shot? Take the shot.
Why would he blow up a chemical plant
and an American ship?
False-flag operations.
Even if you're telling the truth,
you're asking me to let you shoot
a CIA agent who's following orders.
- I can't let you do that.
- Take your shot.
- It's your last chance.
- You gonna shoot me
in the back of the head, Agent Keen?
[GUNSHOT]
[GRUNTS]
I have Osterman in custody.
Human Resources, third floor.
We're gonna need a medic.
Alert NCIS of a potential suspect...
an officer in uniform,
brown hair, medium build,
carrying a black backpack.
Looks like you were wrong.
[EXPLOSION]
[PEOPLE SCREAM]
♪♪
[ALARMS SOUNDING, SIRENS WAILING]
You believe me now?
♪♪
COOPER: You lied to me.
Osterman isn't the imposter.
He was hunting the imposter... you.
Osterman is a rogue agent
who's acted against
our national interests.
- That ship was never your target.
- No.
The blast severed
an undersea communications cable
running from Naval Station Norfolk
to our allies across the Atlantic...
a cable that had been compromised
by Chinese counterintelligence.
Now, if we had simply ceased
sending intel,
it would have tipped our hand.
So instead, you sacrificed
the life of one of your agents.
It was a directional device, Harold.
My agent survived,
as have all the agents I've tasked
with taking out our enemies.
Like the plant foreman in Leeds?
He was leaking classified intel
from one of our
private military contractors
to Russian assets.
Our team hid the ops
behind Surkov attacks,
and in both cases,
we avoided escalating
international conflicts.
- At what cost?
- At any cost, Harold!
I hate to disappoint you,
but like Osterman,
I see things differently.
I see diplomatic solutions.
I see a way to get results
without false-flag operations.
But you and I both know
that a terrified population
means a healthy defense budget.
Harold, are you trying to tell me
that the whole time you've been here,
you've done everything by the book?
No cut corners,
no bent rules for the greater good?
Leon, I answer to people
who will one day judge
the merits of my work.
I'm willing to accept the consequences.
You have been operating
without oversight until now.
I've given my superiors
a full overview of this investigation.
I hope, for your sake, they agree
that your actions were in
America's best interests.
I doubt they will.
♪♪
Time will tell.
Close the door on your way out.
♪♪
[MATT CORBY'S "RESOLUTION" PLAYS]
♪ I'm giving up this whole lie,
this whole me ♪
[SIGHS] You have done more harm
than you could possibly know.
- ♪ Instead I bide my time, get a ride ♪
- I'm counting on it.
And it'll be worth it if it stops you.
♪ Until the rubber leaves the road ♪
♪ You said don't lie,
so I made the truth ♪
♪ Seemed like a lie to even you ♪
♪ Control your fear, it's cle-e-e-ar ♪
♪ That you do not know
where you're going to ♪
♪♪
♪ So, don't you wo-o-o-rry ♪
♪ You'll be my resolution ♪
You're here.
♪ Characters of no illusion ♪
So many people find cemeteries
to be a reminder of loss.
I find them to be a fervent
reminder to seize the day.
- ♪ One month down and it's in sight ♪
- I'm surprised to see you here.
Nik Korpal saved my life,
brought Agnes into this world.
- ♪ Oh, I'm guaranteed to lose my mind ♪
- I came to pay my respects.
How are you holding up?
- ♪ It's dangerous to speak and sigh ♪
- I've been better.
About how he died...
♪ So, don't you wo-o-o-rry ♪
Did you find anything out?
♪ You'll be my resolution ♪
♪ Characters of no illusion ♪
- Reddington was a surprise.
- [SIGHS]
♪ You will be my resolution ♪
He appreciates what Nik's done for him.
And he knows Nik may have
been killed because of it.
- ♪ Characters of no illusion ♪
- He's willing to look into who did it.
He is?
Has he found anything?
Not yet, but it sounds like
he has a lead.
♪ You will be my resolution ♪
What kind of lead? Was he more specific?
♪♪
[VOICE BREAKING]
We've lost so many friends.
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
I don't know if I can lose any more
without just crawling
into a fetal position or...
becoming a stark, raving vigilante.
[SIGHS]
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
Listen, Reddington's a vigilante.
- ♪ Turn around, put it down and see ♪
- All right?
And I'm pretty sure
there's a one per family rule.
[EXHALES]
♪ That this is really the place to be ♪
I think Meera is buried here.
- ♪ I'm not you, nor you me ♪
- I'd like to pay my respects.
All right. You want company?
I'd like to go alone, if you don't mind.
♪ But we're both moving steady ♪
WOMAN: The explosion
rocked the naval yard.
While no causalities have been reported,
Ilyas Surkov has claimed credit
for the attack.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
ARAM: Hey, uh...
about, uh, what happened in Belgrade...
What part?
When, um, Agent Navabi was taken...
uh, she could've been hurt.
She wasn't. She's fine, obviously.
But, uh...
I wasn't prepared, sir.
I didn't know how to react.
And then, with the shootout
at the safe house...
Aram, I understand.
It was an oversight on my part
to place you in danger like I did.
It won't happen again.
No, no, you don't understand.
I don't want to be unprepared.
Mr. Cooper, sir.
I'd like to request to be
operationally trained, sir.
TOM: What changed your mind?
You said he might be in trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Might've killed someone.
Pete?
I don't believe that.
Listen, what he took from me,
people are getting killed.
And whether he did or didn't do it,
just by having it,
his life is in danger.
Are you looking to protect him
or have him arrested?
♪♪
I don't know you,
and I'm sure not gonna take
what you say about Pete at face value.
No way he killed anyone.
[RAZOR BUZZING]
Whatever he took from you,
he must have a good reason why.
He hasn't been to work in a week.
He hasn't called.
His divorce is gonna be
finalized next month,
and we're gonna get married.
I'm worried something
might have happened.
I changed my mind
because I want him found.
Whatever your reason is
for wanting to do that,
I don't care,
as long as you're willing to help.
Tell me everything you can about Pete.
Friends, relatives,
cities he likes, passwords...
♪♪
Everything.
Yeah.
FIONA: This rug was a gift.
My aunt crocheted it herself.
Yeah, it's got to go,
and the allergies with it.
This, my space,
it's a critter-free zone.
It's a critter cabin.
Yeah, not in here it's not.
That's six hold list's worth.
Are you African?
'Cause you're a frickin' babe.
Can you handle that?
Ah. I can handle whatever you've got.
The person who answers
may not know the secret.
No, but they might.
[PHONE DIALING]
♪♪
Wonder what can of worms
we're opening now.
[DIAL TONE]
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
♪♪
Hello?
Who is this?
♪♪
[PHONE BEEPS]