♪
MALLOY: Remarkable, isn't he?
Perfect limbs.
Plenty of bone.
Like God's own racehorse.
NIRAH: Extraordinary.
Tell me about the stud fees.
150,000 euros a mare.
150 mares a year.
Bit early to put him out
to stud, if you ask me.
Truth is, Fitz stands
to make more on the stables
than on the racetrack.
I know 150K is a pretty penny,
but your mare won't find a better match.
[LIGHTER CLICKS]
I agree.
♪ Tra la, la-tra la, tra-ah, la ♪
[CHUCKLES]
To Fitzpleasure.
To Fitz. Slainte.
♪ Tra-ah, la ♪
Unfair, really.
Stallions get the prestige,
but breeding a quality racehorse
is as much about the dam...
as the sire.
♪ Tra la, la-tra, la, tra-ah ♪
- ♪ In your snatch fits pleasure ♪
- What have you done?
♪ Broom-shaped pleasure ♪
♪
You're a beautiful creature.
Too beautiful for this world.
♪
[HORSE WHINNIES]
It'll all be over soon.
♪ Tra la la ♪
♪ Ohh, ohh, ohh, ohh ♪
♪ Blended by the lights ♪
[HORSE WHINNIES]
♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Hey, you want to grab, uh, lunch?
Yeah. There's a burger place
in Adams Morgan
I've been wanting to try.
Lunch sounds so...
I believe the word you're
looking for is "amazing."
Yeah, completely amazing, but,
like, something parents would do.
- [CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Oh!
Yeah. If either of us had even
remotely normal parents.
Now, that's the word I was looking for.
Lunch sounds so completely normal.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
You know I love normal.
Someone's really trying
to get ahold of you.
I know. Sorry. Hello?
NIK: Pete called.
He ran a search on the DNA
from the bones.
Uh, sorry, not interested.
Not interested?
Oh, right. Liz is there.
Look, you shouldn't call this early.
- Telemarketer.
- They're not supposed to be calling us.
Look, Pete wants to meet.
His apartment. 2:00.
Hey, we're on the no-call list.
What you're doing is illegal.
She's right. It is.
And I can't believe I let
the two of you rope me into it.
[CELLPHONES BEEP]
At lunch...
no calls, no interruptions.
Agreed. Just you and me... being normal.
- Yeah.
- [CELLPHONE BUZZES]
Reddington?
LIZ: Nice upgrade
from the no-tell motel.
Can you afford it?
It's a three-day rental Dembe
found through some online site.
Something b-n-b?
Are you familiar with such a thing?
Uh, me and a billion other people.
They match hosts who want
to rent out their homes
with guests who want to rent them
and get a commission from each one.
It's a license to print money.
The renters never have
to meet the owners.
The Robinsons simply put my key
in a lockbox outside.
Completely anonymous.
Peel.
Ah!
Great ideas are like great athletes...
efficient, elegant, powerful.
I'm aroused by both
and mourn the death of either.
"Champion racehorse and trainer
die in stable fire."
Fitzpleasure was
the greatest European racehorse
in a generation.
His stud price was set at 150,000 euros,
but he only covered
a single mare before the fire.
One.
Which is why I know he was murdered.
Peel.
It doesn't say anything here
about murder or arson.
RED: In horse breeding,
genes are everything,
and Fitzpleasure had the best ones.
His owners stood to make
millions spreading his seed.
Now he's dead, and another owner
is conveniently positioned
to reap the windfall.
The owner of Fitzpleasure's
only offspring.
- Bananas.
- What? No.
"Pot," "mustard," "satchel"...
- What's that? Q-I? Qi?
- Chur
[LAUGHING] Oh, come on!
It means "life force."
Honestly. You're like one of
those extraordinary children
who knows how to spell "onomatopoeia."
But even he couldn't spell out
why a horse killer
is on the Blacklist.
The last white rhino,
the final dodo bird...
the only surviving member
of a group or species
is called an endling.
You're not looking for
a horse killer, Elizabeth,
you're in search of
the endling himself...
the nom de plume of the legendary
creator of one-of-a-kind items.
LIZ: Baghdad, 2015.
An RPG took down a private plane
carrying
of the only two known statues
of the Sumerian goddess Inanna.
Four crew members were killed
in the crash,
leaving the only other statue
in private hands.
Turkey, 2016.
A nursery cultivating a unique species
of drought-resistant barley
was stolen and three botanists
were murdered.
The genetic profile used
to create the seed was taken
and all but one
of the samples destroyed,
giving the new owner a virtual
monopoly on the next harvest.
Reddington believes her next
target is on U.S. soil.
"Her"?
Well, according to the report
from the Irish authorities,
the trainer who died in the fire,
he had a visitor
just before the incident...
woman of Middle Eastern descent,
early 30s,
going by the alias Alicia Grey.
The best way to find her
is by talking to the people
who benefit from her actions...
Fitzpleasure's sole offspring.
Do we know the owner?
Yep. Caleb Hess...
CEO of an international security
contracting firm
based in Hanover, Maryland.
Yes, I benefited from the tragedy.
RESSLER: Your horse tripled
in value overnight.
That's not a benefit. That's a windfall.
Call it what you like.
It's still a tragedy
I had nothing to do with.
NAVABI: We reviewed your
company's financial statements.
You have quite a bit of debt.
You can't pay your creditors.
We're having issues, yes,
but I don't see what that has...
We know the woman that you hired
used the alias Alicia Grey.
What's her real name?
I don't know because I didn't hire...
You're the largest shareholder,
and when your stock nosedives,
so does your savings.
Now, this is a tough position to be in
for someone who sees themselves
as a provider...
the person who takes care of the family.
And that's how you see yourself,
isn't it, Mr. Hess?
It's why you transferred ownership
of your prized thoroughbred to your son
just days after the unfortunate
incident with Fitzpleasure
sent the value of his new asset
through the roof.
You may be headed towards bankruptcy,
but it seems your son
is wealthier than ever.
I transferred an asset to
my child for estate-tax reasons.
There's nothing illegal in that.
No, there is not, but it is illegal
to conspire to murder a racehorse.
And when we find out
you did that, which we will,
as well as your son
benefiting from that windfall,
we will go after him
as a co-conspirator.
You leave my son out of this.
Sure.
As soon as you tell us
what we need to know.
NAVABI: The woman... who is she?
♪
She never said anything about murder.
All she said was that she could
increase my foal's value.
- She didn't say how.
- How did you contact her?
I didn't. She came to me.
So, how did you pay her?
She didn't want money.
She wanted information.
What kind of information?
Security protocols we put in place
for the daughter of a king.
- Who is she?
- Princess Sonya of Montenegro.
My firm trained her team years ago.
She'll have at least four bodyguards
working in coordination
with local law enforcement.
She uses aliases, decoy vehicles,
and books an entire floor
wherever she's staying.
♪
[CELLPHONE RINGS, BEEPS]
- Dresner.
- Where are we at?
Uh, the numbers are improving
to hit our targets.
Good. Prepare station three.
I should have an addition soon.
♪
What does the endling want
with European royalty?
The princess is the sole heir
to the throne.
If she dies, the royal family
dies with her.
- Who benefits from that?
- According to the State Department,
King Jovan and his daughter
instituted reforms
that were unpopular with
the country's hard-liners.
So the princess' death means
the end of the king's line
and a win for the reactionaries.
ARAM: Okay, according to the
Diplomatic Security Service,
Princess Sonya is here in D.C.
to deliver a speech
at the UNESCO Conference,
and she has a room block
at the Greylock Hotel
in downtown D.C.
under the name Elise Wolf.
Aram, alert hotel security.
Ressler, Navabi, Keen...
get to that hotel now.
"...of all the long-standing..."
[SPEAKS SERBIAN]
Perfect. Please come in.
Donald Ressler, FBI.
Tom Campbell, Head of Security.
We spoke on the phone.
Ms. Wolf has the entire 15th floor.
What's the fastest way there?
Main elevator. South hall.
LIZ: Go. I'll keep an eye
on surveillance.
I'm gonna need access
to your security feeds.
♪
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
End of the hall. Suite 1550.
Hey, wait a minute. What's going on?
Agent Donald Ressler, FBI.
♪
We're gonna need to see your princess.
There's been a threat.
MAN: Checking the stairwell now.
♪
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
♪
Wait. Go back. That stairwell.
Command. Command,
we lost power on the 15th floor.
What's going on?
♪
MAN: There's been a breach on floor 15.
We lost the feeds!
We need to get her out
of there right now!
[BEEPING]
Back! Back! Back! Now!
♪
[ALARM BLARING]
RESSLER: Don't shoot! FBI!
I need confirmation. What's going on?
FBI. Lower your weapons.
What's going on?
Princess Sonya, there's been a breach.
I need you to come with us.
[BLARING CONTINUES]
♪
RESSLER: We've got the princess.
We're on the move.
♪
Ana Dewan?
- Yes?
- Diplomatic security.
Please come with me.
The princess needs you.
Please! It's urgent!
♪
NAVABI: Are you all right?
- Wait. Ana.
- It's okay.
You're safe now. Please. Please.
No. Ana. We can't leave Ana.
NIRAH: Hurry. Please hurry. Get in.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
PETE: I was able to pull
a sample off the bones
and run a DNA sequence,
which, when you think about it,
is pretty remarkable considering the...
- Did you get a name?
- No.
None of the databases
I searched had a match.
Even the federal DNA database?
CODIS is a two-step process,
and I can't get past step one.
I can run the search remotely...
which is super illegal...
but that will only get you a match.
To get an identity, you need
a Fed to authorize the request.
So, you can know the bones match
someone in the system,
but you can't get the name
of that someone
without an FBI agent signing off.
Which ain't gonna happen.
- Whatever you're thinking...
- I could just take her credentials.
- ...stop thinking it.
- She doesn't even have to know.
That's a terrible idea.
An ID would work.
♪
So, I've started her
on Epogen, B12, testosterone.
If she responds like the others,
I'll have her up to
the desired volume soon.
Alert your team.
I want them ready when I return.
♪
[CLATTER]
RED: Hello, there.
♪
DEMBE: Somebody knows we're here.
Pity.
I was just starting to feel at home.
♪
I need a name.
The person who hired you.
No one.
We weren't hired.
Proverbs 21, verse 10...
Solomon's dissertation on the wicked
and the company they keep.
Do you know it?
Proverbs?
Stirs up more passion
than any other verse we study
in Talmud class.
"There is no honor among thieves."
I disagree.
A few thieves have been
among the most honorable men
I have ever known.
What about you... Sven...
are you an honorable man?
Uh... yeah. I think so.
Hmm.
Let's put that to the test, shall we?
♪
[MAN GROANS]
[CLATTERING]
I need a name.
The Mailman. That's all I know.
Nash talked to him. The Mailman sent us.
I do like a nice, long soak, don't you?
♪
[GASPING]
The Mailman. Where can we find him?
COOPER: I know this is
a very difficult time for you,
but understanding why Ana was targeted
is our best chance
of getting her back safely.
Can you think of any reason
why someone would target
your assistant instead of you?
Ana isn't my assistant.
She's...
It's hard to describe what she is.
I'm pregnant.
My child will be second in line
to the throne.
If something happens to me
while I'm pregnant,
if I need emergency surgery,
Ana was here to provide a transfusion.
Why not get one at a hospital?
I have Lutheran B-negative blood.
It's a rare type.
There's no guarantee they would have it.
But Ana does.
That's why you keep her around?
She's a walking blood bank?
Actually, Ana and I
don't have the same blood type.
You're telling me seven people
in the world
have Ana's blood type? Seven?
Out of 7 billion? Incredible, right?
That is why it is known as golden blood.
I understand that it's rare,
but not why it would be valuable
to someone like the princess.
Okay. So, 99% of us
have high-prevalence antigens
in our blood.
If the ones who don't
receive a transfusion
from the ones who do, the
incompatibility can prove fatal.
So, finding a donor for people
with rare blood types,
like the princess, is super difficult.
And if they're in a crisis,
I can only imagine
it would be a desperate race
against the clock.
And golden blood is compatible
with the princess' blood type.
With any rare blood types.
It is the only known universal donor...
which, obviously,
makes its life-saving
capabilities enormous.
RESSLER: Yeah, when there were seven.
Imagine if the endling
kills all but one.
The sole survivor's blood
would be worth a king's ransom.
And, according to
the Rare Blood Database,
two have gone missing
within the last three months.
Does the database list the locations
of any other golden bloods?
In this country, I see one.
Ethan Isaacs, currently in
the ICU at D.C. Mercy Hospital.
Navabi, Ressler... get there.
TONY: Next.
Next!
He's ready for you.
My apologies.
That last one on the right,
I've see him somewhere.
So have I.
Have you? And where was that?
In my dreams.
I have a weakness for bad boys.
[CHUCKLES]
I received two unexpected packages
at my residence last night.
Did you bring the packages
with you, sir?
I'm afraid they're rather large.
They said The Mailman sent them.
Imagine my surprise when I realized
they meant an actual mailman.
Yeah.
I got no idea who they are.
Let me refresh your memory...
they're the men you sent to kill me.
Yeah. Sure thing, Pops.
Whatever you say.
You know, I got a nice
roll of stamps for you.
They have Calvin and Hobbes on them.
Why don't you take those?
You don't know who I am?
Yeah. You're a pain in my ass.
But you sent them to my house.
Why?
Okay. Is this a joke?
That's... Yes.
Janet from circulation sent you
here to yank my chain, right?
I think you know exactly
what I'm talking about.
TONY: Now, listen, pal.
I don't know nothing about you
or your houseguests.
And the only person I want
to kill is my podiatrist
for having my orthotics on backorder.
$59.98.
♪
Alma, hey.
Ethan was hoping he'd see you
before we take him home.
- How's he doing?
- Kid's a fighter,
but, um...
there's nothing more the doctors
can do but make him comfortable.
Yeah. I know. I heard.
He's always hated hospitals, so...
This way he can be in his room, with us.
That's right. That's right.
♪
So, the nurses on four made me promise
that I would bring Ethan by
before he left.
So, why don't you finish up here
and come down?
They have cake.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
♪
[WHISPERS] Hey, kiddo.
Do you want to get out of here?
- Yeah?
- Do you want to go home?
Okay. Okay.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Agent Ressler, FBI.
We're looking for Ethan Isaacs.
What's wrong? What does the FBI
want with our son?
We have reason to believe that Ethan
is being targeted for abduction.
There must me some mistake.
- Where is here?
- He's in his room with a nurse.
Alma said there was gonna be
a goodbye party on the fourth floor.
♪
Start lockdown procedure now. Go!
Where are we, Alma? Where's my mommy?
Sweetheart, please. Just get some rest.
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪
[ENGINE SPUTTERS]
[SIGHS]
Oh! Hey, come on. What are you doing?
When I was 17 and heading off
to the Naval Academy,
I sent the most extravagant love
letter to Sarah Ellen Winstead.
She never replied.
To this day, I remain convinced
that the post office
failed to deliver it,
and that if your colleagues
had simply done their jobs,
the entire arc of my life
might have been different.
I might have been thinner
and living in Maine.
[HOOD SLAMS]
You do realize that harassing
a federal employee
is a felony, right?
I'll add it to the list.
♪
Drive.
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪
LIZ: 8:00 would be great.
Uh-huh.
Oh, I'm sorry... last name Keen.
Thank you.
You planning a hot date?
Cascabel.
- Oh, I love Cascabel's.
- I know.
We're going for dinner tonight.
What do you mean?
You can't stay for lunch?
No. I'm sorry.
I got a call in the parking lot.
It was Aram. He said we had
a break in the case.
You don't have to explain.
Ugh!
Look at those chickens and the burgers
and the fries!
[SIGHS]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Mmm. Root beer.
Come on. I should just be able
to have lunch
with my husband like a normal person.
Yeah, well, you are not a normal person.
You don't have a normal job,
and that's okay,
'cause that's what I love about you.
W... You said you loved normal.
Well, I did. And I do.
But... normal. Abnormal. Deviant.
Whatever you are, I love...
except hurt, all right?
So go save the day, catch the
bad guy, whatever you got to do.
Just don't get yourself shot.
Okay.
Hey! Can I get one more of those?
Cascabel's at 8:00. You're buying.
Hey... deviant.
It's a big turn-on.
♪
ARAM: All right, after reviewing
Ethan's medical file,
I found something interesting...
prior to 2011, it's blank.
How can that be. He's nine?
Because Ethan Isaacs
wasn't always Ethan Isaacs.
Exactly.
The Isaacs adopted Ethan in 2010
through an NGO
that briefly brought
Syrian children to the U.S.
Ethan Isaacs was born
Shahir Ahmad in 2008
in Daraa, Syria,
to this woman... Nirah Ahmad.
Ethan was taken by his mother.
And adoption records indicate
that she has the same
rare blood type as her son.
And in a war-torn country like Syria,
she must've known that a golden blood
has almost no chance
of surviving a traumatic injury.
Well, if the mother's a golden
blood, then she's also at risk.
So, why didn't she leave with her son?
To fight for her country.
She was an active member
of the Free Syrian Army
until she disappeared in 2014.
LIZ: Right after Ethan got sick.
Three months before her first attack.
Where are we on locating her?
When I ran her photo
against the images taken
from the traffic cams near
the hospital, I found this.
NAVABI: Do we have an ID on the driver?
I am still working on that.
According to his file, Ethan has
progressive idiopathic myocarditis.
Now, the procedure
that could save his life
would require transfusions
of golden blood
that the hospital just couldn't provide.
Ethan was being sent home to die.
Instead, his mother kidnapped him.
After kidnapping
two other golden bloods.
We've been looking at this all wrong.
She's not kidnapping them
to create an endling,
she's doing it so that they'll
have enough golden blood
to perform the procedure.
ARAM: And it's not just
the blood she'll need.
Myocarditis requires a heart transplant.
And in order for his body
not to reject it,
the heart needs to come
from another golden blood.
COOPER: Pull everything DHS
has on Nirah Ahmad...
phone records, passports,
known associates.
Get into her life.
Aram, widen the CCT grid
and see if we can't get
a hit on that car.
I want this woman found
before she starts butchering
people to save her son.
[SINGING IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
ETHAN: Where are we?
Some place safe, habibi.
I want my mommy.
I'm right here, my darling.
And when this is all over, I'll
explain everything to you, okay?
I promise.
All you need to know is
I did everything to protect you.
♪
[HUMMING]
I don't suppose you're gonna tell me
how you managed to get this.
TOM: How long till you ID the bones?
Way you're all lathered up,
you'd think we were looking at
the bones of Osama bin Laden.
Just... let me know the minute
you get something, all right?
I get it.
♪
I have enemies.
People who want to kill me.
Why is not your concern.
What matters is that,
when it comes to my security,
I take extraordinary precautions.
Tigger and Pooh violated those
precautions at your direction.
I assumed it was to kill me.
If it wasn't, I need you
to tell me why they did it.
It wasn't to kill you.
When people go away, they put
their mail on hold, right?
We keep a list... it's a hold list...
of who's away and how long
they're gonna be away for.
And then, while they're gone,
we rob them.
That's it.
I know their correspondence.
I know what magazines they subscribe to.
Based on that, maybe their area code.
You know, I can guesstimate
the value of the items inside the house.
How extensive is the list?
I-It covers the city
and the surrounding suburbs.
But it could cover more.
- More?
- The hold lists.
Does every post office
in the country have them?
Yeah. I suppose so.
And the robbers?
I troll the dark web
for interested parties.
I take my commission in advance,
and then I give out the address.
[CHUCKLING] What a marvelous idea.
Really marvelous.
I mean, except, of course,
when the owners rent out
their homes while they're away,
but that's a small burl
in the wood we can sand down.
Wait, So you... you don't...
- you don't live here?
- [DOORBELL RINGS]
Excuse me.
And w-w-what did you mean by "we"?
- Wait.
- Did he say "we"?
♪
The endling's name is Nirah Ahmad.
She has a sick child
who needs a heart transplant.
My gut tells me that every
attack she's responsible for
has been to finance this procedure.
And I know for a fact
that people will die
if we don't find out where
that surgery is taking place.
What else do you know?
Nothing.
We have a photo, that's it.
And we don't know black-market medicine.
You do.
I've seen him before.
Do you know where to find him?
No, but I know who might.
Let me grab my hat.
This should be fun.
[DOORBELL DINGS]
♪
RED: Good afternoon, young lady.
I'm here to pick up my labradoodle.
What's the name?
I don't think we have
any labradoodles in there.
Her name is Edwina.
She was dropped off by
my dog walker, Hiram Toomey.
Of course. Edwina.
I remember... darling dog.
Right this way.
♪
Thank you.
LIZ: Where are we? What is this place?
RED: The private clinic
of Dr. Melissa Lomay,
general surgeon and owner and proprietor
of Doctors Without Morals,
the first choice in healthcare
for the career criminal.
Mm, such nimble fingers.
Brings back memories.
Mm. Raymond.
How's your ass?
Tight as a drum, thanks to you.
We were camping in the altogether
under the most delightful autumn moon
in the Forest of Dean when a wild pig
[LAUGHING] came out of nowhere
and gored my left flank, so to speak.
And Melissa here not only slew
the beast and salved my wound
with a honey of...
- Yarrow.
- ...yarrow compress,
but also made the most
scrumptious pork pie
in the monarchy.
Fascinating story,
but we're kind of in a hurry.
- "We"?
- Cynthia Rutherford.
I've hired Mr. Reddington
to find someone.
One of your employees...
Dr. Felix Dresner,
if I'm remembering correctly.
He's on a job.
Where?
You know I can't give out
that kind of information.
♪
[HUSHED VOICE] Melissa,
while I appreciate your desire
to protect the good doctor,
he is a liability.
Miss Rutherford isn't
the only one looking for him.
The police are, as well.
Help me find him before they do
and I'll cauterize the wound
so nothing bleeds back to you.
What has he done?
The less you know, the better.
We simply need a location.
ARAM: Okay, hold on.
I think I may have just
figured this out.
Okay, the street address
you gave me was zoned
as a zoological research facility,
but construction was put on hold
due to this ongoing court battle.
However, if I'm reading
these permits right,
it looks like the only section
of the facility that was okayed
was the second story.
Agents Ressler and Navabi are en route,
maybe 10 minutes out.
♪
[DRILL WHIRRING]
Step away from the tables.
Hands. Everyone, hands where
I can see them.
No. No. Keep going.
I know you're trying to save your son,
but I can't let you hurt
these people in order to do it.
I will not let him die.
You're gonna have to let us
take him home.
His home is with me. I gave him up once.
I will not give him up again.
The hospital, then.
You know the hospital can't help.
I know someone who can.
[WHISPERS] What are you talking about?
Is there a force in the universe
more powerful than
a mother's love for her child?
The miracles of modern medicine
pale in comparison.
Can be life-saving.
But not here.
Not now.
The next people
who come storming in here
will be throwing you all
in paddy wagons.
The best chance your son has
is if we leave.
Now.
Leave?
Dr. Dresner can stay
to care for the others.
No. Without the doctor
or a viable heart, we can't...
- I know.
- We can't.
I'm asking the impossible... for
you to trust a complete stranger
with the well-being of your son.
But if you stay here,
the authorities will take him
and he will die.
Please.
Trust me.
♪
Three patients for emergency evac.
- Keen? What's going on?
- Where's Nirah?
She and her son escaped
before I got here.
RESSLER: All right,
I want birds in the air,
units at every intersection
in a two-mile radius...
I want this woman found.
♪
- I need your services.
- No.
It wasn't a request.
♪
LIZ: We're sorry for pulling you
into this.
NIK: No, you're not.
Okay, no. I'm not.
If it means saving Ethan's life.
You're not sorry you're in this world...
his world.
The bypass machine is ready...
patient's prepped.
Soon as we have the donor heart,
we can proceed.
The heart is already here.
♪
You know, the day that you
were born, I was also born.
[SOBS]
It was the day I discovered
the true meaning of my life
was just to love
and protect you forever.
♪
NIK: Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
You cannot kill this woman
to save that boy.
Agreed. I have no intention
of killing her.
Strange...
I always knew a golden blood
would have to die
to save his life...
[VOICE BREAKING] but I just
never imagined it would be me.
♪
[GUNSHOT]
♪ When I passed you in the doorway ♪
♪ And you took me with a glance ♪
♪ Should have been ♪
♪ on that last bus home ♪
♪ But I asked you for a dance ♪
♪ Now we go steady to the pictures ♪
♪ I always get chocolate stains ♪
♪ on my pants ♪
♪ My father's going crazy ♪
♪ Says you're living in a trance ♪
♪ Dancing in the moonlight ♪
♪ It's caught me in a spotlight ♪
♪ It's all right, ♪
♪ dancing in the moonlight ♪
♪ On this long hot, summer night ♪
Clear.
♪ Well, it's 3:00 in the morning ♪
♪ And I'm on the streets again ♪
♪ Disobeyed another warning ♪
♪ I should have been home by 10:00 ♪
LIZ: What's the end game?
♪ Now I won't get out until Sunday ♪
Nirah sacrifices herself
to save her son, and then what?
There has to be an ulterior
motive... otherwise, why bother?
I had no veiled intent
in giving you this case,
just a sincere desire to stop a criminal
I believed to be truly reprehensible.
Now what do you believe?
That a sinner can also be a saint.
Are we still talking about Nirah?
Given the same circumstances,
I'd like to think
I'd be as brave as her.
I know I'd want to be.
♪
- How is he?
- He's alive, for now.
His heart's beating on its own.
An ambulance is on its way to
take him to a proper hospital.
If he makes it through
the night, he has a chance.
Thank God.
I'm in your debt.
Can I collect on it now?
Name your price.
Never call me again...
either of you.
Nik [CHUCKLES] you don't mean that.
He's the country's most-wanted criminal.
He's my father.
Which excuses nothing.
An hour ago, Ethan Isaacs
was brought back to the hospital.
But you already knew that, didn't you?
Yes.
Which means you also know Nirah Ahmad
was also brought in...
for an autopsy to determine
who shot her in the head
and transplanted her heart
into her son's body.
- She shot herself.
- You lied to your partners.
Told them you didn't know
where Nirah and her son were,
when you not only knew where they were,
you conspired with Reddington
to arrange an unauthorized operation.
If I hadn't, Ethan would be dead.
And his mother would be alive.
A criminal died to save
the life of a child.
I'm okay with that.
Who cares if you're okay with it?
You don't get to decide
who lives and who dies.
Neither does Reddington.
This was his idea, wasn't it?
Yes, and I agreed with him.
I know.
And that's what concerns me
not just now, but going forward...
his influence over you.
I'm not influenced by him.
Elizabeth, you know how much
I care about you.
As much as if you were my own daughter.
But you're not, you're his,
and I would be lying if I said
that didn't make me concerned.
You have no reason to be concerned.
Maybe.
But if today was any indication,
I think I do.
I'm watching you, Elizabeth.
♪
Listen, man, I've been calling all day.
NIK: Blame your fatherin-law.
He and Liz pulled me into
something typically insane.
They what?
Don't worry, I didn't mention
our little secret.
Well, what about Pete?
'Cause I've called four times,
and I got crickets.
He'll call when he has something.
I don't like it. He's got the bones.
He's got the connection to CODIS.
I mean, I could practically
see the dollar signs
in his eyes earlier today.
What if he screws us?
Look, his place is on my way home.
I'll swing by, see what's going on.
Honestly, I don't know who's crazier...
you or her
or me for helping both of you.
Just call me the minute
you hear from him.
- [CELLPHONE BEEPS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
I am the worst.
I can't believe I missed lunch
and dinner.
Don't worry about it.
It seems like you had a tough day.
Yeah.
It was... complicated.
♪
Anthony. Welcome back.
Look, if this is about you
wanting a piece of my business...
It's not.
Okay, good.
It's about me taking over your business.
Yeah... No! No! That's not happening!
Right now, you have 100% of a business
that clears maybe $50,000,
$100,000 a year. Maybe.
I'm offering you 10% of a business
that will clear 100 times that.
How you gonna do that?
The value of your information
isn't in what you are able
to take out of these houses,
it's in who you're able to put in them.
Reliable safe houses
are incredibly hard to find
and always at a premium.
Instead of robbing these home,
I propose we rent them
to individuals
who don't want to be found.
If you can secure
hold lists in every state,
we'll have a network
of reliable hideouts
stretching all across the country.
Can you get the lists?
Yeah. I could do that.
You can get the people?
Only the ones willing to pay
through the nose.
So, I... we... are gonna be rich?
Obscenely.
In the meantime,
what do you have available
for tomorrow night?
♪
NIK: Pete?
I'm terrified to admit it.
I don't want to admit it. But it's true.
No, it's not.
Look, Liz, you're kind,
and you're decent and honest.
Reddington is not decent.
He's dishonest and he's dangerous.
Reddington and I
got Nik involved in something
he never should've been a part of.
Nik's a big boy.
He can take care of himself.
I know he can, but ultimately,
it's my responsibility.
Nik would've never been
involved with Reddington
if it weren't for me.
♪
And he's been a good friend to us...
...and I just feel like we're
never gonna see him again.
[GASPS]
And I don't blame him.
He'll come around. He will.
Just give him some time.
It'll be fine.
♪