[SOFI TUCKER'S "AWOO" PLAYS]
♪♪
♪ I know I did not raise a wrist ♪
♪ I know I did not capture it ♪
♪ It came ♪
♪ It went ♪
♪ It conquered quick ♪
♪ I was there and then I quit ♪
♪ Awoo ♪
♪ I know I did not raise a wrist ♪
♪ I know I did not capture it ♪
♪ It came ♪
♪ It went ♪
♪ It conquered quick ♪
♪ I was there and then I quit ♪
♪ Awoo ♪
[HORNS HONKING IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
PHOEBE: Truly a labor
of love, to be able
to bring this magnificent
collection to our city...
Where have you been?
They're about to start.
Well, you left your
clutch in the car there.
...Mr. Greyson Blaise.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ I know I did not raise a wrist ♪
Thank you, Phoebe.
You are truly a patron of the arts.
Speaking of patrons of the arts...
Napoleon.
His first wife was unable
to bear him a child,
so he dumped the Empress of France
for the Archduchess of Austria.
He got a child, and
she got a magnificent
gold and silver necklace
consisting of 234 diamonds,
and what is widely considered to be
the most spectacular
jewelry piece of the age.
It's here, and on loan
from the Smithsonian.
Ladies and gentlemen, it
is with great pleasure
that I give to you the
Napoleon Diamond Necklace.
[APPLAUSE]
♪♪
♪ I know I did not raise a wrist ♪
♪ I know I did not capture it ♪
♪ It came ♪
Lock everything down. The
necklace has been stolen.
[ALARM BLARING]
♪ I was there and then I quit ♪
[CHATTER]
♪♪
You've been a naughty boy.
You said you had to have it.
♪♪
♪ Awoo ♪
_
♪ Elevators in your eyes ♪
I can't believe you're back.
I have so many questions for you,
like where you've been.
I'll tell you later.
♪ And you look me down ♪
♪ Now I run the risk... ♪
- But it's done? You're back?
- Yeah.
I'm never gonna leave you again.
♪ You told me that you're anxious ♪
♪ You seem to let it go ♪
Ow, my foot. Oh. [SQUEALS]
- So sorry. Oh, I'm out of practice.
- It's okay. Come here.
- [TOY SQUEAKS]
- Oh, my God!
[CHUCKLES]
When did she get so big?
Was I really gone that long?
[SIGHS] Oh, it happens fast.
You know what we need?
To have sex?
♪♪
We need to get married.
We never got married.
Yeah.
Great. [CHUCKLES]
First, let's have sex.
Okay.
Mm.
♪♪
I'm so sorry I'm late.
Um, last night was crazy.
No time, Keen. No more
excuses from anybody.
I gotta answer to the DOJ and Panabaker
and a new FBI Director
who likes results.
And Reddington's acting
like it's summer vacation.
Well, I don't wanna make
excuses for Reddington, but...
- Then don't...
- if his contacts are compromised
like he says they are...
I don't buy that for one minute.
The man knows people... Criminals.
He's plugged in to an entire
ecosystem of deviants.
I have a hard time believing
he's suddenly so compromised
he can't be of help to us.
No, he's playing grab-ass by the pool
between naps and happy hour.
Where are you going?
We are going to find Reddington.
I've had a teenage son, and the best way
to handle a man with no aim in his life
is to confront him directly.
Myron, I'm in your debt.
Lotta good that'll do me if
the boys find out I was here.
Your associates are buzzards.
But you, my friend,
will always be welcome at my table.
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
This man gets us to a
man named Dennison,
and Dennison gets us to the suitcase.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Elizabeth. Mr. Cooper.
Harold, Elizabeth, please sit.
Have a siu mai.
Is there somewhere we
can talk privately?
Greyson Blaise.
Your room, an office?
You want a Blacklister,
I'm giving you one.
Or are you here to play ColorKu?
An absolutely infuriating game.
Although, I do love the way it looks.
LIZ: Greyson Blaise?
Isn't he the one who
circumnavigated the globe
in a hot-air balloon?
And raced at Le Mans and
trekked across the Sahara
and stole Van Gogh's "Poppy Flowers"
from a museum in Cairo.
He's an art thief.
A thrill-seeker.
A Van Gogh in Cairo. A Picasso in Rio.
And last night in New
York, a necklace...
The Napoleon necklace.
Blaise is a rising star,
and he's using dark money
in politics to spread his influence,
buying loyalty for the inevitable day
when the next thrill
ride he chooses to go on
is to run for something.
King, perhaps.
So how do we get to him?
There's an auction in
Zagreb 36 hours from now.
I'm told Blaise will be there.
Taking down someone
with Blaise's profile
is exactly what we need right now.
Yes. Unfortunately for you, Harold,
I'm not telling you about Blaise
so you can take him down.
What? I'm telling you about him
so you can help me go
into business with him.
And why would I help you do that?
Because you need a powerful CI,
someone people fear.
And if my world learns
I'm aligned with Blaise,
people will be terrified.
Blaise isn't gonna align with you
if he knows you're broke.
Which is why we must
convince him that I'm not.
Fine.
But you're not going
to that auction alone.
Keen, Ressler, and Navabi
are going with you,
and I don't want any arguments.
Who's arguing?
I need a ride, you've got a jet.
♪♪
[DOOR BEEPS]
CHO: What the...?
We're closed today. How
did you get in here?
We need to talk.
Okay, give me the rundown.
What do we know about this auction?
Uh, not much,
and according to Mr. Reddington,
that is the appeal.
Apparently, it's an upscale affair
run by Juric and Bauer, the
boutique auction house
which is hosting the event in Zagreb.
RESSLER: According to their website,
their auction features
rare and exotic coins,
stamps, decorative arts.
You know the international
one-percenters
are gonna be crawling
all over the place.
Which means high security.
Fortunately, the company uses a
computer system to log guests.
I was able to locate their servers
and add a new profile.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
NAVABI: Lovely.
Who am I going to be this time?
Yasmin Shahidi, the only daughter
of an Iranian textile manufacturer
who made a fortune selling private
estates in Beverly Hills.
LIZ: What about Reddington?
With all that security,
it'll be too risky to
bring him in the front.
Once you're inside, you're gonna
have to find an alternate entry.
South stairwell. 30 seconds.
♪♪
[SPEAKING CROATIAN]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
Nice work.
RESSLER: All right. Look, don't touch.
Or bid. I know the rules, Donald.
Well, humor us and try to follow them.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
This is fun... Out and
about, a glass of bubbles...
Just try to keep a low profile.
The last thing we need is
someone to recognize you.
Truth be told, being stuck stateside
has left me feeling somewhat
smothered as of late.
Oh, my goodness. Look
at those Guan vases.
And that flatware.
Did you know Nancy Reagan...
She could dress a table
specifically for that night's
guest at a moment's notice.
Russian Silver for a tea with Gorbachev,
Italian silver stag-head stirrup cups
for a last-minute supper with Sinatra.
Can you imagine?
Sinatra? I can't imagine.
Let's find a paddle
card and a catalogue.
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't enjoy dickering over
an heirloom now and then.
NIK: I just finished my shift.
I'll be home in 31 minutes.
Yep, I use Waze to find my way home.
Don't let the scrubs fool you.
You're engaged to a moron.
I'll be home soon.
♪♪
- Whatever it is, the answer is no.
- TOM: Two minutes.
Okay, less. Please.
AUCTIONEER: We move
on, then, to lot 348.
Might I remind you that
this rare collection
- I don't see him. Do you?
- Includes the finest known bronze cent...
...from each mint,
including the unique
1943-D bronze penny,
which PCGS has certified
at 68 out of 70.
Shall we open the bidding,
then, at $1.8 million?
Did you hear me? He isn't here.
$1.8 million now.
- $1.8 million.
- What are you doing?
- I can't resist.
- Are you insane?
Elizabeth, we're at an auction.
I have to bid on something.
You don't have any money.
Harold does,
and it's important for me
to keep up appearances.
I can't go around looking
like a party pooper.
- [SCOFFS]
- $2.4 million.
Anything under 3 for the
bronze Lincoln penny
is highway robbery.
- It's a steal.
- Knock it off.
All through?
At $2.4 million?
MAN: 3. $3 million.
Gentleman's bid now of $3 million.
♪♪
Sold to you, sir at $3
million, paddle 143.
♪♪
Well, at least we got his attention.
NIK: Reddington's her father?
I can't say I'm surprised.
I'm sad for her.
That sucks, but what does
this have to do with me?
TOM: Nothing. That
mystery has been solved.
TOM: But this one... hasn't.
Who is that?
I don't know. That's why I'm here.
I can't help you. Whoever is in here,
this is the dying wish of
a good woman, all right?
Mr. Kaplan died so that Liz
could find this skeleton
and identify the remains.
Liz is an FBI agent.
Why can't she have the Bureau ID them?
Because she doesn't know about them yet.
Your two minutes are up.
If I tell her now, she
will tell Reddington.
If he finds out before
we ID the remains...
- We?
- ...He will find a way
to make sure she never learns the truth.
There is no "we."
The last time I helped you guys
keep a secret from Reddington,
he almost killed me.
- [ENGINE STARTS IN DISTANCE]
- I get it.
[HORN HONKS IN DISTANCE] Kaplan
didn't leave instructions?
No, just a number to call when
I picked up the suitcase.
She has a confederate.
Maybe he has the answers you need.
I was really hoping
to get them from you.
I really should go.
♪♪
AUCTIONEER: Ladies and gentlemen,
we come now to our next item up for bid,
a lovely work of craftsmanship.
Raymond Reddington.
I didn't know you were a collector.
Yes!
But $3 million for a book of coins
is a bit rich even for my blood.
I'm sorry. I don't believe
we've had the pleasure.
Greyson Blaise.
Colleen Williams. Anna Cartwright.
I'm surprised to see you here, Raymond.
I heard you were, uh, struggling.
If you're struggling, you're alive.
They say that your
associate, the woman...
She, uh, she tried to destroy you.
Anna, those are lovely earrings.
Mm, they were a gift from Greyson.
Cheers!
Wow.
Those are just exquisite.
- Uh, may I?
- Yeah.
Rumor has it you may be in the mood
to unload a certain
waterway in the Aegean Sea.
Oh, I suspect you know
surprisingly little
about my business dealings.
Perhaps, or perhaps there's a
leak in the boat, Greyson...
One we'd need to plug before
hopping into the canoe together.
I don't think I should
be seen with you here.
Yet you understand that running
an enterprise such as mine
requires a network of trade routes
which could prove quite profitable
to a man with your resources.
Go on.
[KNIVES CLANGING]
[ "TAKING A GAMBLE" PLAYS]
I... I don't know where
Dennison is, honestly.
I'd tell you if I did.
♪ I'm taking my chances ♪
♪ With all the odds in my favor ♪
Do you like carrots?
Yeah, sure. Why?
Good.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you making us... a meal?
♪ If I could fix that fortune wheel ♪
♪ I wouldn't have to think twice ♪
♪ Don't wanna risk that sort of deal ♪
♪ If I'm in control
when I roll the dice ♪
♪ I'm placing my bets ♪
♪ I'm playing my aces ♪
♪ Laying my cards on the table ♪
♪ What more can I do? ♪
♪ I'm taking a gamble on you ♪
[ MUSIC CONTINUES]
We should give thanks.
All praise is due to Allah,
who gave us food and drink,
and whose wisdom may guide us
toward a resolution of our conflict
that doesn't involve hospitalization.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is how you're gonna get me
to tell you where to find Dennison?
I believe one gets more flies
with honey than vinegar.
I have also studied the
Behavioral Change Stairway Model
developed by the FBI's
hostage-negotiation unit.
If the goal is to get
one to tell something
they don't want to tell...
empathy and rapport are vital.
♪ With all the odds in my favor ♪
♪ I'm shootin' for the moon ♪
- ♪ And takin' a gamble on you ♪
- This tastes... amazing.
[CHUCKLES]
- ♪ I'm shootin' for the moon ♪
- Red or white?
Red, please.
♪ And takin' a gamble on you ♪
♪ It's a gamble on you ♪
♪ Takin' a gamble on you ♪
♪♪
To finding Mr. Dennison.
RED: What am I thinking?
This is neither the time nor
the place to talk business.
Let's go somewhere, have a drink.
BLAISE: I don't think so.
It's getting late.
- A nightcap... Amaro, perhaps?
- Anna?
I have an early morning.
Well, if you change your mind
or care to see the
Rembrandt, give me a call.
Wait.
The Rembrandt?
"Storm on the Sea of Galilee."
That painting's been missing
for nearly 30 years.
[CHUCKLES] Missing?
The thing's hanging on the
wall of my house on Lake Como.
Oh, my gosh. That's it. I don't know
why I didn't think of it earlier.
We're having a get-together
at the house Saturday.
You should come.
You have a house on Lake Como?
That's not far from me.
Why didn't I know that?
It's a fairly recent acquisition,
papered, of course to ensure my privacy.
I'm throwing a birthday
party for a friend.
Drinks in the garden.
We can talk a little shop,
and you can experience "Sea
of Galilee" in the flesh.
I'm busy Saturday.
Mm.
But if my plans change, I might...
try and swing by...
for the Rembrandt.
[CHUCKLES]
Cheers, Raymond.
♪♪
I thought you were broke.
I didn't know you had a house
- on Lake Como.
- I don't.
Then why did you tell him
you're throwing a party there?
It was the first thing
that came to mind.
I hope Harold's still in the office.
Can you call him?
And say what?
That we need his checkbook.
We're throwing a party.
COOPER: You want the FBI
to throw you a party?
Why on God's green earth
would I agree to that?
RED: Because I told Greyson Blaise
I was throwing a party.
I-I'm sorry, I'm just
so confused, Harold.
Do you not like parties?
I'm trying to figure out
why you promised Blaise
he could see a painting you don't own
at a party you're not throwing
at a home on Lake Como
which you don't have.
I had to say something.
RESSLER: And what if
Blaise doesn't show?
The man is an art collector
who has an opportunity to
see a magnificent painting
that's been missing for 27 years.
He'll show.
The FBI isn't exactly in the business
of, uh, throwing criminals parties.
Let me worry about the
house and the party.
I only need your assistance
acquiring the painting.
"The Sea of Galilee" was stolen in 1990.
No one has seen it since.
Amalia Hammett sees it every day.
It's sitting on an easel
in the living room of
her apartment in Paris.
How do you know that?
I brokered the sale.
And you want us to steal it back.
The woman is in possession
of a stolen work of art.
The FBI can't seize it in Europe,
and while you could request a
joint operation with the French,
I'm not sure they'll let you
lend it to my estate on Lake Como.
So yes, you should steal it.
♪♪
Hey, Navabi, you got eyes?
NAVABI: Not yet. Any minute.
Aram says her calendar
indicates that she and Marius
have a manicure every Thursday at 11:00.
He sounds like a real heartthrob.
Who is this guy, her boyfriend?
More like her bitch.
I'm on the move.
You gotta be kidding me.
♪♪
Speaking of loyal companions,
uh, how are things with you and Aram?
Lovely. Thank you for asking.
♪♪
You and I got a problem.
I'm touched. You're jealous.
Not quite. The old lady's
coming back with her hamster.
♪♪
The painting... It's not where
Reddington said it would be.
What are you talking about?
"The Sea of Galilee"... It's not here.
It's gone.
Well, Hammett's on her way up.
♪♪
[HORN HONKS IN DISTANCE]
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Do you speak English? I
just need some directions.
I'm sorry, young man.
I'm very late.
♪♪
All right, Navabi. You gotta go.
She's on her way up now.
♪♪
The Rembrandt... Where is it?
Excuse me! What are
you doing in my flat?
I have no earthly idea
what you're talking about.
Out!
Get out!
I'm calling the police.
You're not calling anyone.
♪♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
It's amazing.
How'd you convince the
owner to let you use it?
I haven't, but I will.
Sometimes being notorious has its perks.
I know I've thrown a lot at you,
so please, take time to discuss.
So, you want to take our house.
Ah, not take. Borrow.
ANALIA: Ah.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN] _
_
RED: We'll let you two talk.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Maybe you could just
rent a different house.
One doesn't simply rent
the kind of estate
I would have on Lake Como.
Besides, I told Blaise we had a garden.
They'll come around.
No.
What?
My husband, Paolo... He says no.
Analia, who plays the piano?
- Paolo.
- I see.
RED: Please tell Paolo
he's hosting a party tomorrow afternoon.
He can either drink champagne
and tickle the ivories
or spend the rest of the night
locked in the wine cellar.
[ANALIA SPEAKING ITALIAN]
_
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hmm.
What kind of music would you like?
[LAUGHS]
♪♪
We know that you bought
"The Sea of Galilee"...
That Reddington brokered the sale.
Now, you either tell us
where it is right now,
- Or I sw...
- HAMMETT: Or what?!
Who are you anyway?
You're not French Police.
You have no right to come into my home.
You're right, we have
no right to be here,
which should tell you that
we're very serious people
with a serious need
for the information
that we are requesting.
And since we're willing
to break into your house,
there's no telling
what we'd be willing to
do to you or Marius.
How did you know my dog's name?
Where is the painting?
What do you mean she sold it?
It's gone, out of the country.
That back-stabbing old bird.
She promised that if she ever
decided to let that painting go,
she'd allow me to broker the sale.
Donald, we need that painting.
It's not here and we can't get it,
so I hope you have a plan B.
I'm out of the game!
Dale, hear me out.
I'll double your highest fee.
Raymond, I like you, I do.
But this isn't about the money.
The thrill is gone.
Right.
You know what, never mind.
It would've been impossible.
What's impossible?
No, I get it. I'll go.
What are you trying to duplicate?
"Galilee."
Impossible!
Nobody can recreate Rembrandt.
You'd have to be a fool to try!
Uh, forget I asked. It was a mistake.
You're on to other things.
How long until you need it?
24 hours.
♪♪
You'll have it in 20.
["CARMEN: L'AMOUR EST UN
OISEAU REBELLE" PLAYS]
♪♪
Christoforo. [CHUCKLES]
Hello, old friend!
Yes, a party.
[LAUGHING] Yes, yes.
Why would I not invite you?
♪♪
No, no no. Where are you?
Sí, sí.
Yes, a party.
Yes, yes! No, no no!
No, no, bring Basillo and his wife.
No, no no. Sí.
Yes, and the sister, too.
Sí, sí, sí. Yes.
Grazie mille.
♪♪
RED: You look nice.
Thank you, you look...
What is that?
I only brought one suit.
I had to borrow something from Paolo.
What color is that, pumpkin?
It looks like a pumpkin.
His wife says it's Tuscan Sunset.
Ah.
Where's Ressler?
On his way, which is more
than I can say for Blaise.
According to the tracker
I put on his girlfriend,
they're still at their house.
Ah, yes, the tracker.
About that.
The men just finished a security sweep.
Found this.
♪♪
LIZ: What do you mean,
you intended for the
tracking device to be found?
To gain his trust.
I told Blaise he had a mole.
The tracking device confirms it.
- Reporting what? I don't ev...
- GREYSON: Get her out.
No, Greyson, baby, please!
Greyson! Get off!
Greyson!
Anna Cartwright is not a spy.
No, she's a con artist and a thief.
But she's innocent of this,
and by framing her, she could be killed.
She won't be killed.
She'll be banished.
To rebuild, I need Blaise.
And to get to him, I need his trust.
Where the bloody hell is Ressler?
How'd you know about Anna?
I didn't.
Raymond Reddington did.
♪♪
Perhaps I should attend his
little party after all.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN] _
LIZ: Okay.
The good news is Ressler is en route
and the painting will
be here in 20 minutes.
- And the bad news?
- Blaise just walked in.
Of course he did.
[PIANO PLAYING]
RED: Greyson!
- Welcome.
- Raymond.
It seems like the rumors of your demise
have been exaggerated.
Fake news, curse of our times.
[CHUCKLES]
So, where's this painting?
I have absolutely no idea.
So many rooms, so many masterpieces.
Let's wander.
I'm sure we'll stumble
upon it eventually.
Cheers.
[HORNS HONKING]
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
CALVIN: Welcome to Geo. Can I help you?
TOM: Yeah.
I just need to change
the, uh, billing address on my account.
Sure, I can help you with that.
You all right, man?
Uh, yeah.
Let me get your number.
It's 202-555-0105.
Mr... Dennison?
You don't have to call me Mr.
I'm sorry, man.
My wife just, uh,
[CHUCKLES] just left me.
Oh, no, no.
That's fine, uh... Albert.
No worries.
I'll get that billing
address changed for you.
Just, uh, let me get the
last four of your social.
Seven years we've been
together, you know?
- Sorry.
- And she's sleeping with her boss?
- What?
- And now
I'm the one who has to move out.
And I found that apartment, you know?
I remodeled it myself,
and now I'm sleeping
on my buddy's couch.
And she's banging a guy named Phil!
That's messed up.
You know, the guy wears a
bowling shirt, all right?
The kind with his... His nickname
embroidered right on the front,
and it's... It's "Chesty," all right?
She picked a guy named Chesty over me.
If I could just get that new address
where you want the bill sent,
I'll fix you right up.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's, uh, it's 618, uh, Hillgrove.
Great.
So, uh, you want me to
discontinue the copy
being sent to the Kinsey Street address?
That's fine. I don't even, uh, get it.
I just pay it online.
Nah, it says here you still get a copy
sent to 319 Kinsey Street.
I'd be a completely silent partner.
Harold Lloyd hanging
from the clock tower,
risking all, saying nothing.
It's an interesting proposal.
My goods run through your ports.
If I'm caught, you disavow;
If I'm not, you get 5% of the profits.
10% and you have a deal...
- if you show me the painting.
- Yes.
Of course, it looks even better
if you've got a glass of
champagne in your hand.
Where is that young girl?
Don't move a muscle.
[UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
Finally!
Apparently, genius can't be rushed.
Careful! It's still wet.
There's an entrance on the south side
leading into the study.
♪♪
♪ Have you ever ♪
Analia, just in the nick of time.
No, enough with the
champagne and the stalling.
Do you have the painting or not?
♪♪
As a matter of fact, I don't.
Truth be told, I'm broke.
I knew it. And this...
all of this, the estate?
It belongs to Analia here.
- The caterer.
- A-And the pianist, Paolo.
They lent it to me under duress.
Is that true?
Sí.
♪♪
Leaving so soon?
As far as I'm concerned, sugar,
it can't be soon enough.
Oh, but you haven't
seen the painting yet.
♪♪
What's this?
We were just, uh, taking it down to...
I don't understand.
Y-You said you didn't have it.
I don't. You do.
That's why my men were taking it down.
A gift to commemorate
our new partnership.
♪♪
It's beautiful.
So much more vivid than any photograph.
The colors jump out,
almost as if the oils on
the canvas were still wet.
Dale has spent two long
years restoring it.
And now it's yours.
No. I'm sorry, but I-I couldn't.
You could, and you will.
Wrap it up and load it into his vehicle.
♪ She's trying and she wanna know ♪
I don't know what to say.
Go. Enjoy.
We'll talk tomorrow,
set things in motion.
Thank you, Raymond.
♪ We trying and we wanna know ♪
I can't believe it worked.
Almost.
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
Inspector Scutari?
Yes, hello.
I'm calling about the stolen painting.
Sí, the Rembrandt.
♪♪
COOPER: He did what?!
RESSLER: It worked... The entire plan.
Blaise agreed to align his
operation with Reddington's,
and then, Reddington turned
him in to the Italian police.
Apparently, it was all pre-planned.
There was an art-crime inspector
waiting for Reddington's call.
♪♪
Sir, you seeing this?
[CHATTER]
ARAM: So Mr. Reddington gave the
forgery to Blaise as a gift,
then set him up to get arrested with it?
COOPER: This makes no sense.
The whole reason to go there
was to convince Blaise
to do business with Reddington.
So he played us, but why?
RED: I told you.
The reason we're here is
to rebuild my empire.
By partnering with Blaise,
by getting him to vouch for
your financial situation.
That is a lily I may have gilded,
but it's a lovely evening on Lake Como.
Let's not spoil it picking
the sense from the nonsense.
Where are you going?
Blaise's mansion is about
15 minutes from here,
and inside it is the cornerstone
on which I can begin to rebuild.
Are you telling me that
this entire thing...
The forgery, the mansion,
the 150 bottles of wine
and Blaise's arrest...
Were all an extremely
expensive and elaborate ruse
so that you could rob him?
Yes.
Cool!
Cool? May be the wine
or the fact that I have no
legal jurisdiction in Italy
or that Blaise called
me "sugar" earlier,
but yeah... I think it's really cool.
♪♪
[ENGINE REVS]
Help you with something?
What are you doing?
Why aren't you destroying everything?
Destroying? I'm sorry, who are you?
They haven't notified you?
We're on the brink of a Level 4 breach!
- What is your name?
- My name?
Caden Gard, Chief International
Council for your employer.
I have some attorney out
here, Caden somebody.
- I don't have time for this.
- I-I'm only here
because Blaise has been arrested
less than 20 minutes ago,
and within another 20,
this place is going to be
crawling with Carabinieri.
I called ahead, gave
explicit instructions
that everything was to be destroyed.
We just got a tip from
our man in Interpol.
- They said that...
- That Blaise was arrested.
What do you think I'm standing here for?
Miss Chloe and I are only here
because this is a
Single Scope SCI sweep.
- I... I d-don't know what that is.
- Oh, my God.
Where is Peniford?
- Peniford?
- All right.
Radio your team... Everyone!
Tell them I'm on site and
we're at Tier 3, okay?
Miss Chloe, contact our man in Interpol.
Find out how much time we have.
If anyone shows up, the
alert word is "pumpkin."
You, inside.
- SECURITY OFFICER: We're Tier 3.
- MAN: Huh?
Cellphones, pagers, anything with a chip
needs to go in the microwave right now!
Egidio says the police
are on their way...
15 minutes, maybe less.
You. Can you access the security feeds?
Yes, sir. Get there and destroy them.
Okay people, listen up...
Sugarfoot has been arrested,
and time is of the essence.
We're Tier 3,
but this is what we prepared for.
You all know the protocol.
This is now officially a
Single Scope Operation.
You and you, I need you to find
anything with a hard drive,
get it in the bathtub.
You two, you're on paperwork.
Anything with numbers gets burned.
Somebody show Miss Chloe the financials.
And you, show me Yankee Bob White.
- Sir?
- The safe!
Where's the safe?
Oh, my God.
He's keeping financials
on the entire staff.
This could implicate all of us.
Take it downstairs and burn it.
You, get me the
combination to that safe.
Take these.
♪♪
Before we get killed,
you mind telling me
what we're looking for?
Blaise's passports...
Find them, shred them.
Miss Chloe, time?
Six minutes and counting.
Some of the records are on paper,
but Mr. Blaise...
He keeps the important
docs on this thumb drive.
The passports! Go, now!
What about the painting?
"Dance"? The Picasso?
Get it out of here, anywhere.
H-Have them put it in my car.
♪♪
- [GASPS]
- Take it.
- What?
Uh...
The Lincoln Penny?
That's what we're here to steal, a coin?
Do you have the thumb drive?
♪♪
Threw both of Mr. Blaise's
desktops in the lake.
Uh, the police may find them,
but the drives are toast.
Listen to me. Good God, man, listen.
If you make it out,
there's a small hotel in Paris...
3241 Rue de la Mare. Say it back.
- 3241 Rue de la Mare.
- Go there.
Get a room under the name Mr.
DeLacey. Say it!
Mr. DeLacey. Right.
I'll make contact when it's safe.
Until then, talk to no one.
Do you understand?
Good luck, mate, and Godspeed!
♪♪
[CHUCKLES]
Is that really a Picasso
in the back seat?
Yes. That was a nice surprise.
[ENGINE STARTS, REVS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Harold, you're obviously upset.
COOPER: No, I'm not upset.
"Upset" is an emotional word.
My reaction isn't about emotion.
It's about my job.
It's about you consistently
keeping me in the dark
and refusing to respect my role
as the head of this task force.
And you know what else it's about?
Your ego and your obvious
failure to understand
that this entire operation,
everything we're trying to do
here, is hanging by a thread!
My mistake. I thought
you might be upset.
You lured us in, acted
like the only thing
you needed from us was a
ride to that auction.
The next thing I know,
my people are stealing paintings...
To be fair, stealing back a painting.
Or trying, at least.
Not to mention half-a-dozen invoices
for a party at a house on Lake Como!
Right.
Please don't forget to
pay the catering bill.
Those folks were very, very nice.
After all of that, what do
we have to show for it?
Nothing. You handed Blaise
over to the Italian police,
so we don't even get
credit for the arrest.
True, the Italians will get
credit for arresting Blaise
with "The Sea of Galilee."
Of course, it's not
"The Sea of Galilee,"
which they will undoubtedly
realize shortly,
at which point they will be forced
to release Blaise with apologies.
So nobody gets him. Wrong.
You get him, Harold...
You and this Task Force.
Because while the Carabinieri
have bogus evidence,
you have the genuine article.
Fast, hard proof of Blaise's
criminal activities
all over the globe...
Art heists, missing masterpieces.
That necklace alone should
be enough to put him away
and get your new Director off your back
for a long weekend, at least.
♪♪
What was in that house
that was so important?
♪♪
Penny for your thoughts.
Why'd you do it?
Why'd you let me?
It wasn't the wine.
♪♪
I'm scared of you.
Now more than ever.
Of who you are, because...
you might be who I am, too.
I let you do it because it felt
like the right thing to do.
It wasn't.
But it certainly felt
that way because...
Because you're my daughter?
♪♪
In more ways than I care to admit.
[DOOR CREAKS]
♪♪
Are you Dennison?
- Who did this to you?
- [COUGHS]
What happened? You okay?
Who did this to you?
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[ELEVATOR DOORS SLIDE OPEN]
I'm sorry.
♪♪
[DOOR CREAKS]
RED: Albert?
♪♪
Albert, look at me.
Do you know who I am?
♪♪
You're a tough son of a bitch.
Your loyalty to Kate is admirable.
But you will die, Albert...
here and now,
if you don't tell me
where that suitcase is.
♪♪
Who has it?
I won't ask you again.
♪♪
[LAUGHS]
[CRYING]
♪♪
[GUNSHOTS]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
Hey, hey.
Who... Why did I pick up the suitcase?
Ole...
What?!
♪♪
Oleander.
Who's Oleander?
Find him.
Who is he?
What is... What is Oleander?
♪♪
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
NIK: Hey, it's me.
Nik, what's up?
I've been thinking about this,
what you said.
I have no interest in getting
involved with Reddington,
but if what you said...
If you think Liz is in
some kind of danger,
just tell me what you
need me to do, okay?
Thank you. Nik, that's, uh...
Thanks. Look, I don't feel comfortable
talking on the phone. Can we meet?
Yeah. Text me an address.
LIZ: Wow, smells amazing!
Yeah, well, hold your judgment
until you've tried it,
because I might end up killing us all.
- [CHUCKLES]
- "Us all"?
What's going on?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
♪♪
Elizabeth, good evening.
Hello! What's going on?
Tom didn't tell you? I
was invited to dinner.
I set four place settings.
Every time I see you, you're with Dembe,
so I just thought the
two of you, you know.
TOM: I don't know what I thought.
Thank you, Tom. I regret I can't stay.
I have another engagement.
Sorry to have inconvenienced you,
but at least you'll have
plenty of leftovers.
Before I go, let's have a toast.
♪♪
What exactly are we celebrating?
Tom's return, of course!
Your family must be very
happy to have you back.
I remember warning you not to embark
on that silly adventure.
But nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Welcome home.
Cheers.
♪♪
So, what have you been up to?
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com