(BIRDS CALLING)
♫ ♫
Did they go all the way
down to Arctic Avenue?
Yeah, if you hit Arctic,
you went too far.
No, turn back.
Yeah, you're gonna hang a left
on Ashley Street.
All right,
I'll see you in a bit.
♫ ♫
All right, Brax.
Bring it on!
Whoo! There you go!
(WAVES CRASHING)
♫ ♫
Mom?
(COUGHING)
Mom!
Michael!
- Come on. Come on.
- Yeah, I see them.
Come on. Brax, Poppy,
go to your mother!
- Come on. Come on, Brax.
- Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
(COUGHING)
♫ ♫
(ALL COUGHING)
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
- (CELLPHONE VIBRATING)
- If you answer your phone...
- Ohh.
- ...we are getting a divorce.
I have to meet Reddington
in 30 minutes.
No! No, you don't!
Just tell him
you're on your honeymoon.
Tell him that
your second husband insists
- you take one day off.
- Um, technically...
- One day...
- ...you are my first husband
because our first marriage
was annulled...
- Uh-huh.
- and last night was our first time...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...sleeping together
as husband and wife.
- Hmm.
- Well, actually, like, the third time...
- Well, first night.
- Mm. Mm-hmm.
- And morning.
- Mm-hmm.
(LAUGHS)
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
Guy really has a problem.
That's your phone.
Oh.
"No Caller ID"?
- That's very mysterious.
- (CELLPHONE BEEPS)
- I want to keep it that way.
- (CELLPHONE THUMPS LIGHTLY)
Hey, you could've won a set of
steak knives or the lottery.
You know what?
I did win the lottery...
when you agreed to marry me...
- Aww.
- ...again.
- And I have steak knives.
- So we're good.
It's fine. Don't need to answer.
- Ah.
- (LAUGHS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Are you okay?
I'm better than okay.
I'm great.
We're great... Tom and I.
We got married.
See?
Now's normally when people say
"congratulations."
(CHUCKLES) Sorry.
Tom and I have had
our differences,
but I believe he wants
what's best for you.
And Agnes.
Congratulations, Elizabeth.
Thank you.
You know, um...
for the first time
in a very long time,
I feel...
I don't know... (INHALES DEEPLY)
Happy. (CHUCKLES)
Then I see what's going on
in the world.
Migrants hidden away...
in a Chinese freighter bound
for South Carolina.
Human trafficking.
"Trafficking" implies
the passengers...
are being moved
against their will.
These people...
paid for the privilege.
All over the world,
criminals are smuggling people
into countries
they can't enter legally.
Some are hoping for
a better life.
Others are escaping war
or persecution for a price.
People like me can help them.
Like you?
You're in the
human-smuggling business?
I was.
My organization provided
access to the Americas,
various European countries,
select destinations in Asia.
For a fair price,
I provided a quality service.
Mr. Kaplan put an end to that.
In her feverish desire
to destroy me,
Kate destroyed
my relocation networks.
Why are you telling me this?
Because, as you can see,
a ruthless and unscrupulous
player has stepped forward
to fill the void
left by my absence.
- (DOOR OPENS)
- The ship these people
were packed into
like sardines...
...was a death trap.
It wasn't fit to
make the journey,
which is why it sank two miles
off the Carolina coast.
(IRISH ACCENT) Mr. Zhang...
I'm a simple man.
When I hire a mechanic (CHUCKLES)
I expect him to know
how to fix my car.
When I hire a Snakehead,
I expect him to know how
to ship our clients
without killing them.
It was... a mistake.
Please.
29 clients died.
Clients who were supposed to pay
a balance upon arrival.
But that's obviously
not gonna happen...
now that they're dead.
We did what you said.
We put a-as many people on...
(GUNSHOTS)
(THUDS)
(SHELLS CLATTERING)
Sorry, Da.
I wish you didn't have to
see that.
Dead clients
don't make us money.
But neither do
dead employees.
RED: Elizabeth,
whomever has filled the vacuum
left by my downfall
has to be stopped,
or more innocent people will die.
So, Reddington was moving people
illegally across borders.
Do I have that right?
In his mind,
he was giving people hope.
Yeah. Some are only alive
because he got them away from,
you know, whatever they
were running from.
Don't assume that all those
people were good people.
Most, perhaps, but border
control is essential.
Whatever you believe
about the business,
bottom line, people are dying,
and that needs to stop.
The player who took over
Reddington's routes...
- He doesn't know who it is?
- Which is why he needs our help.
COOPER: Sounds to me
like what you want is...
help getting rid of
the competition.
There are much easier ways
to earn a dollar...
than moving migrants.
I did it because someone will,
and if it's going to be done,
it should be done well...
by someone who holds
to certain standards.
Very noble.
A man in your position
has the luxury...
of acting on
his own conscience.
I am the Assistant Director
of the FBI.
I'll help you take down
whoever took your place,
but the Bureau can't be responsible
for putting you back in
the global smuggling business.
- Fair enough.
- Good.
Then where do we start?
Greece.
The route north,
through Macedonia.
It's the most traveled
and the most lucrative.
It's a simple plan.
We put someone in the pipeline.
He gets the name of the person
who took over my routes.
- We pull him out.
- Does that mean
you know the access point
they're using?
I do. Normally, I'd suggest
we insert one of your people
to get the name,
but this time...
I suggest we use one of mine.
ARAM: We'll stay in touch
via this device...
I can embed in your rear molar.
It works like a microphone
and allows me to
pick up your voice.
And I can hear you because
the same transmitter allows
the sound of your voice
to travel up the jawbone
and into my inner ear.
Yeah, that's... that's right.
Um, how'd you know that?
Khan Academy.
I took their course
in electrical engineering.
Uh, don't you also speak,
like, five languages?
Eight.
You know, other than the fact
that you sometimes...
have to kill people for a living,
you're, like, my role model.
Open up.
♫ ♫
(MAN SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE
IN DISTANCE)
♫ ♫
(MAN SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE
IN DISTANCE)
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
He's in.
Aram, you have ears?
ARAM: I do.
We are up and live.
Okay, heads up, people.
We have no idea
what we're walking into here.
Aside from the fact that we have
no legal authority in Greece
and we're sending a civilian
in undercover.
He's gonna crush it.
Welcome, friend.
Help you find something?
I was told you have a copy
of Eratosthenes' map of the world.
It's not for sale.
♫ ♫
I was also told...
everything's for sale.
You'll have to ask the boss.
♫ ♫
(DOOR CREAKS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
♫ ♫
(DOOR CREAKS)
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV)
♫ ♫
(SIREN WAILING ON TV)
(SOUND ON TV MUTES)
(REMOTE THUMPS LIGHTLY)
Let me look at you.
What's your name?
Malik Charef.
Where you from,
Malik Charef?
Oran.
I see.
And how does
an Algerian find himself
so far from home?
I traveled to Zawiyah,
bought passage across
the water to Lesbos.
And now I'm seeking safe
transport to Berlin.
Search him.
He's onto something.
He's checking for a wire.
Who are you?
The police?
The Astynomia?
♫ ♫
Open your mouth.
Open.
Sir, what do you want us to do?
Hold. Let it play out.
You're not from Oran.
You've had dental work
done in the West.
Maybe I should kill you.
(STERNLY) Who are you?
Count down from five.
If I'm with the police,
they're listening.
They won't let you
get to zero.
They'll storm this place,
and then you won't have
to guess who I am.
You think this is a game?
(GUN COCKS)
Let's play your game.
Five...
- Sir, they're gonna shoot him.
- We got to move.
No! Hold your position.
...three...
two...
one.
♫ ♫
Be here tomorrow, 10:00.
I'll have you in Germany
by the end of the week.
The cost is 3,000 Euro,
and payment is due up front.
The Irish are no longer
accepting funds upon arrival.
(PHONE DIALS)
LIZ: The Irish...
The coyote Dembe met with
mentioned something
about the Irish.
Do you know
who he's talking about?
Yes, the Irishman...
Arthur Kilgannon.
I've never met him.
He lives in Sofia.
That's not a city I frequent.
♫ ♫
(ICE CLINKING)
Hello, old man.
Is the sun past the yardarm?
Perhaps I'll have a drink, too.
♫ ♫
(TIRES SCREECH, GEARSHIFT CLICKS)
- TOM: Hey.
- I wasn't sure you'd come.
Sorry. I couldn't take your calls.
My wife and I were,
uh... occupied.
- What have you got?
- You were right.
Pete's been using
my account information
to take out
a credit card in my name.
- And he used it here?
- The fraud unit called,
asking if I could confirm using
one of my cards here
yesterday at 6:43 p.m.,
so he was here.
Come with me.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
♫ ♫
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Sweetie.
Do you have somewhere
I could try this on?
Uh, no.
Sorry, I don't.
Figured as much.
Mind holding my purse?
♫ ♫
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(SIGHS)
What do you think?
Too tight?
No.
No, it I... It looks good.
Yeah.
♫ ♫
(PHONE SHUTTER CLICKING)
(TOILET FLUSHES)
Hey! Y-You can't be in here.
Hey, did you hear
what I just said?
(BOTH GRUNT)
That one. Definitely. Time to go.
Thanks again.
You're a life saver.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
♫ ♫
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Your reputation precedes you.
But unfortunately for you,
so does yours.
You've had a setback.
Yes, of which you've taken
full advantage.
Well, I doubt you came
all this way...
just to compliment my efforts.
I have a proposition.
Well, then, you've come to
the wrong Kilgannon.
My son handles
all the day-to-day now.
He rebuilt your
smuggling network
in next to no time. (CHUCKLES)
It's easy to move quickly
when you don't care about
quality control.
The ship from China?
Colin said
that's an isolated incident.
My sources say otherwise.
The way I hear it,
travelers are dying
all over the place.
In six months,
the business you took from me
won't exist.
My proposition is
a 50-50 split.
Colin cedes
operational control to me.
Mortality rates plummet.
Profits soar.
My son...
knows what he's doing.
♫ ♫
(GLASS THUMPS LIGHTLY)
The reputation
that precedes you
is one of a man with
exacting standards.
I'm sorry to see
that's not the case.
♫ ♫
LENA: He's hurt.
TOM: Yeah, well, it's not
easy killing a man.
I'm sure
Nik put up a fight.
You don't know he killed him.
Well, he changed his appearance,
so he's hiding something.
That one. There...
that's his car.
♫ ♫
Hello.
What is that? A key?
"Red Birch Motel."
♫ ♫
COOPER: Meet Arthur and
Colin Kilgannon.
On paper, they're consultants
to the shipping industry.
In reality, they smuggle
illegal objects and substances
around the globe.
- Including people.
- ARAM: They operate out of Bulgaria,
protected by the older Kilgannon's
political connections.
So local authorities
won't cooperate...
- on warrants or subpoenas.
- Which will make it impossible
to track their operation.
Not if we have someone
on the inside...
to document it for us.
Absolutely not.
I've already been
approved for transport.
You went in to get a name.
You got it.
- Mission accomplished.
- People are dying.
Which is why
you mustn't go.
Or why I must.
I know what it feels like to be
seen as less than human.
A thing transported for money.
You saved me from that.
Which is why I know you'll want
me to try and save others.
♫ ♫
I'll fly you back to Thessaloniki,
then head up to Berlin
and wait for your arrival.
If we lose contact,
the Task Force...
will track you from
the point of departure.
And I can work backwards
from the destination
until we find you.
- If something goes wrong...
- It won't.
If it does...
♫ ♫
I'll look after your family.
I know you will.
But my concern is,
who will look after you?
(SCOFFS)
♫ ♫
(DOOR CREAKS)
GOGA: I commend you
for getting this far.
Now all that stands between
you and your destination is me.
Do as I say,
and I will make sure
you get there.
Disobey me,
and I will make sure
that never happens.
(GASPS) Mama?!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I'll see you
on the other side.
♫ ♫
(DOOR CREAKS)
That Chinese ship!
You knew it was in no condition
to make that trip,
but you sent it anyway.
Who told you that?
Raymond Reddington.
He'd say anything
to get his routes back.
No, Colin, I've checked it out.
Hundreds dead.
And you gave the orders
to overcrowd the ships
and the trucks.
We're moving people in equipment
unfit to transport livestock!
- Da, listen.
- No!
It's my fault.
I thought if I gave you
the business, you'd change,
but you've always had
a mean streak,
even as a child.
You've proven yourself to be
unfit to run this business.
Sorry, Colin.
You're out!
You can't do that.
Da.
Get off me!
No!
Colin!
You can't do this.
Do you hear me?!
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINED) Colin!
♫ ♫
Do you hear me?!
Are they in Macedonia yet?
Yeah, they just crossed
the border...
using a series of tunnels
along the Suva Reka River.
COOPER: I spoke to their
Minister of Internal Affairs.
He knows that we have agents
in-country watching the van,
but that's all
we're allowed to do.
Any official action
has to be taken...
by the Macedonian police.
Hey, Dembe.
Everything is okay here.
We've got a solid fix
on your location.
♫ ♫
- (BRAKES SQUEAL)
- LIZ: Looks like we've hit
our first way-station.
Armed guards and gates.
You guys seeing this?
All right,
I clock multiple warehouses,
rail cars, trucks...
a lot of movement.
I have eyes on a secondary exit,
but there must be more.
There's no way
we can cover them all.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(HUSHED) Out. Out.
No talking. Quick.
Let's go. Come on.
Stay together.
Hurry.
Mama.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
GOGA: Quiet!
♫ ♫
Go, go, go, go.
ARAM: Guys, this place is
the perfect cover...
a shipping complex housing
over a dozen corporations.
Everything from smart-phones
to frozen fish.
Shipping containers
moving in and out.
How would anybody know
some of them are packed with people?
We could be looking at a lot more
than just a way-station here.
This could be the Kilgannons'
European base of operation.
If it is, there's probably
enough evidence in that building
to build a damn good case
against them.
We should move on it now
and get Dembe out
- before something goes wrong.
- COOPER: I agree.
Let's end this before
we get in over our heads.
I'll ask the Macedonians
to secure a warrant.
♫ ♫
LENA: There... that's Pete's car.
You sure?
Yeah.
♫ ♫
(GEARSHIFT CLICKS)
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF)
♫ ♫
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
- What does it look like?
- (GUN COCKS)
You don't know that
he killed your friend.
We don't know he didn't,
so if it's all right with you,
I want to make sure
he doesn't kill us, too.
You have a problem with that,
you're welcome to wait in the car.
♫ ♫
(CONVERSING IN ARABIC)
_
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
♫ ♫
(COUPLE CONTINUES CONVERSING IN ARABIC)
_
♫ ♫
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
PETE: Who is it?
It's Lena.
I need to talk to you.
- Lena?
- (LOCK DISENGAGES)
- (DOOR CREAKS)
- What are you doing here?
Miss me?
- Where's the suitcase?
- Were you followed?
- Suitcase.
- Shut the door!
Where are the bones?
You have no idea
what they're capable of.
I know what you're capable of...
killing Nik.
He said you killed his friend.
Me?! If anyone's responsible
for what happened to him,
it's you... (GROANING)
for what happened to me, too!
Oh, my God.
H-He came into the clinic
looking for you.
You disappeared.
I was worried.
You lied to her
about being married.
Why should we believe you
about this?
I don't care
what you believe.
You roped us into this.
And the guys who did this...
They knew it, too.
They knew I put in
a request with CODIS.
I don't know how,
but they did.
So they came to my place
to get the bones and kill me.
- Kill you?
- Yeah.
After playing mumbly
peg to try to get me
to give up the names
of anyone else who knew,
which I didn't, FYI.
Yeah. They did get the suitcase,
I bet. And Nik?
He showed up after I passed out.
And when I came to,
I heard a noise, a struggle.
I looked out.
I saw this guy.
He had his arm wrapped around
Nik's neck.
I ran.
All I know for sure is that
if he hadn't shown up,
they would've killed me, too.
(DOOR CREAKS, THUDS OPEN)
♫ ♫
(THUMPS)
Up!
Time to go! Let's go!
Hurry! Quick!
Quick, quick.
Move, move, move, move.
All right. You, this truck.
- (SHOUTING IN ARABIC)
- You, over there.
No! Move! I said move!
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
- Wait!
- Move!
Please, that's our daughter!
- Don't do this.
- Anna!
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We just lost the connection.
It sounded like he was hit.
- Get him back.
- I can't.
- Sir, we need to get in there.
- Nobody's going anywhere.
I'm not sending you blind into
a building full of armed guards.
And we were specifically told
not to take any action
without the local police.
- I'm begging you!
- It is my daughter.
- Please!
- Mama!
♫ ♫
SAMAR: Tactical units
are pulling up now.
♫ ♫
(TIRES SCREECHING)
- (SCREAMS)
- Anna! Anna!
(SOBBING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
♫ ♫
(MEN SHOUTING)
- Ohh!
- (GROANS)
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
♫ ♫
MAN: He's got a weapon.
Look out!
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(GROANS, COUGHS)
Dembe? Do you see him?
I don't have him.
He's not here.
Keen, check that truck.
MAN: Let's go. Now.
- Dembe.
- Ohh!
♫ ♫
- Dembe is gone.
- What do you mean gone?
We believe his truck
left the premises
before we got to the building.
Well, they couldn't have
gotten very far.
We set a perimeter,
but it's not that simple.
They used tunnels
to get into Macedonia.
Elizabeth,
somebody in that warehouse
knows where to find that truck.
Yeah. I know.
We're working on it.
(CELLPHONE BEEPS)
(GROANS)
Cornelius Goga. Huh.
You're losing a lot of blood,
Cornelius.
(STERNLY) Hey!
Do not pass out on me.
(GRUNTS) That truck that just left...
Get on the phone and
contact the driver now.
(SCOFFS) You won't find them.
"Them"? How many are
still out there?
The minute you raided,
our dispatch sent...
a burn signal to our drivers.
- I don't believe you.
- You're too late.
Our drivers know.
They ditched their trucks,
walked away.
Nobody can find them now.
Only our drivers know
where they are.
- LIZ: Cooper?
- We're here, Agent Keen.
- The photos you sent are coming through.
- Reddington?
I'm right here.
Tell me what you know.
As of now, there are still
seven trucks unaccounted for.
The police are looking for them,
but the drivers were instructed
to abandon them in
hard-to-find places.
Dirt roads, parking garages.
- Then find the drivers.
- The drivers are in the wind.
ARAM: Uh, everyone,
uh, I think we might have
another problem here.
The truck in the photo you sent...
Is it the same size and style
- as the one we think Dembe's on?
- Yes. Why?
It's a refrigerated truck,
meaning its cargo bay
is airtight.
- If the truck stops running...
- The air stops circulating.
COOPER: Aram, can you
pull up the specs on the truck?
Tell us how much oxygen
the cargo bay can hold?
Actually, it's... it's not the
oxygen that's the problem, sir.
It's the carbon dioxide
we breathe out.
3% is fatal to humans.
When the air reaches 3% CO2,
everyone inside
will asphyxiate.
How long?
- Aram, how long?!
- Hang on.
The truck's cargo bay is
just under 1,000 cubic feet.
The average person produces about
1.7 cubic feet of CO2 per hour,
times 15 people.
- Maybe 2 1/2 hours.
- I have to go.
- Do what you can.
- (CELLPHONE BEEPS)
♫ ♫
Hey! Can you hear us?!
Why have we stopped?!
Shh! You will give us away!
You're afraid of being caught?
We've been abandoned!
- Someone will come.
- Staying calm will not keep us alive.
We have to get out of here.
There's not enough air.
♫ ♫
_
(GRUNTING)
♫ ♫
It's okay. Someone will come.
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
All right, I'm coming!
(DOOR CREAKS)
Where is Arthur?
- I'm sorry. Who are you?
- I need to see your husband.
Please, It's important
I speak to your husband.
My husband is dead.
♫ ♫
Your... Uh, your son?
If you could get your son
on the phone.
No, whatever on earth
is the matter, please...
Mrs. Kilgannon, someone
I care about a great deal
is in imminent danger,
and I have very little time.
The only person who can help me
is your son.
So unless you want
this exchange...
to become considerably
more heated...
you'll get him on the phone
immediately.
- The entire facility lost!
- (CELLPHONE RINGING)
Do you have any idea
what that means?!
That one location was funding
most of our operation!
- (CELLPHONE BEEPS)
- (SIGHS) I can't talk now!
The seven trucks that received
burn signals in Macedonia...
I need the names and addresses
of the drivers.
Reddington.
You told my father I was unfit
to run the company.
You tried to have me pushed out.
Why would I help you?
Allow me to pay you the courtesy
of being blunt.
I need your help to find
those trucks,
or I'm gonna have to put
a bullet in your mother's head.
You'll kill my mother?
That's your leverage?
You have five seconds.
Oh, let's not waste time.
Go ahead and put her down.
Put a bullet in the old lady.
I would've done it
meself eventually,
- but you can save me the trouble.
- (CELLPHONE BEEPS)
(CELLPHONE BEEPS)
♫ ♫
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Colin drives
an old American sports car.
It was very expensive.
He had the vehicle outfitted
with GPS tracking.
If you let me
go to my computer...
I can give you
his exact location.
♫ ♫
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GRUNTING)
GARVEY: Did I wake you?
I'll make this simple.
I have the suitcase.
And because I have the suitcase,
I need to speak with
Raymond Reddington.
So here's my offer.
The person who puts me
in contact with him first
will live.
I can't guarantee
the quality of your life,
but breathing is
part of the package.
♫ ♫
The other two will die.
Thoughts?
Questions?
I can't tell you
what I don't know.
That's more of a comment, really.
Tom, tell him, damn it.
Tell him!
Look, he's the one who knows.
He ran it all.
He... hired me
to extract the DNA.
I just ran the search.
I see.
So you're of no use.
(SCREAMING)
♫ ♫
It's no small thing to betray
a man like Reddington.
I'd want to think about it, too.
But, unfortunately,
you don't have that luxury.
Maybe this will aid
in your deliberations.
Wait! Wait!
She doesn't know anything.
I don't. Please.
I-I won't say anything.
I-I don't even know
where we are.
I could just go...
- I'll just go.
- Go?
You don't have to do this.
Darling, I-I'm not...
uncivilized.
I just need the information.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
♫ ♫
Go.
Go on.
You're free to go.
♫ ♫
(HURRIED FOOTSTEPS)
(SCREAMS)
♫ ♫
Then there was one.
Pull any docs that tie us to the
facility and destroy them.
The bank records, payroll,
evidence of our payoffs
in the border...
- (GUNSHOTS)
- Oh!
♫ ♫
Your mother brought you
into this world, Colin.
Did you really think
she couldn't take you out?
♫ ♫
Aah!
I want the names of those drivers.
Okay. Okay.
I can get them.
They're in his briefcase.
How convenient. Who's he?
My financial adviser.
He handles the payroll.
Mm. Thanks, Colin.
♫ ♫
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
♫ ♫
It's not working.
We need to save
the air we have.
You need to slow
your breathing.
Give me that!
♫ ♫
(WOMAN COUGHS LIGHTLY)
_
♫ ♫
This just came in
from Reddington.
Those are the drivers happen
who received the burn signal.
I don't understand.
How did Reddington...
He got to Kilgannon,
got the payroll records.
We have their legal names
and addresses...
and the routes
they were assigned.
They've found three trucks
so far...
two in a forest,
one in a parking garage.
There's no sign of Dembe.
- How much time do we have left?
- About 35 minutes.
All right, we need to get to
these guys and find those trucks
before they turn up
full of bodies.
Wait.
There were seven trucks.
There's only six on this list.
Reddington is going after
Dembe's driver.
♫ ♫
(GUN COCKS)
We all don't have to die.
- Sit down.
- No. Look.
If there is something we can do,
something to give a few of us
- more time to be saved...
- What are you saying?
I'm sorry,
but if there were fewer people,
there would be more air
for the others.
- Enough.
- Let him talk.
Who do you propose?
I was thinking by age.
The oldest first...
That seems fair.
Fair? To murder my wife?
Yes. To save others.
And who will do this?
You?
Look her in the eye as you
choke off her last breath?
I am not going to die here!
And you will not kill
anyone either.
I don't remember anybody
putting you in charge.
Maybe you will go first.
♫ ♫
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Even with fewer people,
the air won't last long.
We will not start killing
each other just to die anyway.
Whatever happens...
we do it together.
♫ ♫
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Can you feel that?
Can you hear it?
That's your heartbeat.
Concentrate on it.
Slow it down.
It's okay.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Shh.
Driver's not here.
I'm too late.
LIZ: You don't know that.
All of his stuff...
his clothes,
prescription bottles...
It's all still there, right?
He knows the police are after him.
He can't run with nothing.
He has to come back.
You ever wonder why Dembe
stays with me...
why anyone so decent
would spend his days
at the side of
someone so indecent?
You saved him.
He owes you his life.
He protects you because
you protected him.
No, Elizabeth.
Dembe didn't stay with me
because he saw me as his savior.
He stayed with me because
he saw me for the man
I really was...
a man surrounded by darkness.
No friends who could be trusted,
no faith that loyalty or love
could ever truly exist.
I was...
Well, I was younger then.
Angrier.
Dembe connected his life
with mine to show me,
that day and every day,
that the world is not
what I fear it to be.
He is the light
in the darkness.
Living proof that
there is another way,
that life can be...
good...
that people can be kind,
that a man like me
might one day dream
of becoming a man like him.
He pledged his life,
offered it up as evidence
that I was wrong about
this world.
Dembe guards my life
because he's determined
to save my soul.
♫ ♫
You were wrong.
Nobody knows we're here.
Nobody's coming.
♫ ♫
It's okay.
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
Sleep.
Your parents will be waiting
when you wake up.
♫ ♫
(CELLPHONE BEEPS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
♫ ♫
(LOCK DISENGAGES)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(GUN COCKS)
The truck.
Where is it?
♫ ♫
DEMBE: She barely has a pulse.
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
(GRUNTS)
The ambulances are on their way.
She won't make it if we wait
for an ambulance.
♫ ♫
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(ENGINE REVS)
(SIGHS) She's alive.
And sleeping.
The doctors expect
a full recovery.
The resilience of the young.
♫ ♫
(ENGINE STARTS)
I thought I'd lost you.
Not yet, old friend.
The world can be such
an unsparingly savage place.
One could be forgiven
for believing...
that evil will triumph in the end.
Those who believe so are wrong.
If you'd died today, like that,
it would be all the proof I needed
that you are the one who is wrong.
And here I am.
(CHUCKLES)
And here you are.
♫ ♫
They found all seven trucks,
packed full of people.
The police say
some might not make it,
but we saved
a lot of lives today.
So that they could be
arrested and deported
like the others
at the warehouse.
What about them?
Ressler is on with Cooper now.
15 passengers as expected, yeah.
Three were taken to the hospital
by ambulance.
And Dembe and Reddington
took the girl.
- So you have 10 there.
- Correct.
Police have their hands full
with the warehouse
and the other trucks.
And once everyone's been
cleared by medical,
they asked us to transport
everyone we've got...
back to the station house.
Sir, look, I have to say,
I-I knew this was happening.
I knew people were risking
their lives...
by the hundreds of thousands.
But, I mean,
knowing it and seeing it...
♫ ♫
It's different.
Agent Ressler,
stay on the line.
(DIALING)
(CELLPHONE RINGS, BEEPS)
Harold! I'm here with Dembe.
Dembe. Thank God.
Oh, we have some good news.
It seems the young Anna Elazar
will live to see
a brighter day.
Another day, maybe.
I'm not so sure about brighter.
Her parents were arrested.
Who knows how long it'll take
to reunite them?
And even then,
her future is back
at that migrant camp in Greece.
Bleak business, Harold.
Yes, as we speak,
my agents are preparing
to transport
10 recovered migrants
into the custody of
the Macedonian police.
10 people...
with only minutes left,
perhaps,
before they wind up
back in a cell.
Of course, were my agents
to encounter any resistance
while making the trip
to the local station house,
our hands would be tied.
We have no formal authority
in Macedonia.
In fact, we've been
specifically ordered
not to engage with
hostiles of any kind.
Donald!
♫ ♫
♪ So I rise ♪
♪ I rise ♪
♫ ♫
I'm not sure what will happen
with the girl and her parents.
Well, I've found a little
bribery goes a long way.
♫ ♫
♪ High rise ♪
(SPEAKS IN ARABIC)
(LAUGHS)
♪ Who is in you? ♪
♪ High rise ♪
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
♪ You hide them behind you ♪
♫ ♫
♪ High rise ♪
♪ Who is in you? ♪
(DOOR OPENS)
You know, all this time
I've given you to think has
prompted me to do
some thinking of my own.
And, uh... I got to tell you,
I'm stumped.
When you consider
all the people on the planet
who would be interested
in the contents of that case
and you multiply that number
by an even greater number
of unspeakable things
those people would do to get it,
how the hell could it
end up in the hands
of a little pissant like you?
♫ ♫
Maybe because I'm not
the pissant you think I am.
Oh, no?
Do tell.
Your man got the drop on me
at the Red Birch.
I'll give you that.
But that story has a different
ending in a fair fight.
Shame I won't get a chance
to see that.
Thinking time's over.
Listen, listen, listen!
He's my boss.
CRESPIN: We've got
a very serious problem.
Someone grabbed Keen
and the case.
♫ ♫
You want to know
why I had that case?
'Cause I work for Reddington,
and he sent me to get it.
- You're lying.
- I'm not lying.
I got a wife and a kid.
I'm not dying here,
not from you, not for him,
and certainly not for whatever
the hell's in that case.
(CHUCKLING) I don't even know why
everybody wants the damn thing.
You want Reddington?
I can give him to you.
He trusts me.
I can deliver him to you.
Just give me a chance.
♫ ♫