♪
[ Engine revs]
♪ many years since I was here ♪
- It's not here yet?
- Sir?
I had the maitre d'
call for my car
about 20 minutes ago.
I'm gonna be late, pal.
- ♪ I was passin' my time away ♪
- [ Horn honks ]
- We got a 0-1-2-0-6.
- ♪ to the left and to the right ♪
- [ Horn honks ]
Sir, so sorry.
We don't seem to have
this vehicle in the lot.
The car's
been picked up.
[ Scoffs ]
The hell it has!
My guy says
the car's not here.
Now, wait a minute.
I haven't picked my car up.
I've been in your restaurant
eating lunch.
A lemon-verbena iced tea
and salmon salad,
- which was overcooked, for what it's worth.
- [ Horn honks ]
And I'm certainly not
one of these meatheads
who tells you
to keep it close.
But if my Range Rover
is gone--
Sir, the ticket--
The ticket is collateral
for my $100,000 vehicle,
and if it's not--
This is a waste of my time.
- I need to speak to your manager, okay?
- [ Engine revving ]
♪ sayin' "Where are we?" ♪
♪ stop at 3rd and 43 ♪
I am so sorry.
We're having a little
employee situation.
I don't want to hear it,
boss.
Just do your job
and park the car.
And, boss?
Keep it close.
♪ ooh ♪
♪ feels so good tonight ♪
- [ Engine revs ]
- ♪ ooh ♪
♪ who cares about tomorrow ♪
♪ so, baby,
you'd better believe ♪
- ♪ I'm back ♪
- [ Tires screech ]
♪ back in the New York groove ♪
♪ I'm back ♪
♪ ooh, yeah ♪
- ♪ back in the New York groove ♪
- [ Siren wails ]
♪ I'm back ♪
- ♪ back in the New York groove ♪
- [ Cellphone rings ]
Elizabeth.
How are you today?
Liz: Oh. I'm good.
Where are you?
I thought
we were meeting up.
Just bumped into
a few old friends,
- just catching up.
- [ Siren wailing ]
Are those sirens?
Yes.
[ Chuckles ]
We're outside.
It's very noisy here.
Perhaps I could
call you back.
- Wait. Reddington, are you okay?
- Never been better.
Hey, why don't you drop by
my new place.
You'll love the pool.
I'll send you
the address.
Sorry, sweetheart.
I need to get off.
- ♪ so, baby, you better believe ♪
- [ Engine revs ]
♪ I'm back ♪
- ♪ back in the New York groove ♪
- [ Tires screech ]
♪ ooh ♪
♪ I'm back ♪
♪ back in the New York groove ♪
♪ ooh ♪
♪ I'm back ♪
♪ back in the New York groove ♪
[ Engine revs ]
♪ ooh ♪
♪ I'm back ♪
♪ back in the New York groove ♪
[ Siren wailing,
glass shattering ]
♪ I'm back ♪
♪ back in the New York groove ♪
♪ ooh ♪
♪ I'm back ♪
- ♪ back in the New York groove ♪
- [ Engine revs ]
♪ I'm back ♪
♪ New York groove ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
_
My God, Raymond.
She's a beauty.
Yes.
Yes, she is.
How'd she do?
Like Bergita Olofson
in her parents' rumpus room
on a Saturday night.
[ Laughs ]
This should cover
my outstanding debt,
along with the rest
of the month.
And, Dariush, if it's not
too presumptuous,
I'd like pay for drinks
at tonight's social hour.
I'm feeling flush.
♪ one, two, get down ♪
[ "Paid The Cost To Be The Boss"
by James Brown playing ]
♪ paid the cost to be the boss ♪
♪ I paid the cost
to be the boss ♪
♪ look at me,
you know what you see ♪
♪ you see a bad mutha ♪
♪
♪ look at me,
you know what you see ♪
♪ you see a bad mutha ♪
♪
♪ paid the cost to be the boss ♪
♪ look at me,
you know what you see ♪
♪ you see a bad mutha ♪
Hold up.
Agent Navabi.
"Agent Navabi"?
I think we're
a little bit beyond
"Agent Navabi,"
aren't we?
Yeah, um, 100%,
but, um, we agreed to keep it
professional at work.
[ Elevator clanks ]
It's not like
we broke any laws.
Oh, my God.
I forgot my bike.
Your bike.
Where is it?
In the shop.
I cracked the hub
on the Rolf wheel,
so, uh, took a taxi.
Well, you're late.
- Cooper's been looking for you.
- What's going on?
The new FBI director
got sworn in today.
And his first
order of business
is a Bureau-wide review
of all special operations.
They're gonna find out
that Mr. Reddington's empire
has been decimated.
What they'll find is that
Reddington gives us
more high-level targets
than anyone else in the Bureau.
I'm not worried about his
ability to provide us cases.
I'm worried we may have
a perception problem.
- What does that mean?
- "Perception," sir?
There was a DNA test
between Reddington
and Keen.
And it's only
a matter of time
before I have to disclose
the results of that test.
Which were?
♪
Raymond Reddington's
her father.
♪
- [ Muzak playing ]
- [ Footsteps approach ]
Reddington?
Elizabeth.
You've just missed
the Ludeman family.
I must've thrown quarters
for that little girl to fetch
for over two hours.
Soda pop?
You're living here.
I make my bed
where I lay my head.
At the Terrace Vista
Motor Lodge?
I got to tell you, I'm thinking
about making it permanent.
Dariush, the owner and I,
are somewhat the same size,
which has been
a Godsend.
I think you'd
quite like it here.
They host a social hour
at sunset--
music and cocktails.
It's a lovely crowd,
really.
Eclectic,
to say the least.
I thought you'd be
a little bit more proactive,
trying to find ways
to rebuild,
crawl your way
back to the top.
Where's Dembe?
Dip your toes in.
I swear Dariush keeps the pool
at body temperature.
You can't even feel the water.
[ Chuckles ]
I'm glad you're having
a nice time.
But Cooper actually
sent me to see
if you might
have a case.
Oh. I didn't realize you were
here on official business.
Well,
you are my father and...
Oh, my God, that sentence
and all that it means.
But, to be honest, knowing
who my father is at this point
isn't gonna change who I am
or the fact that you're my CI.
And I need a case.
Then I suppose
I'll need my pants.
♪
[ Door bell jingles ]
Good afternoon.
♪
Everybody be cool.
I know who you are.
I've always wanted
to hunt for bounty.
♪
- You're Raymond Reddington.
- And you're a bail bondsman,
which means you're likely
looking for a fugitive.
I believe I can help.
Are you asking
for a job?
Yes.
Your biggest case.
- Who is it?
- This isn't happening.
You're offering to help me
find a fugitive?
You're a fugitive.
And as much
as it pains me
to hunt one of my own,
it pains me more to admit
I need the cash.
So, a name.
Smokey Putnum,
wanted for embezzling
over $2 million
from Davis and Fox
Entertainment.
- The movie company?
- No, the carnival.
How fun. Even better.
I love a good carnival.
Liz: Um, could you excuse us
for just one moment?
Sure.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
We need
a Blacklister.
Harold needs
I need
to pay the rent,
and beggars
can't be choosers.
- We need a name.
- And we have one.
Smokey Putnum.
Please, do tell.
Putnum went dark
about two days ago.
He's due in DC for a trial
in 36 hours.
Now, if he doesn't
show up,
I forfeit my $80,000,
all-cash bond.
What do skip tracers
usually get?
About 10%.
20%?
I couldn't sleep right
if I took a penny over 50%.
$40,000, and I'll have Smokey
to court on time.
Elizabeth,
you'll need to pack a bag.
We're taking
a road trip.
- "We"?
- Yes, please.
I don't have a car.
[ Scoffs ]
[ Footsteps depart ]
- See you in 36.
- [ Door bell jingles ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
Tell me you have news.
[ Indistinct announcement
over PA ]
I was able
to trace the suitcase
to a bus station
in Columbia Heights.
But it's gone.
No witnesses,
no surveillance.
Dembe, one of Kaplan's
associates has to have it.
We need to find
that suitcase
before it finds its way
to Elizabeth.
♪
[ Country music playing ]
Yes, sir.
I told him the situation.
[ Sighs ]
No, he doesn't seem
to care.
It's Cooper.
He's been happier.
Hello, Harold.
You're
a bounty hunter now?
Have you ever had
deep-fried butter?
Bringing a fugitive
carnival manager back
to stand trial
for embezzlement?
Clogs more arteries
than a car accident
during rush hour,
and, yet, people out here
can't get enough of it.
Keen told you
we're under review.
We have a new director.
I need Blacklisters.
And you'll have one soon,
after we do a little rebuilding.
You expect the FBI to help you
rebuild a criminal empire?
Perhaps you're the one in need
of some clarification.
The Blacklist has value
because it is based on the best
possible intelligence--
information that was not
available yesterday
and will be obsolete
tomorrow.
The criminal underworld
is not static, Harold.
It consists of
constantly shifting
alliances and leadership
which can only be discerned
by a few key players.
I was
one of those players,
and with your help,
I intend to be one again.
Because,
like deep-fried butter,
I am unhealthy
and yet irresistible.
[ Cellphones beep ]
Excuse me, um, sir?
I'm wondering if, uh, you
decided to tell the new director
about Agent Keen and
Mr. Reddington's relationship.
Not yet,
but as a rule,
I like to come down
on the side of transparency.
So you think the Bureau
should be kept informed
about
personal relationships?
[ Cellphones beep, vibrate ]
_
Hey. Just got word
from Main Justice.
Laurel Hitchin
was found dead.
The National Security
Advisor.
Medical examiner and Mobile
Crime are on scene now.
- You and Navabi, get there.
- Sir?
We both know
Reddington's behind this.
If it points back to him,
it points to us.
- Go.
- Find out what's going on.
- Aah!
- Settle down, boy.
Big Boy:
Dog house is closed.
We're looking
for Joe Putnum,
or "Smokey,"
as they call him.
US Marshals
come and gone.
K-eaz-eep y-eaz-our
m-eaz-outh sh-eaz-ut.
I w-eaz-ern't go-eaz-nn-eaz-a
s-eaz-ay n-eaz-oth-eaz-in'.
Y-eaz-ou al-eaz-ready s-eaz-aid
t-eaz-oo m-eaz-uch.
[ Laughs ]
Ah.
[ Grunts ]
Wh-eaz-at, uh, d-eaz-id
y-y-eaz-ou--
Ah, the hell with it.
The Marshals.
What did you tell them?
And preferably
not in Cant.
Cant?
It's a private language
carnies use
to keep outsiders
from understanding
what they're
talking about.
I spent two summers
operating the Whack-the-Cats
at the Emmet County Fair.
And to be honest,
I had no idea what the hell
any of them were saying.
But I'm pretty sure
this one was telling this one
not to cooperate.
Bad advice.
We'll tell you
same as we told them.
Don't know
where he's at.
Wouldn't say
even if we did.
Why not?
Putnum stole from you.
[ Scoffs ]
Says Hawkins.
She handled the books.
Always got first count.
Total cake-cutter.
Got caught, cut a deal
to testify against Putnum.
That's why he skipped.
Minute he sets foot
in the court,
he's got a snitch
waiting to finger him
for a crime
he didn't commit.
Who's TL?
♪
The lady asked you
a question.
TL?
Who's TL?
Tammy Lynn Thompson.
And where might we find
Tammy Lynn?
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Camera shutters clicking ]
♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
You think
it was an accident?
No sign
of forced entry.
Any prints,
signs of a struggle?
Well,
we're still dusting.
Good news is, turns out
she has a surveillance system.
And?
We just got here.
Give me a little time.
We're talking about
the National Security Advisor
dead in her own home.
I want real-time intel
on this.
When you know, I know.
♪
This was no accident.
[ Birds chirping ]
Didn't know
Smokey had no sister.
I'm sure you didn't.
Smokey still doesn't know.
Loretta spent
her last five years
trying to find him.
And when'd she die?
Just under
a year ago,
which is why we must
find Mr. Putnum soon.
If I can't conclude
the paperwork by week's end,
the entire inheritance will
be forfeited to the state.
Tammy Lynn, I've worked with
Jacobson and Orr for 36 years.
I have never seen
an estate payout this big.
We're talking
life-changing money.
Putnum smokes Hartswicks.
We saw a picture of him
at Russell Springs.
This one's still warm.
Oh, dear.
- Where is he?
- [ Gun cocks ]
What the hell
are you doing?
Mr. Putnum, you need
to come out right now,
or we're gonna make a mess
in Tammy Lynn's living room.
Get out!
Get out of my house!
Mr. Putnum?
I'm gonna count to three.
1, 2, 3.
- [ Gunshot ]
- What the hell?!
- [ Gun cocks ]
- No?
Let's try again,
shall we?
[ Gunshot ]
- [ Ceiling rumbling ]
- Smokey?
[ Chuckles ]
Funny.
The janitor
at my elementary school
was called "Smokey."
No idea why.
He never smoked
a day in his life.
But I tell you what--
If you don't come down here
right now,
they're gonna be calling you--
[ Ceiling creaks ]
Oh!
[ Rattling ]
[ Grunts ]
Now,
there's an entrance.
[ Coughs ]
You can't take me back.
They got Hawkins.
She cut a deal.
That greedy, craven, little
coward is gonna testify,
and when she does,
they're gonna lock me up.
Maybe you should've
thought of that
before you stole
the money.
Red: Tell me it's true.
The file says you were
a gaffer
with the Ringling Brothers.
I've always been fascinated
by your line of work.
His "work"?
Running the bumper cars?
Elizabeth,
this man was responsible
for moving
the greatest show on earth
from city to city.
The Pentagon sent
its top people
to study
his logistical legerdemain
to learn how to move troops
in and out of battle.
Imagine the trains,
all the performers,
their equipment,
the crew, roustabouts,
the animal wranglers,
veterinarians.
An entire city
moved at night.
Not to mention the lions
and tigers and bears, oh, my.
What a showman.
What a mind.
I forgot my insulin
at the house.
We got to-- We-- We-- We
got to turn around.
- We're not turning around.
- But my insulin.
I sincerely doubt
you have--
What do you want?
You want money?
You can have the money.
It's yours if you let me go.
How do I know
you still have it?
- You're not seriously considering--
- It's in Richmond.
5052 West Graham Road.
It's yours.
Fine.
I'll take it.
- No, no deal!
- Yes! Thank you.
After I surrender you
to the court
and collect my bounty.
Now, it's just
over 600 miles to DC,
so if we push on, we should
be there in 10, 12 hours.
That said,
if time permits,
I would love to stop
along the Bourbon Trail
and try
a Honey Ginger Buck.
I think
we might be stopping
a little earlier
than you'd like.
♪
Must be
US Marshals.
♪
US Marshals!
Pull over!
- Oh, God.
- Don't stop.
No, no,
you-- you can't pull over.
They're US Marshals.
If I don't stop--
If you do stop,
they'll search this car,
and while it may be
Mr. Putnum they're after,
they'll be thrilled at
their unexpected discovery.
Let me handle it.
- Elizabeth, no.
- [ Tires screech ]
Just let me
get rid of 'em.
♪
FBI. I'm transporting
a fugitive.
- What is it?
- Trouble.
These aren't Marshals.
Elizabeth!
- [ Gunfire ]
- [ Man shouting indistinctly ]
[ Glass shatters ]
♪
Reddington!
[ Gunfire continues ]
♪
[ Tires screech,
metal twisting ]
[ Groans ]
♪
[ Gun cocks, fires ]
Get in!
[ Car door shuts ]
[ Tires screech ]
[ Gunfire continues ]
[ Screams ]
I got a lot of questions!
But first,
who the hell were those guys?
♪
They're skinheads?
What the hell do you mean,
skinheads?
Other than the fact that
they happen to have skinheads?
They run
a massive drug cartel
that launders profits through
Davis and Fox Entertainment.
- The carnival?
- It's a cash-heavy business.
The profits
are Smurfed
and worked into the proceeds
of each city.
So, your brilliant
criminal enterprise
was founded on the concept
that you steal money
from the most ruthless,
bass-ackwards groups of racists
you could
possibly find?
You're dragging me halfway
across the country for 40 grand.
That's a business plan?
[ Coughs ]
This car's shot.
I'll call Cooper.
No.
What?
Why not?
If the Feds take Putnum in,
I don't get my 40 grand.
Are you kidding me?
I'm an FBI agent.
He's in my custody.
I'll make sure
you get your money.
If I give him to you,
you're gonna take him
to the nearest
FBI field office,
where he'll demand
an identity hearing
or fight extradition.
In either case--
He'll miss
his court date,
and you won't get
your money.
- Hey. Talk fast.
- [ Handcuffs rattle ]
Your smoking car's
like the Bat-Signal.
Those goons'll find us
any minute.
[ Gunshot ]
Next one
goes in your leg.
I'm not afraid
of you, Bub.
Do you even know why
you're turning me in, hmm?
To stand trial for embezzling
from my employer--
not the cartel--
from the carnival.
The Feds have no clue
the cartel's even involved.
Only reason they know anything
about the missing money
is because
of some random IRS audit,
but the truth is
gonna come out in court,
and I'm gonna
be killed in jail.
So how about you let me go,
I stay alive,
and when I'm home safe,
I'll write you a check
for the 40 grand?
Think that's a lot smarter
than whatever
you two geniuses
have planned.
Red: "Planned"?
[ Laughs ]
I don't have the foggiest idea
how to get you back.
That's what makes it fun--
the surprises.
Your carnival people,
your skinheads,
your mouth that
won't stop running.
So buckle up, Smokey,
because before this is over,
you and I are gonna
get to know each other better
than either of us
would like.
And my 40 grand--
I'm gonna enjoy earning
every damn penny.
Uncuff him.
♪
[ Engine humming ]
Putnum: I'm-- I'm-- I'm
getting dizzy.
I need to get
my blood sugar up.
I need-- I need
to get-- get some air.
[ Whispering ] Mind telling me
what's going on?
I don't know.
I feel pretty good.
Knock it off.
Rent money
and an adventure?
What are you up to?
I feel alive.
Zipping off in that car,
bullets flying.
What a thrill.
[ Chuckles ]
And the driving.
Dembe's always driving.
I should
do more driving.
I am sorry about your car,
however.
You can pretend to be
loving this all you want,
but I know the truth.
The truth is
you're scared.
Scared because
you've lost everything
and you don't know
how to get it back.
Good morning.
- Hmm.
- Cincinnati?
No, not yet.
I do have a funny joke about
Cincinnati, though.
A priest, a rabbi, and Pete Rose
walk into a casino and--
Orange juice!
I-I-I-I need a glass
of orange juice!
- Oh, stop it.
- Anybody?
- My-- My-- My-- My-- My blood sugar!
- Stop it!
I need it, I need it!
I'm-- I'm gonna be sick!
[ Country music playing ]
How is it?
Mmm.
It's delicious.
I'm sorry
I don't have any money.
I would've paid.
I'm just happy
you're happy.
I tried to tell you
I'm a diabetic.
Just eat your pie.
Please don't do this.
The cartel,
those skinheads,
they have people
on the inside.
You know
what will happen to me.
Yes.
I'm serious
about the money.
It's yours if you-- if you--
[ Cellphone rings ]
Oh, it's my boss.
Well, that's a sentence
I never expected to say.
- [ Cellphone beeps ]
- Maurice, great news.
We have Putnum is custody.
Fantastic.
Where are you?
Well, there was a slight
hiccup in our plans.
We'll be taking
the 2:00 PM Cardinal
out of Cincinnati.
Should arrive
with plenty of time
before the trial.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Cellphone speed-dialing ]
Just got a location
on Putnum.
Cincinnati Amtrak, next train
to Union Station, DC.
- [ Cellphone beeps ]
- Tad got a location.
[ Knock on door, door opens ]
Ressler:
You wanted to see me?
Shut the door.
Sit down.
- [ Door closes ]
- Something wrong?
You were at Laurel Hitchin's
home the day she passed.
Yeah, which I included
in my report.
I saw that.
But I noticed
you omitted the fact
that there was bad blood
between the two of you.
Well, I didn't see
how that was relevant.
In the weeks
before she died,
you stormed
into Hitchin's home,
shot one of her guards,
and accused her of murder.
In turn, she had
your badge taken away,
and now you're one of the
last people to see her alive.
And?
And you have nothing
to say about that?
No intel
on how she died?
I'm sorry, but what exactly
are you getting at?
I'm asking
if it's a coincidence
that the woman you despised
ended up dead
shortly after
you paid her a visit?
Well,
it sounds like it.
Either that or,
uh, karma.
♪
I see.
I had to ask.
That's all,
Agent Ressler.
[ Door opens, closes ]
♪
[ Cellphone speed-dialing ]
[ Door bangs ]
- Yes?
- Hey, it's me.
I think you and I
need to talk.
[ Train whistle blowing ]
Train's delayed
again.
Again?
How long?
Another hour.
We're gonna miss
the cut-off.
I'm gonna
find us a car.
To steal?
No.
No, you're not.
I'm sorry, my dear, were you
about to suggest something else?
Don't speak to me
like I'm a child.
Elizabeth, please keep an eye
on our fugitive.
Announcer: [ Over PA ] Second
train to arrive on Track 5.
Next is service to San Antonio.
All passengers...
He's your dad.
That's why you're helping him,
because he's your father.
Drink your coffee.
I saw you badging
our bus driver.
I couldn't
figure it out--
A cop with him?
Why?
I'm not helping him.
I'm bringing
a fugitive to justice.
I see.
You won't steal a car,
but you'll take me
to prison,
where I'm gonna
get killed?
I'm just doing this
by the book.
Hmm.
[ Cellphone speed-dialing ]
♪
I got to use the can.
No.
You think
I'm gonna try and run?
I'm not stupid.
I-- I just got
to take a leak.
Okay.
I'll hold it for you.
♪
[ Door handles rattles ]
[ Door bangs ]
[ Toilet flushes ]
♪
[ Water running ]
[ Door handle rattles ]
♪
[ Engine revs ]
[ Tires screech ]
♪
Hey!
FBI!
[ Doors close, tires screech ]
♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
They got him!
He's gone!
Putnum's gone!
- [ Through cellphone ]
- The truck had Texas plates.
I'm sending you everything
I got from the database
matching that criteria--
6'1", tattooed neck,
white supremacist
with known ties
to the Lone Star State.
He has
a "warrior rune" tattoo.
That could indicate
he did some time
- in federal prison.
- Okay, got it.
By the way, Mr. Cooper told us
about you and Mr. Reddington.
Most people are really happy
to have a lawyer in the family.
- You've got a master criminal.
- [ Red grunts ]
How cool is that?
Wait, this is the guy.
Okay.
Odin Neiland.
He did five years
at FCI Lewisburg
for distribution
of methamphetamines.
Wait, Liz,
hang on a second.
Okay, this guy has ties
to Roman LeMarc.
Okay, LeMarc runs
a neo-Nazi outfit
called
the Friedrich Brigade.
They are a ruthless,
Mafia-style crime syndicate
that smuggles drugs through
the federal prison system.
Reach out
to FBI headquarters.
Have them run
their contacts and sources
and see if they can't
get a location
- on this scumbag.
- [ Keyboard clacking ]
LeMarc had to have his people
listening in on us.
To the bondsman,
maybe?
It's the only way
they could have found us.
And as for Putnum,
if he's not dead yet,
he will be soon.
[ Engine starts, revs ]
- Let's go.
- Go where? What about Putnum?
I doubt he's dead, and I think
I know where to find him.
Get in.
♪
It's been a pleasure.
You're not
going anywhere,
not until you tell me
what's going on.
You left Hitchin's body
at the scene.
There's cops crawling
all over that place.
They'll discover she slipped
and fell and hit her head.
You're supposed
to be a fixer!
You were supposed
to make this go away!
Calm down,
Mr. Sturgeon.
[ Sighs ]
Laurel Hitchin was
the National Security Advisor.
She had enemies,
she had lots of them.
And because
of your brilliant plan,
you just triggered
a multi-agency investigation
into her death!
Mr. Sturgeon,
I don't care what kind
of scrutiny it draws,
because I'm very good
at what I do.
The evidence is gone,
every trace,
which means
you were never there.
So unless you go home
and suddenly grow a conscience,
this thing is over.
You're welcome.
Now, goodbye.
♪
[ Guns cock ]
Boys.
♪
Mr. Putnum,
go find your money.
♪
You, sit.
Mr. LeMarc, I understand you're upset.
You trusted a man to launder
your criminal nastiness,
and instead,
he absconded with it.
I'm here to make things right--
a proposal.
You get your money, and I get
the man who took your money.
[ Laughing ]
Now, why would I agree to that?
Because I have the guns.
[ Footsteps approach ]
♪
Take your money and go.
What? No.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to get involved
in your affairs,
so if you take your money
and leave,
you'll never
see me again.
And Mr. Putnum will not
be telling anyone--
the courts
or otherwise--
about the intricacies
of your business operations.
I'm his rabbi now.
- You're free to go.
- No, you're not.
Whoa, whoa.
What the hell's going on?
Mr. LeMarc
was just leaving.
And what if I tell you
I'm not leaving here
without both him
and my money?
I put a bullet in your head
and keep your money.
I said no.
Mr. LeMarc,
she won't shoot you,
but trust that I will.
On three.
- 1, 2--
- Don't touch that money!
♪
[ Chuckles ] Now, that's a
nasty look that takes practice.
You must have sisters.
You walk out that door,
I fire.
♪
Uhh!
[ "The Edge Of The World"
by Redeye playing ]
♪ I remember
you were a charmer ♪
♪ laughing as though ♪
Want to know
why I took the money?
No.
It's in my nature.
Back when I traveled
with the bigtop,
I liked to get a little
card game going after rap.
You know, stud, hi/lo,
Texas Hold 'Em.
My daddy, he was
a gambler like his daddy,
so, um,
I had to be careful.
It was four years ago,
I-I got into a game
with a few of LeMarc's boys.
Lost a lot of money
that night.
Lot of money.
That's how they got me.
LeMarc wanted me
to pay off my note,
asked me to find a way
to launder his money for him,
so I-- I did it,
but I wasn't never gonna
get out from under him.
That's why I was skimming
from his cartel.
To get out.
I should've known
all those years ago,
but just like my daddy,
I was a gambler.
No way to avoid
the family curse.
It's nature vs. nurture.
And nature wins
every time.
Our DNA is what it is.
♪ ah-ah-ah-ah, ah-ah-ah-ah-ah ♪
[ Gear shifts ]
[ Chuckles ]
I'll-- I'll-- I'll die
in there.
Don't do this.
Mr. Putnum,
I believe turning you in
is the right thing,
the legal thing.
Do you agree,
Elizabeth?
Yes,
it's the right thing to do.
You have 45 minutes before
I have to be at the courthouse.
C-Can you at least let me call
Tammy Lynn and say goodbye?
Right there.
[ Dialing ]
For a moment there,
I didn't think
we were gonna make it.
I never should've
let LeMarc go.
Red: You weren't willing to shoot
an unarmed man in the back.
I think that's something
to admire, not regret.
LeMarc's the real bad guy
in this.
If we had him,
Putnum could agree
to testify against LeMarc,
get leniency,
stand a chance.
I'm not defending
what he did,
but he's only
in this situation because--
Because of his father?
Perhaps.
Or perhaps it's the dumb luck
of a gambler.
He just wanted to get away from
the criminal in his life.
Can't blame him
for that.
- [ Laughs ]
- [ Indistinct conversations ]
What the hell?
What happened?
What's going on?
A bomb-- They're saying there's
a bomb in the building.
♪
FBI!
Federal agent!
There's no treat.
This genius here called in
a 10-89 as a diversion
- to avoid a court hearing.
- [ Handcuffs click ]
I need you
to escort him.
He's got an appointment
with a judge in 40 minutes.
♪
So that's it?
Reddington takes you
on a grand adventure
to bring a carnival barker
to justice?
I know it sounds crazy
he would do something like this
to make ends meet,
but Putnum is now
in the US Marshals' custody,
and he is at trial
as we speak.
He did it for the money.
I owe you an apology.
Sir?
I've decided to disclose your
relationship with Reddington.
It's the right thing
to do.
I want to do
the right thing.
I'm sorry
for the personal scrutiny
that will likely result
from this--
the doubts,
suspicions of your loyalty,
which may rise again.
I'm not going
to sugarcoat it.
This is gonna
be a struggle.
But I have great
confidence in you,
confidence you'll make
the right decisions,
if you just stay
true to yourself.
[ "Run Run Run" by ChinChin
playing ]
♪
Got your bail money?
I did.
Thank you.
There's something
you should know.
You may be my father,
and I am going to help you
rebuild your empire,
because it will enable us
to catch criminals.
But I'm not gonna lose sight
of who I am in the process.
Please don't make me
return the car.
I've always secretly wanted
a Wagoneer.
It smells
like Dad's car.
Like peanut shells,
gasoline.
[ Laughs ]
Elizabeth, if it helps
to salve the wound,
we did bring
a fugitive to justice.
And a neo-Nazi is walking free,
and his cartel is thriving.
And as for Putnum,
the only way
he could get leniency
is if he returned
the money he embezzled,
but thanks to us,
he can't do that.
And his former partner,
Hawkins,
is being transported
from jail to the courthouse
and is going to testify
against Putnum,
and he will be found guilty,
and he will go to prison.
And there is no guarantee
LeMarc won't have him killed.
♪ I know you're scared,
but that's all right ♪
Oh.
♪ when you're living out here
in the wild ♪
_
[ Tires hiss ]
♪ when you're living out here
in the wild ♪
Hey, Morgan.
Chuck.
You have the package?
- Any trouble?
- Close call.
We passed the real transport van
on the highway.
Make sure the guard
gets his money.
And thank you, guys.
I'm in your debt.
♪ instinct's the only thing
that keeps us alive ♪
♪ take my hand and every step ♪
Who are you?
- Your Fairy Godmother.
- [ Van door closes ]
Your deal
with the prosecutor
got your sentence reduced
to four years.
With me,
it's reduced to none.
- [ Handcuffs rattling ]
- Care to hear more?
Yeah.
Judge: I've given the prosecution
several continuances.
And now your star witness
is nowhere to be found--
Your Honor, if I may,
it was contin--
No,
you have no witness.
The charges against
the defendant are dismissed.
- Mr. Putnum, you are free to go.
- [ Gavel bangs ]
♪ when you're living out here
in the wild ♪
That's what this
whole thing was about?
You had to get Putnum back
in order to draw Hawkins out,
which could only happen if
Putnum showed up to trial.
This whole thing was about
getting to the accountant.
That's half of it.
I'd be happy to explain,
but there is something
I need you to do for me first.
Agent Navabi and I...
we're, um...
- Dating?
- Yes.
And if, uh, that's gonna be
a problem, you know,
with the higher-ups, then, uh,
I'd be willing to--
[ Knock on door ]
Hey. You wanted to see us?
Aram,
it's not a problem.
What's going on?
I heard
from the medical examiner.
He's concluded Laurel Hitchin's
death was an accident.
Forensics pulled nothing
off the surveillance.
Evidently, it was as simple
as it sounds--
slipped and hit her head.
So that's it.
Case closed.
You may think you want
to be off the pool,
believe me, up and ba--
Smokey!
What the hell
is he doing here?
Nope.
No way in hell.
No way.
Eaz-I t-eaz-old y-eaz-ou i-eaz-f
I-eaz e-eaz-ver s-eaz-aw y-eaz-ou--
B-eaz-ack o-eaz-ff,
p-eal.
I-eaz'm i-eaz-n
n-eaz-o m-eaz-ood.
Okay, take a breath.
Let's celebrate.
Can a diabetic
drink wine?
- Dariush.
- Who has diabetes?
Well, you can't blame
a guy for trying.
Earlier today, you two were both
on your way to trial,
to prison,
and now, thanks to us,
you're both free.
Free to greet opportunity
knocking at your door.
- What?
- Opportunity?
Imagine owning 2%
in a multi-national conglomerate
with interests in travel,
beverage, technology,
cyber, defense, revolution,
with gross profits
that would be the envy
of most companies
in the Fortune 500.
Which-- Which-- Which
conglomerate is that?
Mine.
You live in a motel.
And LeMarc
is still out there.
I have every confidence
that the FBI is in the process
of finding whatever rock LeMarc
and his men are hiding under.
Well, we...
We-- We-- We-- We
don't know anything
about
your line of work.
Hawkins here
knows money laundering
like the Pope
knows the Bible.
And you, Smokey-- You know
everything there is to know
about logistics
and tactics.
It wasn't your fault
the greatest show on earth
went out of business.
That says more about lack
of vision than anything else.
And sure,
you're down on your luck
and you made some poor choices
that put a wedge between you,
but I removed
that wedge today.
And if you're as smart
as I know you two are,
you'll agree
to this proposal.
And together,
we'll take a wild ride.
[ "Don't You Forget About Me"
by Paul Stone playing ]
Yes?
More wine!
Help yourself to the pretzels
and the cheeses.
We're all family here.
- ♪ won't you come see about me ♪
- [ Chuckles ]
I was wrong.
You're not at all
scared of the future.
Oh, my gosh.
♪ giving me everything,
inside and out ♪
♪ don't you forget about me ♪
You're actually
loving this.
[ Laughs ]
♪ don't, don't, don't, don't ♪
♪ don't you forget about me ♪
♪ as you walk on by ♪
[ Laughs ]
♪ will you call my name? ♪
What are you doing here?
You shouldn't be here.
I was careful
not to be followed.
[ Sighs ]
The official report
came back.
ME ruled the death
an accident.
Which is why I'm here.
Yeah,
I couldn't help but wonder
how Reddington's security man,
Mr. Sturgeon, knew details
only the police
should know.
So I did a little
police work myself.
I ran your prints.
Turns out you're not
Mr. Sturgeon after all,
but rather Special Agent
Donald Ressler with the FBI.
What do you want?
I want you to know you're
gonna be doing me some favors
in the very near future.
Did you forget that
you got rid of the evidence
that I was even at
that crime scene?
I didn't get rid of it,
Agent Ressler.
I hid it.
Do what I ask, when I ask,
and it'll stay hidden.
- We'll be in touch.
- [ Car door opens ]
♪ lala, la-la, lala, la-la ♪
♪ la, la, la la, la, la-la-la ♪
- [ Laughter ]
- [ Speaking indistinctly ]
That was Cooper.
He's got a beat
on LeMarc and his crew,
and they should be in custody
within the hour.
So you get your bad guys,
and I get mine.
[ Door opens ]
Dembe.
Where have you been?
Do you want a drink?
Yes.
Thank you, Elizabeth.
How'd you do?
I couldn't find it.
Dembe, that suitcase...
♪
We need to find
that suitcase.
[ Hinges creak ]
[ Keys rattle ]
[ Lock clicks ]
Hey.
Don't shoot.
[ Gasps ]
You're back!
[ Laughs ]
Oh!
[ Grunts ]
How you doing?
Are you really here?
I really am.
God, I missed you.
I have some news.
You've got news?
I've got news.
It's about Reddington.
What about him?
He's my father.
He's your father?
I know, it's crazy.
Uh, but it explains
so much.
I mean, of course,
I'm confused about why he took
so long to tell me
and how I feel
about everything, but--
Wait a minute.
You're here.
[ Laughs ]
So, do you have
something to tell me?
I wanted to tell you that
I love you, Liz,
and that I'm never
gonna leave you,
ever again.
[ Gunfire ]
♪
[ Casing clinks ]
[ Gunshots ]
♪
You better not leave.
I'll kill you.
♪