Baltimore PD.
Come out, Stansbury. We got a warrant.
PARKER: We know you're here, Scottie.
Why don't you come on out,
make this easier?
[CLATTERING]
Ah, please. I... if you take me in
and my parole officer
finds out I've been using...
♪♪
W... what's going on?
I'm sorry, Scottie.
[GUNSHOTS]
♪♪
McGinnis!
[GUNSHOTS]
♪♪
What the hell happened?
I... I just...
He drew. He fired.
Is he...
He's dead.
You came in... what...
you had no choice.
You had to fire, right?
He had a gun.
Yeah, I had to fire.
♪♪
CHIEF: McGinnis.
Hey. Can you hear me?
Yes.
Chief, look, I got nothing to hide.
I'll wave my Garrity rights.
- I... I was following protocol.
- And I'm sure IA will confirm that,
but right now, I want you to go home
and call a lawyer.
You need a lawyer.
♪♪
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
♪♪
You sure nobody followed you?
Password to the account.
Funds are now available.
[SIGHS]
I didn't think it'd be this bad.
You're alive, Officer McGinnis.
Which is more than we can
say for Scottie Stansbury.
You've done your job.
Now let me do mine.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
_
♪♪
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
What's up, buttercup?
You finally change your mind,
decide to join me and Gary tonight
- in the hot tub?
- Yeah. Uh, tonight?
- Maybe.
- Is it the scab on his leg?
Oh, no, no, no! No, no, no!
Gary's...
Gary. I'm just distracted. I
locked myself out of my room.
I certainly don't want
to go down to the lobby.
- I was hoping I might use your phone.
- Oh, yes, of course, silly.
- Get in here.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
You coming to social hour tonight?
Gonna bring Daddy's
favorite little pickle-bites.
Piper, I have no idea what that means.
I spread cream cheese
on a slice of dried beef,
wrap it up real good around a dill.
Put a little toothpick
in 'em, real good.
Dariush! It's Bruno.
[CHUCKLING] I'm sorry.
I... I somehow locked
myself out of my room.
I was hoping...
Oh...
right. No. Oh, no, that's fine.
That would be gre... Wait.
[CHUCKLING] I found it now!
Never mind. I... Yeah, right here,
in my pocket of all places.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay. I'm sorry. Thank you.
I'll tell Gary we'll hot tub at 8:00.
- [OPENS DOOR]
- Don't forget the pickle-bites.
♪♪
_
[CELLPHONE BEEPS, DIALING]
♪♪
Dembe.
Yeah.
Did you get a plate number?
Okay.
Who is this guy anyways?
I mean, what kind of "medical expert"
agrees to help covertly
identify human remains?
I'm sorry. I didn't
realize he needed a résumé
and a urine sample to get the job.
You asked me for help,
I'm getting you help,
- and I'm breaking the law in the process.
- Yeah, for Liz.
Right. For Liz.
That worked out well last time.
He's a friend of yours, this Pete?
He has access to the kinds
of medical equipment you need.
[SIREN WAILING]
That guy?
Did he even go to medical school?
He was the smartest kid at
Harvard during my residency.
Then he sort of dropped out.
Today he's plugged in
to some kind of network
of criminal drug activities.
You two should get along swimmingly.
What up, Nikky? [SNIFFLES]
You got gray as Grandma.
- You must be...
- Tom.
Cool fake name. You a cop?
All right, you know what? Forget it.
- This isn't a joke, Pete.
- Yeah,
- well, I don't know your friend.
- You know what? It's my mistake.
- I barely know you.
- I never should've come to you
- I'm not going jail for someone I haven't seen
- ... for help in the first place...
- since med school.
- ... because this guy is not...
Shut the hell up, both of you.
He is not a cop.
And you are the smartest
guy I've ever met...
destroyed me in boards...
so I know you're smart enough
to run this DNA test,
take the money you clearly need,
and keep your mouth shut.
Look, those remains, if
they're damaged like you say...
exposed to air, natural elements...
then pulling DNA might be difficult.
I can do it... maybe...
but it's gonna take time.
Then I guess you should
stop talking and get to work.
♪♪
Dembe told me you
moved out of your hotel?
Sadly, my time at the
Terrace Vista has run out.
So, what, you're apartment hunting?
Yes.
While you go on a hunt
for some dirty cops.
- _
- I believe the unfortunate incident
with Officer McGinnis was far
more than the stuff of headlines.
I believe it was premeditated murder.
Says here the victim shot first.
I still have a few friends
among the men in blue.
They're whispering that
the scene was staged
by a well-compensated mercenary.
McGinnis... a paid-for killer.
But according to this
article, he has a clean record.
The perfect alibi...
an officer well-respected by his peers,
paid by your government
to carry a weapon
to protect and serve the citizenry.
But I'm telling you,
Officer McGinnis is a killer,
and he's not the only one.
Killer cops for hire?
Who's hiring them?
Whoever it is, this isn't
the first police shooting
they're responsible for...
and unless you find them,
it won't be the last.
LIZ: Andrew McGinnis.
He's a rookie officer without
a blemish on his record.
The victim was Scott Stansbury
who spent 20 years bouncing
between prison cells,
- parole hearings, and rehab.
- What about the pistol?
The one Reddington said was planted?
ARAM: It was registered to another owner
who reported it stolen three weeks ago,
Stansbury was never a suspect.
There's already an internal
investigation under way.
- Why not let it play out?
- IA could spend months filing those reports.
- More people could die by then.
- Look [SIGHS]
I know it's not politically correct
right now to say this, but, uh...
cops don't kill people,
they protect them.
COOPER: Most of them do.
But the ones who let anger and emotion,
prejudice and carelessness
affect their behavior
are every good cop's worst nightmare.
Keen, talk to McGinnis,
see if something feels off.
Ressler, pay a visit to the partner.
I want to get to the bottom of this.
♪♪
You kicked the door down even
though you got no response?
No, ma'am, we went in
because we had a warrant.
The guy violated parole
on a drug conviction.
- RESSLER: And when you got inside?
- Nothing.
It was... quiet.
Noise on the TV, I guess...
We split up.
Parker went one way. I went the other.
And that's where you saw him?
Right. He was dumpin' evidence...
dope probably... down the drain.
He saw me, pulled a gun.
... and next thing I hear, four shots.
He fired first. Two
shots. So I returned.
But his shots both missed.
Luckiest rookie
son-of-a-bitch I ever seen.
Which shot hit him?
Which shot?
He was hit once. You
said you fired twice.
I assume you remember which
missed and which didn't.
♪♪
He's dirty.
Why do you say that?
Said he shot twice and the
second shot hit him.
Well, that's odd,
it's always the second shot that
goes high, off the kick of the first.
Like I said...
he's dirty.
♪♪
Did you miss me, sweetheart?
Aw, that's nice.
- So nice.
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
I missed you, too.
Word to the not-so-wise...
[SHOTGUN COCKS]
When you come for someone,
don't show up in a rental car
under your own name
with a local address.
You never delivered the guns.
Two months Rivera is
fighting BLO without them.
Well, he won't get them if I'm dead.
By the by, what's with the boots?
You guys do a lot of riding?
♪♪
Our brothers are dying because of you.
They cannot defend themselves.
How many has Rivera sent for me?
Enough to get the job done.
Tell him that won't be necessary.
He'll have his guns within 36 hours.
♪♪
A shipment of guns? You have no guns.
Or money to buy them.
Or a plane to deliver them in.
This is impossible.
No, Dembe... that
periodontist from Tarkio?
She was impossible.
This is simply improbable.
I want to make my
client's position clear...
their son was unarmed when he was shot.
Tell that to the cop that he shot at.
A cop murdered our son!
- If that's what our investigation determines...
- [CELLPHONE VIBRATES]
... that officer may well go to prison.
- _
- MRS. STANSBURY: I'm sorry, Ms. Thrall,
- but there's something I need to say.
REBECCA: We discussed this.
This was our fault.
- LIZ: What was?
- All of it.
When Scottie was a little boy,
we didn't have money.
We moved to this dump of a place...
We didn't know about the lead paint.
It made him so sick.
The Stansburys lived in public housing.
- [CELLPHONE VIBRATES]
- The lead paint in their unit
left Scott cognitively impaired.
- _
- We sued and were awarded a structured settlement
worth a little under
half a million dollars.
- Structured settlement?
- Yes.
The money was supposed to
be disbursed over decades,
almost like a paycheck that would
show up every month for Scott.
But then Waterday showed up,
waving $100,000 in front of Scottie.
They offered a lump sum.
Yeah, 20 cents on the dollar.
Of course, he didn't see that.
He just saw a check for more
money than he ever dreamed of.
There ain't no way that my
boy shot at that officer.
- [CELLPHONE VIBRATES]
- But for him to even be in a position
where that is a question?
Mnh-mnh. No.
- _
- I blame Waterday for that.
I... I got to make a phone call.
- Waterday...
- [CELLPHONE BEEPS]
- ... tell me more about them.
- [RINGING]
- PRESCOTT: Took you long enough.
- I'm not your errand boy.
No. You're my indentured servant.
And you will be until you
repay the debt you owe me
for hiding your little mishap
with the National
Security Advisor's skull.
You got no play here.
You can't sell me out
without implicating yourself.
That's true. And maybe
I'm not willing to do that.
Or... maybe I'm bluffing.
Are you gonna call my
bluff, Agent Ressler,
or are you gonna go fetch me that car
before the cops process it?
Text me the, uh,
license and registration.
[WHISPERS] Hey.
What's going on?
Look, a friend of mine, uh...
he did something,
and instead of coming clean, he's just
digging himself a deeper hole.
And he needs you to dig himself out?
Something like that.
- [SIGHS] Okay, go. I got this.
- Thanks, Keen.
[WOMAN OVER P.A.] G2-8 to window R.
G2-8 to window R.
[COUGHS]
[SNIFFLES]
[MAN OVER P.A.] Attention...
Registration and insurance
is at room 443.
Room 443.
Registration and insurance...
- 443.
- [CHUCKLES]
83? Number 83?
Let's go, lamb chop. You're
not gettin' any younger.
RED: I think this is the first time
you've made it a priority to see me,
and I appreciate that. Thank you, Glen.
Truth is, you look sort of...
blue sitting out there all
alone in that stew of humanity.
Made my heart squeeze.
Your heart?
I like pokin' you in the
nose and watching you bristle,
but after all you been through...
it don't feel right.
The thrill is gone.
It's been...
unpredictable.
How are the mighty fallen
in the midst of battle!
I knew you would show
up sooner or later,
hat in hand, begging for
help from ol' Jellybean.
What do you need?
A million dollars.
Whoa!
Are you dickin' with me?
I'm a government employee.
I make 44 grand a year.
Of which you don't spend a cent.
You live with your
mother, and I'm confident
you've amassed quite a nice nest egg
from all your various
extracurricular activities.
Go ahead. Kiss the ring, sport.
I'm gonna need to hear the details.
I need a million cash.
Not to keep, to borrow.
For two days.
Glen, please,
this is important.
♪♪
Hey!
Who loves ya, baby?
LIZ: Waterday Financial buys a ton
of these structured settlements,
mostly from people like Scott Stansbury.
Yeah, people without the cognitive
ability to know they're being duped.
The lump sum Waterday
offers may be unseemly,
but it isn't a crime.
Other companies do this all the time.
Reddington said someone is
paying cops to commit murder.
Does the financial settlement
support that theory?
Well, maybe. Or...
uh, maybe it's just a
really odd coincidence.
But Waterday doesn't just
buy structured settlements,
they also make loans.
And some of the loans
they make are to cops.
And just last month,
one of the cops who had gotten a loan...
is Officer McGinnis.
LIZ: The same cop who
shot Scott Stansbury.
Are you telling me the same company
that bought the victim's settlement
loaned money to the cop who shot him?
That cannot be a coincidence.
Of course it's a coincidence.
Look, we're a nationwide company.
We made over 1,400 home
loans in the past fiscal year.
174 of them to cops.
And so this was bound to happen.
Is that what you're saying, Mr. Johnson?
Look, what we do matters.
To the officers who are
looking to buy a home,
and to the victims like
Scottie Stansbury who,
thanks to us, don't have
to wait for this money
to slowly drip in.
With the lump sum that we offer,
they can pay for college,
start a business.
We're gonna need to see the documents
pertaining to your
structured settlements
and the loans you made to the members
of the Baltimore Police Department.
Do you have a warrant?
- We can get one if you insist.
- I do insist,
- and you won't get one.
- And why is that?
Well, because to get one,
you'll need to convince a judge
what you think is going on here,
which is as obvious
as it is offensive...
a payoff to a cop to
get him to commit murder?
Is that what it was?
[SCOFFS] Okay.
See, the structured
settlements that we buy
only pay out as long
as the victim is alive.
Now, we paid Mr. Stansbury
$100,000 for his settlement.
At the time of his death,
we had recouped $62,000.
So, sure, someone may
have wanted him dead,
but not us.
His death cost us a fortune.
Jennifer, of course you're conflicted.
I mean, it's just... my
sister is sick, but...
- this really crosses a line.
- No.
I... It isn't only about the money
or paying for an operation
or even about saving your
sister's life. It's...
It's also about the victim.
His name is Robert
Urwiller, and he's suffering.
Robert is cognitively impaired
and no settlement amount
will ever make him whole.
His pain aside, look at his record.
The assaults,
the prison time.
Jennifer, when I vet these candidates,
I carefully consider everyone involved.
Statistics show
it's unlikely Robert will even
ever make his 45th birthday.
But you can let him go.
You can end his suffering,
and save your sister's
life in the process.
♪♪
You busted me out to
help you strategize.
And I'm telling you, we
need a covert landing strip
where these boys can
belly down a Gulfstream,
and that means a minimum of 500 meters
of well-camouflaged pavement
that ain't monitored by... by... by...
by radar or FAA.
He doesn't have the capital
- for a covert runway...
- Was I talking to you, gumdrop?
Smokey. Please.
Raymond. You're broke.
Now, I can promise you that this moron
will run his mouth
with harebrained ideas
as long as there's air in the room,
but none of those ideas are gonna float
if you can't pay for them.
And as your financial planner,
- I have a fiduciary obligation to point out that...
- Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, so... so the racketeer
who cut a deal with
the Feds for embezzling
- has a fiduciary obligation?
- Why don't you button your lip
and figure out where to park the plane?
- Oh, I got a place.
- Is that fact? Where?
Why don't you bend
over and I'll show you?
- Bend over?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Listen, you two need
to find a covert runway.
I don't care if you have to
build it yourselves, just find it
- and try not to kill each other in the process.
- [DOOR OPENS]
Tom. Right on cue.
Liz said you wanted to see me?
Yes. About a certain
business venture I'm pursuing.
I think you'd fit right in.
The AUSA agreed we don't
have enough to get a warrant.
ARAM: Yeah, a cop who had gotten
a loan from Waterday shot a man
who had gotten his
settlement bought by them.
And they lost money on the deal...
plus, we only have one example, but,
granted, that seems like one
more than anyone would need.
But since it wasn't, we
reviewed the class-action lawsuit
that Stansbury was a part of...
now, out of 179 plaintiffs,
four sold their settlements to Waterday.
Stansbury...
and these three...
My God.
Two were shot by police
after high-speed chases.
The other charged an
officer with a knife.
- Suicide by cop.
- And the cops...
they all got loans from Waterday?
Loans that, as far as we can tell,
they've never paid back.
LIZ: We don't know why,
but Waterday appears
- to be financing assassinations.
- COOPER: Get this to the AUSA.
Have them pull search
and arrest warrants.
And find Ressler. We
need all hands on deck.
LIZ: FBI. Step away from your desk.
- Who's in charge of your cybersecurity?
- I am.
Mr. Johnson's secretary.
Where's your boss?
♪♪
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
It's your office.
Rhona knows not to call me
unless it's an emergency.
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
Hey, what's up?
A... and they showed you a warrant?
And what did they take?
Um, you know what?
Forget it. I'm on my way in.
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
The FBI just raided the office.
Did you hear what I said? The Feds know.
They're pulling the files, Rebecca.
What? Rebecca. Come on!
Let me up. We're in trouble.
We?
They're pulling your
files from your office.
Wha... Wait. Wait. Wait,
wait, wait! Come on!
What are you... Rebecca!
Rebecca! Please!
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Raymond Reddington.
They said that you were out of the game.
Taken down by an old lady, no less.
Yes. And to think I've
always had such good fortune
with older women.
- Who's the boy?
- Levi Edwards.
My munitions man. He'll be
inspecting the merchandise.
Why should I make a deal with you, hmm?
Until today, you dismissed
me as a thick-necked sea lion.
I believe I said walrus.
I don't remember, I
was drunk at the time.
TOM: We're here for some guns.
.50 caliber, G3s, as discussed.
- You brought money as discussed?
- The money won't be a problem.
Money's always a problem.
I hear it may be your biggest problem.
Adika, I didn't come here to
waste my time or watch you eat.
You've been trying to get me to
kiss you into the business for years,
I'm here at your table to do just that,
so put down the fork...
♪♪
Where's the money?
I said it won't be a problem.
♪♪
This doesn't feel right.
You don't feel right.
On the contrary, I've never felt better.
Now put away the gun
before you do something you'll regret.
This feels like a setup. No?
GLEN: Okay, okay, I'm
here. I know I'm late.
Traffic was a bitch.
♪♪
Ohh!
Easy! I'm ticklish!
Who the hell is this?
Geynor Collins, TG&L Lending.
I'm the moneyman.
The one who makes the magic happen.
[SNIFFS] Ugh. What are you eating?
Smells like duck.
♪♪
RED: A million reasons for you to
have faith in my financial fortitude.
We'll need the merchandise
delivered by the end of day.
Leave the money.
I will make some calls.
Forgive the overt mistrust, but
I'm not going to hand you a penny
until Mr. Edwards has had a
chance to inspect the shipment.
No deal, then.
I need collateral.
♪♪
Then take Edwards.
If there's a bump in the
road, do with him as you wish.
Now get your merchandise in order.
I'll call you with a
rendezvous site shortly.
We can make this work.
I'll take your word for it.
Take him.
♪♪
Really?
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
♪♪
SMOKEY: Yes. I... I'm on
my way... 45 minutes tops.
Smokey, Buhari's plane is supposed
to land here in four hours.
If I were throwing a
picnic, it'd be lovely,
- but there are trees.
- The runway will be ready.
Tell that wizard the
McClintock boys are here!
Where the hell is he? We need
the shovels and chainsaws!
- Shovels and chainsaws.
- Tell her to button her lip. I...
I... I got shovels and chainsaws.
- Smokey, if this doesn't work...
- Mr. Reddington,
I need you to trust me on this.
We are going to belly
that gunrunner's plane
in that field, so help me God,
I just need 45 minutes to
get Leroy and Quackers there.
We'll jive then, my friend.
Who the hell are Leroy and Quackers?
ARAM: Based on the insurance records,
I think maybe I figured
out who the next target is.
- LIZ: Insurance records?
- Waterday's in the insurance business, too?
Oh, no, but they take out a ton of it.
Life-insurance policies on the lives
of the people whose
settlements they buy.
Johnson said the company
paid Stansbury $100,000,
but they had only received $62,000
when Stansbury died and the
settlement payment stopped.
That's true, Waterday
lost a few thousand
on the settlement payouts, but
they took out a $5 million
policy on Stansbury's life.
So when he died, they made a fortune.
Let me guess... they had policies
on the other victims, too.
- Isn't that a little obvious?
- Uh, yes and no.
First, Waterday had
policies on all of the people
whose structured settlements
they bought, not just the victims.
And second... the victims.
It looks like they pick ones who
are living on "borrowed time."
Cancer victims, addicts, people
whose illnesses may explain
the type of erratic
behavior that could result
- in a deadly altercation with the police.
- LIZ: And the next target...
you said you might know who that is.
Yes. Based on the three knowns...
the recipient of a
structured settlement,
a preexisting medical condition,
and a large insurance
policy on their life...
I found one name in
the Waterday database...
Robert Urwiller.
♪♪
Let me get two of them scratchers.
Might be my lucky day.
♪♪
[ELEPHANT TRUMPETS]
SMOKEY: Let's get that last
maple to the south pulled!
That oak, too!
Mikey and John, run a string line
and mow me some threshold markings.
Humberto, check our compaction
in the touchdown zone!
Chip-chop! Chip-chop-chip,
folks! Show time in 20!
[CHUCKLES] My land!
They don't make men like
that anymore, do they?
Thank the Lord.
♪♪
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪♪
- That's it, huh?
- Yep.
- Was it brought in like that?
- No idea. Sign here.
Thanks.
[CLANGING]
[CELLPHONE RINGING, BEEPS]
Ressler. Whatever
you're doing has to wait.
Sir. This situation has been handled.
Good, because we got a location
on the blacklister's next target.
♪♪
Ressler?
- Ressler, you there?
- I'm on my way.
♪♪
RED: Smokey, you were
born a century too late.
You're a miracle worker.
Heddie, I can't thank you enough
- for keeping us on budget.
- Oh, you had not budget.
- Well, there you are.
- [CHUCKLES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[MARC SCIBILIA'S "MY
TIME IS COMIN'" PLAYS]
♪♪
[JET ENGINES WHIRS]
♪ I've been waitin' ♪
- ♪ for the longest time ♪
- It's him.
This ought to be interesting.
Agent Keen, I've got Urwiller's
car heading east on Irving Street.
Do you have a vehicle description?
You are looking for a
1994 tan Toyota Tercel...
- which just made a left on Georgia.
- You still can't get him on his cell?
- I tried at least a dozen times...
- Trying again now.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
- ♪ Can't nobody save me ♪
- [SIREN CHIRPS]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
♪♪
♪ Devil, please
don't take me alive ♪
♪♪
♪ Ah, ooh ♪
Mr. Cooper, I just
spoke with Agent Ressler
and gave him Agent Keen's
10-20. He's en route as we speak.
- And Urwiller? You make contact?
- Uh, not yet, but we're still trying.
♪ Coming ♪
♪ Ah, ooh, yeah ♪
- [CELLPHONE RINGING]
- ♪ Ah, ooh, yeah ♪
- ♪ My time is coming, coming ♪
- [RINGING CONTINUES]
On my damn cellphone. Sorry.
- ♪ My time is coming, coming soon ♪
- License and registration, please.
- I'm sorry...
- License and registration.
♪♪
Aram, we have eyes. There's
a unit on scene now...
notify Annapolis Police and
get cars there right away.
Copy that.
- Whoa! What are you doing?!
- [SIREN WAILING]
♪ Ah, ooh, yeah ♪
- ♪ Ah, ooh, yeah ♪
- LIZ: FBI!
Drop your weapon!
Put the gun down. I'm
not gonna warn you again.
♪ My time is coming, coming ♪
♪ My time is coming, coming soon ♪
RED: Adika! How was your flight in?
ADIKA: Bumpy as hell. Are
you trying to kill us all?
Well, I picked the site
for its magnificent views.
- Levi, you look well.
- Any chance we can untie me?
Adika, I appreciate the good faith.
And if your merchandise
is as good as I hear,
there's no end to
what you and I could...
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- What is it?
- Shh.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
You hear that? There it is again.
I don't hear anything.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
A piping plover.
Their breeding grounds
are along coastal beaches
and alkali marshes, so...
to hear that bell-like call
from a shorebird this far inland...
my gosh, poor little fella must be lost.
Do you want to talk birds or guns?
- [PLOVER CHIRPING]
- [GUNFIRE]
- [CHIRPING STOPS]
- Impressive.
Not if you're a lonely little plover.
The other five crates are in the jet.
.50 caliber and 3Gs, as discussed.
Dembe, if you could please
grab Mr. Buhari's payment.
Levi, you look fit.
You can help me load the merchandise.
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
Adika, what the hell have you done?
- ATF!
- Everybody on the ground!
- ATF! Get on the ground!
- Let me see your hands!
I said hands! Get on the ground now!
I said don't move!
- Nice work, Chief.
- Hands!
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Nice ride.
Guy I was helping
out... it belongs to him.
Okay. Why are you driving it?
Turns out he killed a guy,
stuck him in the trunk.
I'm dumping the body for him.
Officer Serry won't talk.
Aram told me that the
Waterday CEO is dead.
But, more than likely,
he had an accomplice.
And, for all we know,
is soliciting more cops.
If we can get to Serry, we might
be able to put an end to this.
Mind if I take a run at her?
Why not... one crooked cop to the next?
Maybe you can bond over
the body in your trunk.
There's a body in the trunk?
Hurry up before it gets ripe!
I told her I wanted a lawyer.
I'm not answering any questions.
A Mongolian peasant
gets brought into an office,
where an important man offers him
a million dollars on one condition...
that he press the red
button on his desk.
And he tells the poor man that
if he presses the button,
an old man in Mongolia drops dead.
Now, he won't tell him why, only that
his death is good for the people.
So he pushes the button,
takes the money, and goes home.
But he's haunted by what he did.
He can't spend any of
the money, and eventually,
he commits suicide.
A man recently told me that story.
Said we all have a Mongolian
peasant in our lives...
something we've done
that we're ashamed of...
and that the minute someone
finds out what that is, well,
he can make you do anything.
Say anything. Confess to
anything. Either to cover it up...
or to atone.
She said the target was sick...
- She? Your contact was a woman?
- ... that he didn't have long to live...
that if I did it, I'd have
money to take care of my sister.
So I pushed the red button.
Do you have a name?
Some way to contact her?
- [CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Yes?
SERRY: I didn't do it.
- We had an agreement.
- I know. I just...
- I couldn't.
- Couldn't or wouldn't?
You know what?
There's still time.
I'm just not comfortable
talking on the phone.
- Can we meet somewhere?
- You want to meet?
Okay.
Where?
♪♪
TOM: You know, I told Liz that
I didn't want to do this...
that I wanted no part of it.
But she insisted that
we work things out.
Women.
And now we're going to prison.
I'm going away to prison because of you.
And the only saving grace is that
you will be even further away,
buried in the hold of a ship
somewhere in the Indian Ocean.
And Liz will finally be rid of you.
And here I was thinking she
had finally made peace with me.
She had...
because she's kind...
and decent and she sees
the best in people...
... even when she's being lied to.
You're certainly living proof of that.
I'm an open book compared to you.
I know you swear you never lie to her,
- but I know better.
- Do you now?
Yeah.
I do.
♪♪
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
It's her.
SWAT Commander, target is on site.
We move on my go.
♪♪
[GUNSHOTS]
Ah. Bulletproof glass.
Good to see you again, Ms. Thrall.
♪♪
If you're gonna leave me
locked up with someone,
perhaps it could be a
redhead with a nice smile
and a friendly demeanor.
- Who the hell is this guy?
- Sorry it took so long.
Once I knew Humberto
had your African friend
and his chums in transpo,
I stopped for some Bengay ointment.
Think I overdid it with my back.
RED: I use Epsom salt baths.
These guys work for you?
♪♪
I thought I was going to jail...
that I was never gonna
see my family again.
You're telling me this whole
thing was about getting some guns?
Not just guns.
A man needs to travel,
and when traveling,
- I like to stretch out a little.
- That Buhari thug could've killed me
- if this had gone wrong.
- Tom, if I wanted to get rid of you,
I'd put the bullet in your head myself.
However, you are
important to Elizabeth, so,
like it or not, you're important to me.
There's a piping plover
out here somewhere.
Have either of you heard it?
♪♪
COOPER: I understand you
stumbled your way into a new jet.
Yes! I can't wait to get airborne.
This is the longest I've
been grounded in some time.
But not to worry, Harold, it's
a two-for-one special this week...
you not only get Miss Rebecca Thrall,
you also get that
despicable African gunrunner
your agency has been hunting for years.
I need you to arrange for him
to be taken into FBI custody
directly from my people.
You still have people?
I make friends easily.
And this gunrunner. Buhari.
Did he happen to have any guns?
♪♪
Not this time.
- We mustn't look a gift horse in the mouth.
- ♪ It's where you live, ♪
♪ but you don't
know how it's built ♪
LIZ: I know he can be terrible
sometimes, but come on...
- elephants?
- [TOM SIGHS]
- That sounds at least amusing...
- Yeah, for him, maybe.
I... [SCOFFS] I was
taken hostage, all right?
He could've gotten me killed.
I cannot believe that
you are related to him.
[WHISPERING] Because he's a nutjob.
Nutjob or not, he is my father.
And I... I appreciate
you offering to help him.
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
- Means the world to me. Thanks.
- [CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Okay. They need me. Um...
- I'll see you in a bit.
- Okay.
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
- ♪ It lit me up ♪
- Nik.
McGee just called.
Said he was able to
extract DNA from a tooth.
Well, that's great. Nik...
♪ It lit me up ♪
♪♪
Thank you.
Look, just, uh... let me
know the minute you know more.
♪ Something's stirring in
a deep Atlantic trench ♪
♪♪
♪ Doesn't forget
the thousand years ♪
♪ Before it slept ♪
♪♪
- ♪ It's the beast, it's my heart, it's open ♪
- You know, Donald,
before I turned myself in to the FBI,
I held people like you
in extremely low regard.
Right back at you.
But I've found your determination
to do the right thing,
your genuine commitment
to the thin blue line
that separates order and innocence
from the likes of me to be...
quite admirable.
Why are you telling me this?
I want you to know
you can count on me...
if you ever find yourself
in as difficult position
as Officer McGinnis has put himself in.
Never gonna happen.
Nevertheless, my offer stands.
♪ It lit me up ♪
For the day I hope will never come.
♪♪
♪ It lit me up like a
rag soaked in gasoline ♪
♪ In the neck of a bottle
breaking right at my feet ♪
♪ It lit me up and I
burn from the inside out ♪
Who was he?
Who was who?
All you did was get
a car out of impound.
And you'll be getting your
next assignment real soon.
♪♪
- ♪ It was a good dream ♪
- [ENGINE STARTS]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
DEMBE: She's a nice plane, Raymond.
No fuel and no pilot,
but a plane of our own.
[SIGHS] I like it out here.
It's peaceful.
GLEN: I'm telling you...
the mosquitos out here
are the size of birds!
Agh!
Glen, you came for your money,
which has been returned in full...
and while I'm deeply
grateful for what you've done,
you're perfectly welcome to go.
Nah, I know what it's like
to feel alone, partner.
Ahh.
Denbee.
- Want another dog?
- No, thank you.
Well, I don't mind if I do.
♪ Moving on ♪
- ♪ Moving on ♪
- [FARTS]
[GROANS] Excuse me.
That's right... mosquitos or not,
I'm afraid we'll be sleeping
with the door to the jet
open tonight, boys.
- ♪ Many times I've been told ♪
- [GROANS]
♪ All this talk will make you old ♪
♪ So I close my eyes ♪
♪ Look behind ♪
♪ Moving on ♪
♪ So I close my eyes ♪
♪ Look behind ♪
♪ Moving on ♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -