Anything we do, he will
try to slow us down.
- As long as he exists, he will stop us.
- _
Today is the day I start
working at Evil Corp.
I can help them rebuild the database
and defend the fort at the same time.
This patch ensures that the UPS devices
will only run trusted code.
Bottom line, they won't be
able to blow up that building.
U.N. vote to annex the
Congo, it's as good as yours,
but this currency war must end.
Stage 2, I want it to happen
on the day of the U.N. vote.
Protesters have surrounded the building.
Summon as much NYPD as is necessary.
You know that telling
Elliot anything about this
would violate the
terms of your immunity?
I think I have a lead, but
I need to go at it alone.
I may have immunity, but
I'm gonna lose my brother.
- Stage 2 was never called off.
- How do we find them
and just end this once and for all?
The best lead we've got is me.
Irving, he says we'll
be ready to go on Monday.
We've prepared for an
emergency evacuation.
We have?
I'll have Elliot's access revoked.
I need you to fire Elliot Alderson.
Consider it done.
You okay?
- What's happening?
- Angela, why is he here?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Elliot saw everything.
I had to knock him out.
You're staying here this weekend.
We can't have anymore accidents.
He's gonna wake up again.
He only saw us for a few seconds.
Maybe he won't remember.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[WOMAN SPEAKING ON TV]
[STATIC TRANSMUTES,
ACCORDION MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUGHS, CLEARS THROAT]
♪ ♪
[YAWNS]
[CLICKING ON PHONE]
♪ ♪
Aller Anfang ist schwer.
Anfang ist anfang.
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
CHORUS: ♪ One, two, three four ♪
♪ One, two, three, four, five, six ♪
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Five, six, seven, eight ♪
[WOMAN SPEAKING ON TV]
♪ ♪
To relay to the Syrian President.
But Putin's stance is
that it would be a mistake
to abandon the current government.
Meanwhile, the U.N. Security
Council has gathered today
for a much talked about vote,
the People's Republic of
China's proposed annexation
of the Democratic Republic of the Congo.
As the world awaits
the result of the vote,
many questions are being raised:
- What does it mean...
- [PHONE BUZZING]
For the relationships
between world superpowers
and impoverished nations?
[PHONE BUZZING]
♪ ♪
CHORUS: ♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Five, six, seven, eight ♪
- [PHONE BUZZES]
- Elliot?
♪ ♪
[PHONE BUZZES]
Isn't that your phone?
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
- Is it?
- [BUZZING CONTINUES]
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[BUZZING CONTINUES]
Hello?
Finally, I've been trying
to reach you all weekend.
Are you at work?
- Yeah.
- Don't go anywhere.
We need to talk, in person.
Meet me downstairs.
I'll be there in ten.
Okay? It's... it's important.
Is everything okay?
- [ELEVATOR DINGS]
- Everything's fine.
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
Hey...
we should grab lunch later.
[SLOW CHIME MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
Something isn't right.
Like something slipped away from me.
What is it?
I can't put my finger on it.
What am I even doing here?
I'm arriving at work. I'm
walking toward my cubicle.
I'm just on autopilot,
running my routine.
Did my daily program crash?
When code runs, it should
run straight through
without interruption,
until all of its tasks
have been completed.
Unless something goes wrong.
A runtime error.
Sometimes, corrupted
memory can lead to one.
Is that what's happening to me right now?
A runtime error?
♪ ♪
Yo, what up, E?
I barely made it past those
protesters this morning.
I mean, the natives
are getting restless.
This shit's crazy AF, right?
Is it?
Hey, uh, so I had a
piece of tang this weekend
you are not gonna believe, dude.
I was unlocking
achievements Saturday night
that went all the way
through to Sunday morning.
I even impressed myself.
Every morning starts like this,
graphic sex talk.
Thankfully, I'm able
to tune most of it out.
When people talk like this,
they're either insecure,
or they're full of shame.
Which one do you think it is?
♪ ♪
I, uh...
Sorry.
♪ ♪
Shit. That was meant for you.
I'm really off today.
Uh... [SIGHS]... I mean...
Jesus, Elliot, I, um...
You know what, man? Fuck you.
I'm just trying to brighten up your day
with my dope-ass anecdotes,
but if you don't appreciate it,
I can just sit here in silence.
[CHUCKLES] Really?
Is this gonna end up being
a beautiful accident?
Mm, no... no, I'm...
I'm sorry, bro. I
shouldn't have said that.
Spoke too soon.
I'm bigger than this,
man, and, in a way,
what you just said actually helps me,
'cause I've always wondered
if people here thought I was
just trying to get attention,
but I was like, "Nah."
But I should've started the day off
by asking what you did this weekend.
He does raise a good question.
What did I do this weekend?
Instead I'm always just
rambling around some bullshit.
But you know what, I'm gonna
drop some truth on you, dude.
Since we're opening up here, I, uh...
I've only ever gotten laid twice.
Okay, actually, it was 1 1/2 times,
but the first time, it was...
It was one of those high-end
escorts, dude, a courtesan.
I saw her at the Plaza Hotel...
And actually, she saw me, dude.
She totally was hitting on me.
It cost me, like, two weeks' pay.
Oh, I know what I did this weekend.
I rehearsed my proposal.
I have a big meeting with
the VP of Technology.
I've actually never
had penetration, dude.
I've never penetrated.
I just... I... [SIGHS]
I went to one of those rub and tugs...
No, wait, I already had that meeting.
That was last week.
What happened this past weekend?
I just kept thinking she
was one of those girls
that got kidnapped and
was forced to do it.
I was, like, thinking of
her family the whole...
Hey, dude, thanks for
letting me confide in you.
Uh, just don't tell any of
the guys about this. Cool?
It's hard what he just did...
- [CHUCKLES] Yeah...
- Opening up face-to-face,
which is why I probably talk to you.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
♪ ♪
Why is my account locked out?
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[LINE RINGING]
E Corp Help Desk.
Hey, I got locked out of my account.
Can you do a password reset for me?
Can I have your employee number?
072391.
Please hold.
[CHEERY MUSIC PLAYS OVER PHONE]
[PHONE BUZZING]
My work email is prompting
me for a password.
Did someone try to get on the domain
as me too many times?
Or has E Corp locked me out?
Did they discover my shipping hack?
I need to check my monitoring server.
Hey, Samar...
Samar, I got locked out.
Can I hop on your machine to
check something real quick?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure, go for it.
Yeah...
Is this that bad feeling
I have looming over me?
Is this why today doesn't feel right?
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
An update failure.
No, this can't be happening.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Maybe something's wrong
with my dashboard.
- I need to check the full log.
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Shit. This morning at 6:07 a.m.,
the Dark Army tried to run Stage 2.
My patch stopped them, but
it doesn't change the fact
they're trying to blow up
the downtown building today.
Damn, dude, Bobbi from HR
is rolling up with Security.
Wonder who they're axing.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
Mr. Alderson, thank you for waiting.
I looked into this. It
looks like we cannot
restore your account at this time.
Is there anything else I can...
Samar is right. HR is firing someone.
Me. Fuck...
I can't leave the building
until I get back on a machine
and figure out how they're planning on
getting around my patch.
Samar, I need you to
distract them for me.
Wait, what?
Help me figure this out.
Do not leave me. Stay focused.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
♪ ♪
Excuse me, I had a question for you...
We're looking for Elliot Alderson.
Do you know where he is?
Oh, yeah, yeah, he's on floor 11.
You know, they have the best bathrooms,
and he likes to take his
morning dump around this time.
Samar, you need to be serious right now.
We have talked about these
micro-aggressions of yours.
I am being serious.
He told me he was
crowning his whole commute.
He was just here.
We need eyes on Elliot Alderson.
Elliot, I didn't know if you'd be here.
- Janet, I...
- Great news on your proposal.
Starting with the
Southwest region this week,
all paper records will
be digitized locally.
I tried to find you on
Friday. I... you weren't in.
I wanted to congratulate you in person.
Before we know it, the database...
Did you hear what she said?
I wasn't in Friday. Where was I?
When did my program halt?
Why can't I remember? Wait...
- Mr. Robot...
- Mr. what?
What day is it today?
You know it's gonna be a long week
if you gotta ask on a Monday.
Is everything all right?
Janet, I can't talk right now.
There's an I.T. emergency on 29.
♪ ♪
Last thing I remember
was the E Corp party.
That was four days ago.
Did Mr. Robot really
take over for that long?
[SYNTHS WHIRRING]
Don't look up. Security cameras.
[PHONE BUZZES]
That's right. Darlene. I remember now.
She was supposed to follow me... him.
You know what I fucking mean.
She must've seen Mr. Robot.
- Darlene...
- I can barely hear you.
It's a madhouse down here.
You were gone all weekend.
You left Flipper alone. I had
to give him to your landlord.
Listen to me. Did you follow me?
- Did you see him?
- Okay, just come downstairs.
I'm getting fired. I
can't leave until I've...
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Ma'am. Check the stairway.
Elliot? Elli...
I'm going to get him.
[DOORS OPENING]
All I know is it's
been six fucking weeks,
and I haven't had a weekend with my son.
[DISCORDANT SYNTH MUSIC]
I did trade the car.
I'm taking the subway. So what?
I'm picking him up from school today.
They cut my access privileges.
I completely disagree. I
think he definitely loves me.
Sir... Sir...
♪ ♪
Are you gonna really
get into that right now?
That was one time I
told him I hated him.
♪ ♪
I'm going to attract attention.
I have to remain calm.
- Take deep breaths.
- [ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
Be cool.
Don't panic.
Slow everything way down.
[AUDIO MODULATES]
Blend in.
Look bored, broken.
Get a blank office stare on my face.
This is how they do it, isn't it?
How they're able to watch the world
fall apart around them?
Because to them, this is normal.
It's all they know.
Maybe I can learn from them.
I wish I could see
myself through your eyes.
Don't you wish you could
see yourself through mine?
As we step through our
code, line by line,
debugging it to find the
cause of our runtime error.
What am I doing?
I'm still attracting attention.
I'll still get caught,
and it'll be painfully slow to watch.
- This isn't gonna work.
- [AUDIO SPEEDS UP]
We need to find an open
space, a network jack.
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
God damn it, it's the
start of the work week.
Monday morning attendance:
All of the conference rooms are booked,
and all of the cubicles are full.
I'll have to get someone
off their work station.
Here...
♪ ♪
She's the perfect candidate.
[SNIFFING]
♪ ♪
Hi, Edie, I'm Henry from I.T.
- Hello.
- We've detected you using
some unauthorized remote access software
to connect to your computer
work station from home.
Oh, my. That can't be true.
Don't worry, I'm just gonna
take a look at your machine
and perform an assessment
to make sure you don't have
an unauthorized desktop
sharing service installed.
Well, I'm gonna have to contest that.
I've hardened my install
further than the standard configuration,
including a restrictive
host base firewall rule set,
and whitelisting to block
unauthorized apps from running.
I might've chosen the wrong candidate.
I think I know your culprit, though.
Fred over there uses
GoToMyPC all the time.
Let me introduce you.
[KEYBOARD CLACKS]
♪ ♪
- Fred...
- [MUSIC PLAYS THROUGH EARPHONES]
♪ ♪
You loused it up again.
Hi, Fred.
- Henry from I.T.
- Are you serious?
You gotta take a look at my machine now?
I just got in.
Listen, I just need it for 15 minutes.
I'm... I'm backlogged here, man.
I got my supervisors
giving me deadlines.
This isn't a matter of debate.
♪ ♪
Whatever. I'll be in the break room.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
♪ ♪
Log data from the Dark
Army's back-doored machine.
♪ ♪
They're using this guy's
account: Frank Bowman.
He's a member of the code
signing architecture team.
This is what they're doing.
They wanna sign their own
firmware and bypass my patch.
If they do that, they'll blow up
the downtown recovery building.
My only chance to stop it
is to get to the hardware
security modules, the HSMs.
They're on the 23rd floor.
[FLUTTERING SYNTH MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[TENSE TONE]
[STAMMERS] No, I haven't seen him.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT MURMURING]
[AERY AMBIENT MUSIC]
- Did he just come in?
- [CLEARS THROAT]
♪ ♪
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
Hi. How are you?
One sec, I'm just finishing up an email.
♪ ♪
I think that you're in the wrong...
Almost finished.
All right...
Excuse me, very important memo.
We should get started.
I think you're in the wrong room.
I'm sorry, you are?
- Sean, head of Sales.
- Sean. Of course.
Dave Kennedy.
I work with Craig on the Q4 push.
I had longer hair then.
Listen, we're on a deadline.
We don't have time for this.
You are in the wrong room.
Well, maybe there's been some confusion,
either on your end or mine.
What room did you say this was?
44, 12C...
You know, I think that's my room.
[CHUCKLES] No.
All right, let me check my calendar.
Service has been spotty all morning.
All right, here it is.
Ah, you're right, so embarrassing.
Uh, I'm not supposed to be on 44, 12C.
Yeah, I'm down one floor,
43, 12C.
- [DERISIVE CHUCKLE]
- [CHUCKLES]
♪ ♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
I should've known.
We always have chocolate donuts too.
Oh, Jesus Christ,
you have wasted enough
of our time already.
We need to get started.
♪ ♪
You know, Sean,
sometimes I get a lot like you,
where you have a lot of anxiety,
because of a deadline,
you know, where you
feel pressure, because...
something has to get done.
And then, all of these damn little
unknown variables keep popping up.
♪ ♪
And when you find yourself
at the center of one of those storms,
man, you just gotta breathe.
Just let go.
Get it done.
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
♪ ♪
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Mr. Alderson!
Hey, stop!
Mr. Alderson, stop!
St...
Shit, I'm going through the lobby.
Security will force me out.
What should I do? What would you do?
That's right, you never answer me.
Is this why I created Mr. Robot?
To help me get out of
situations like this?
At least he interacts with me.
If Mr. Robot was here,
what would he do?
First thing he'd tell
you is to stop talking
to your imaginary friend.
You're not really him, though.
[CHUCKLES] Would you stop trying to be
so technical about everything?
You know if he were here,
he'd tell you exactly what he told you
when he said to walk away from Vera.
This is a zero-sum
game. Accept the truth.
That building is going to blow up,
and there's not a damn
thing you can do to stop it.
I'll find a way to destroy the HSMs.
Once I do that, there'll be no way
for the Dark Army to run Stage 2.
How are you gonna do that, huh?
You're about to be kicked out, Einstein.
So the real question is,
can you get to the HSMs before they do?
All I need to do is
get to the ground floor.
Once I'm there, I'll
find a way to get back in.
With the security they have?
I'll tailgate someone.
Hate to see it, kiddo,
but you'd have better luck
tailgating the parking
lot at a Yo-Yo Ma concert.
They got all their
peepers peeled for you.
- I know my way around.
- Even if you do get up there,
you got Bobbi and her
Keystone Cops looking for you.
You'll never get away with that.
And while you're busy
spinning your wheels,
trying to prove that
piece of wisdom wrong,
the recovery building's
going to explode,
and the people inside
right along with it.
He's right. I need to worry about
the people in the
building, not the HSMs.
But there is no he.
- That was just my imagination.
- [ELEVATOR DINGS]
We haven't seen each other in months.
We've been battling each
other in our own voids.
But at least now I know my next move.
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS,
INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CROWD CHANTING] This is
what democracy looks like!
Elliot Alderson, we've been instructed
to escort you off the premises.
Show me what democracy looks like!
ALL: This is what democracy looks like!
- [LINE RINGING]
- E Corp Recovery Center.
- How may I direct your call?
- Listen, there's gonna be
a buildup of hydrogen
in the data center.
Sir, I'm having trouble hearing you.
Would you like me to connect you...
You've gotta get everyone
out of the building now.
A spark will ignite the hydrogen
and bring the whole place down.
Have someone look at the battery room
for your UPS devices.
Sir, UPS?
We use E Shipping for our
freight services here.
Would you like me to transfer
you to the warehouse?
There's a fucking bomb in your building.
Clear everyone out now.
Hopefully that gives everyone
enough time to get out.
Now all I need to do
is find a way to...
Elliot!
You've gotta help me get back inside.
I have to tell you something.
There's a code signing machine on 23.
- We have to find a way to...
- I'm working with the FBI.
[TENSE TONE, RINGING]
[REVERBERATING] After Cisco,
when the FBI questioned me,
they did more than that.
They had everything
laid out on this board:
Us, Angela, Trenton, Mobley, everyone.
They had been following
our every move for months.
They knew everything.
And Tyrell, they think he's
at the center of it all.
Wait... wait a minute.
Back up.
[DARK PIANO MUSIC]
This... this has been
going on since Cisco?
♪ ♪
You've been working with them? The FBI?
Why didn't you tell me?
I made a deal for us.
- All they want is Tyrell.
- What?
What deal?
♪ ♪
Is that why you hacked me?
For them?
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
What's going on?
♪ ♪
Are you wearing a
fucking wire right now?
No.
No, they don't even know that I'm here.
Elliot, I'm telling you the truth.
The truth?
You've been working with
the FBI behind my back?
You've been spying on me?
Am I to blame for this?
Not telling her how
much I miss Mr. Robot?
How a part of me may have
let all of this happen?
The other night,
I followed you like you asked me to.
He snuck out of the
apartment around 2:00 a.m.,
and met up with Angela.
She knew it was him.
I think the two of them
have been working with...
Tyrell.
That's it.
- My runtime error.
- [ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
I saw her...
And him.
I was standing in a room...
- and they were together.
- Angela is the one behind this.
- I gotta stop her.
- Angela's been betraying you?
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
So have you.
♪ ♪
You kept this from me.
You've been trying to play
me this whole fucking time?
ALL: This is what democracy looks like!
Show me what democracy looks like!
[SIRENS BLARING]
- Four, three, two, one...
- We are live.
ALL: This is what democracy looks like!
Okay, we've live in five,
four, three..
Thanks, Jack. I'm here
outside E Corp headquarters,
and while it's typical
to see daily protesters,
it's unusual for the crowd to
be this size and this vocal.
An NYPD official told me
they're taking the
situation very seriously,
and sending in additional
units for crowd control.
What's less clear is why today.
With an all-time high
unemployment rate of 26%,
giving many citizens
something to march about,
most of the protesters I spoke with
did give me varying answers
as to why they're here.
From forced currency changes
to corporate greed and corruption,
I even had one gentlemen tell me
he was here to protest
this morning's U.N. vote,
that he felt it was
somehow connected to E Corp.
ALL: This is what democracy looks like!
Show me what democracy looks like!
Settle down!
ALL: This is what democracy looks like!
Everybody!
Settle down!
Everyone!
- Everyone...
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING, TEARGAS HISSING]
[GRUNTS]
[DRAMATIC PERCUSSIVE MUSIC]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTING]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
♪ ♪
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Scan your badge.
I said scan your badge now!
[MOUTHING WORDS]
[BEEPING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[WOMAN SPEAKING ON TV]
Tensions are running high,
as the United Nations vote approaches.
While no one can predict
whether today's resolution
will pass, all five permanent members,
China, France, the Russian federation,
the United Kingdom,
and the United States
must be in unanimous agreement
for the measure to be adopted.
CHORUS: ♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ One, two, three, four, five, six ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Five, six, seven, eight ♪
♪ One, two, three, four, five, six ♪
[ELEVATOR DINGS, DOOR OPENS]
[MELODIC COUNTING SPEEDS UP]
Yeah! Got it, whoo!
♪ ♪
- [GRUNTS]
- [SPRAY PAINT CAN HISSING]
[WOMAN SPEAKING OVER SPEAKER]
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from elevators and stereos
- until further notice.
- [SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
This is Angela.
- Blankenship.
- Mentor.
Walk toward the elevator
bank on your floor.
There's a package waiting for
you at the reception desk.
Has your name it.
There's something going on.
I don't think I can leave my office.
That's our distraction.
What do you mean your distraction?
Get moving.
- We don't have a lot of time.
- [EQUIPMENT SLAMS]
- [DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
- This is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
- What's going on?
- Ran into a bit of a snag.
We're gonna need you
to go ahead and have
Elliot implement our contingency plan.
Elliot?
What contingency plan?
He needs to get to a
computer called a, uh, HSM,
make a backup of it.
Once we get that, we'll be good to go.
Come on, let's go, let's go!
I got the package.
Good. Take the package to Elliot.
It contains all the hardware he'll need.
He'll pose as a member of
the internal audit team
based out of Detroit.
Everything he needs to know
is on a sheet of paper inside.
[ALARM CHIRRING]
[DISTORTED SYNTH MUSIC]
He'll get it done.
Call me when it's finished.
♪ ♪
[POUNDING ON DOOR, PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
- Please stay on your floor.
- [SHOUTING]
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from elevators
and stairwells...
[ELEVATOR DINGS, DOOR CLICKING]
♪ ♪
[BEEPING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
♪ ♪
[PHONE BUZZING]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
♪ ♪
Ma'am, what are you doing here?
It's not safe for you
to be on elevators.
I was, um...
I'm trying to get to my office on 23.
There's a secure room
and a safe zone on 23
with no windows. I'll take you there.
[MAN SPEAKING ON TV]
Okay. Thank you.
As no permanent members of
the council voted against it.
The draft resolution contained
in document S/2015/511
hereby passes,
allowing annexation
of the Congo by China.
I will now open the floor to
members that wish to extend...
[ELEVATOR RATTLES, ELECTRICITY DRONES]
This is Murphy. I'm on elevator 4.
We just lost power.
I'm stuck between floors 26 and 25.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Don't worry, they'll sort it out.
We'll be fine. What's in the package?
[CHUCKLES] Hopefully
it's something we can eat.
We may be here a while.
Hard drives.
Probably not the healthiest choice.
[ELEVATOR BUZZES, RUMBLES]
Here, let me help you with that.
Oh, no, it's okay.
- [GASPS]
- What the heck is this?
It belongs to my direct report.
He, uh... he ran out of a meeting
and left his badge in a conference room.
I'm bringing it back to him.
Interesting that your direct report
has special access and you don't.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
- [WOMAN WAILING]
- [GLASS SHATTERING]
You're gonna have to come with me.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from elevators and stairwells
until further notice.
I really should, uh,
head back to my office.
It's actually just right back there.
No, no, no, no, no, we're
gonna straighten this out.
Hey! Over here!
- [GASPS]
- [GRUNTS] Douchebag!
[SKULL CRACKING]
♪ ♪
- Hey, over here!
- Go, go, go!
[GRUNTS]
[BEEPING]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
♪ ♪
Attention, all E Corp employees.
This is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
- [BEEPING]
- Lock all doors,
and find the nearest safe zone.
Stay away from
elevators and stairwells
until further notice.
[SIRENS BLARING]
This is the police!
Do not attempt to cross the line.
[DISTORTED SYNTH MUSIC]
This is the police.
Do not attempt to cross the line.
♪ ♪
[CABINET CLICKING]
[CABINET SQUEAKS]
♪ ♪
[MUTTERS]
[RUMBLING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
♪ ♪
[SLOW STRING MUSIC]
Where's the USB key?
[PERCUSSION MUSIC BUILDS]
♪ ♪
[DOOR CLICKING]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[ALARM CHIRRING]
Attention, all E Corp employees...
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Oh, fuck... Come on, come on,
there's gotta be one
around here somewhere.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
♪ ♪
[BEEPING, DOOR OPENS]
- Hey.
- [GASPS]
Fuck, you scared the shit out of me.
Sorry.
Have you seen what
they're doing out there?
It's insane. Yeah, I know.
♪ ♪
You okay?
Yeah, I am now.
♪ ♪
Wait...
How did you get in here?
♪ ♪
I'm a part of the internal audit team,
out of Detroit.
Was in the middle of an unannounced
physical security audit
of the code signing operation.
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [SCREAMS] Oh...
- [SCREAMING]
- [GRUNTING]
[PEPPER SPRAY CAN HISSES]
Ah, you fucking bitch! [GRUNTS]
[PANTING] Oh...
[GROANING]
[COUGHING]
♪ ♪
Ah... [GASPS]
[BEEPING]
♪ ♪
[GASPING, SNIFFLING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
♪ ♪
[DISTORTED DRONING]
Oh, thank God.
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
Yeah...
♪ ♪
[EXHALES, SNIFFLES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪ ♪
[ELECTRICITY SQUEAKING, POPPING]
[ALARM CHIRRING]
♪ ♪
[DOOR RATTLING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[YELPS]
[EQUIPMENT SMASHING]
♪ ♪
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
[EQUIPMENT RATTLING, JANGLING]
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
[POUNDS, GLASS SHATTERS]
[COUGHING]
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
[EQUIPMENT SHUFFLING, RATTLING]
♪ ♪
[FLUTTERING SYNTH MUSIC]
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from elevators and stairwells
- until further notice.
- [EQUIPMENT RIPS]
Yeah!
[MUMBLING]
♪ ♪
[EQUIPMENT SCRAPING, RATTLING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [EQUIPMENT THUDDING]
♪ ♪
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[MAN SPEAKING ON TV]
[COUGHING, WHEEZES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
This great country didn't
start out with 50 states,
so why stop at 50 states?
And, let me add, that
this is why we need a man
with a business acumen like
Donald Trump as President.
If China makes another
move like they did today,
our standing as a world superpower
will be put into question.
Mr. Trump has the drive,
the ambition to help us...
- Marlinspike.
- Moxie.
It's done, but we got a problem.
I was made.
There was a woman in the CSAT room.
She saw me.
Wait, why were you in that
room instead of Elliot?
I couldn't find him.
What the hell are you talking about?
Your distraction is fucking overkill.
I couldn't find him in the
middle of a goddamn riot.
- Your men came after me.
- Well, they're not all ours.
Just 'cause we lit the fuse
doesn't mean we control the explosion.
You weren't supposed to
be on that floor anyway.
You said you wanted it done
immediately, so I got it done.
Uh-huh.
This woman who saw you,
did you get her name?
Lydia Riley.
♪ ♪
We'll take care of it.
So, you were able to follow everything
on that sheet of paper, huh?
[EERIE MUSIC]
Angela, if you didn't do
everything on that list...
Yes, yeah, I got it done.
Oh, good.
There's a delivery man waiting for you
at Reception on your floor.
Give him the package
with everything in it.
Irving?
Are you still gonna
evacuate the Recovery Center?
♪ ♪
That's been done already.
- So this is really happening?
- We need you to stay strong.
It's like you said,
she can make all of this better.
This is a step toward that.
Remember the cause.
♪ ♪
[BEEPING]
[EXHALES SLOWLY]
♪ ♪
[AUDIO MODULATES]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
♪ ♪
[ALARM CHIRRING]
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from elevators and stairwells
until further notice.
♪ ♪
[WOMAN SINGING FADES IN] ♪ Ah ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ ♪
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
[DISTRESSED BREATHING]
[SNIFFLES]
♪ ♪
[SHAKY BREATHING]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
- Angela...
- [GASPS SOFTLY]
Is there something you wanna tell me?
[ALARM CONTINUES CHIRRING]