I need you to keep an eye on
me... you're the only person
I can trust.
[CHANTING] This is what
democracy looks like!
Elliot, I'm working with the FBI.
You've been spying on me?
The other night, I followed you.
He snuck out and met up with Angela.
Stage 2... I want it to happen
on the day of the U.N. vote.
It's time Phillip
Price's hand got slapped.
This morning at 6:07 a.m.,
the Dark Army tried to run Stage 2.
They're trying to blow up
the downtown building today.
We need to get Tyrell
before it's too late.
[GUNSHOT]
My wife, my son, and I
will go to the Ukraine
- after the plan is complete.
- I'll get into that.
[GUNSHOT, BABY CRYING]
- Everybody...
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
This is a zero sum
game. Accept the truth.
The Recovery building's going to explode,
and the people inside
right along with it.
Angela's the one behind this.
I gotta stop her.
- I got it done.
- Oh, good.
Irving, are you still gonna
evacuate the Recovery center?
That's been done already.
I'm Emily Moss's daughter, Angela Moss.
I'm here to discuss the
Washington Township case.
- Dad, what's going on?
- I'll let you two talk.
26 employees died from
similar types of leukemia.
Evil Corp killed my mom,
and my whole life, I've
always wanted justice...
for her death.
[TENSE TONE]
[DARK AMBIENT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[MUSIC SWELLS]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[MUSIC CONTINUES ON TV]
♪ Tell me, doctor ♪
♪ Where are we going this time? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Is this the '50s? ♪
♪ Or 1999? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ All I wanted to do ♪
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
I think I've seen this one, yeah.
Elliot has these on VHS.
Is Elliot here, Mr. Alderson?
No, he didn't... He didn't come.
[BACKGROUND CHATTER]
Why?
Well, I guess he
wasn't feeling up to it.
I don't wanna be here, either.
There's a lot of nice people visiting.
Are you sure you don't
wanna join the party?
We got this cake.
Red Velvet.
- Not hungry.
- [CHUCKLES]
You know, if that were me over there,
I would want Elliot and Darlene
to come over and talk to me.
But I don't want to talk to her.
[SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[CHUCKLES]
You remember the, uh,
Enchantment Under the Sea dance
in the first "Back to the Future" movie?
Marty had to push his dad
to ask Lorraine to be his date.
And if George didn't overcome his fear,
they would never have gotten married,
and Marty would never have been born,
and he would've disappeared
from that photograph, right?
♪ ♪
I guess so.
[SIGHS]
I know it's scary,
but I also know that you can do it.
Just might need a
little push. That's all.
[CHUCKLES]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hey, Angela,
somewhere down the road,
if Elliot needs some help and...
I can't be there for him...
Just give him a little push too, okay?
Okay.
♪ ♪
- You understand?
- Of course, Emily.
Also, I know we discussed it before,
but I wouldn't be doing my job
if I didn't bring it up again.
It's about the anonymous
benefactor who keeps...
- I'll let you two talk.
- Don...
♪ ♪
Sorry, did I say
something I shouldn't have?
Not at all. You're fine.
Well, he reached out again,
offering to pay for your...
That's very nice of him,
but I've made my decision.
No more treatments.
I wanna spend what time I have left
with my friends and family.
Just know that there's still
people fighting for you,
for your family.
We're gonna continue with the lawsuit
and do everything we can in your name.
[SOFT, ANTICIPATORY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hey, you.
Hi.
What do you think of the party?
This isn't fun.
It's weird.
Weird how?
♪ ♪
It's okay. You can say it.
- I'm dying.
- I don't want to.
I hate this.
- I hate all of it.
- Angela...
you know this isn't good-bye, right?
No, I know what dying is.
You're never gonna see us again,
- not Dad, not me...
- Mm, no, listen,
I am always gonna be there for you,
no matter what.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
You wanna know what I believe?
♪ ♪
What?
That this isn't the end,
that there's another world
out there for both of us,
that we'll see each other again.
And we'll play and dance
and... bake and sing.
♪ ♪
Doesn't that sound beautiful?
[MUSIC BUILDS]
♪ ♪
Will you believe with me?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
[ALARM CHIRRING]
Angela...
Attention.
Is there something you wanna tell me?
This is an emergency...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I saw you.
The 23rd floor.
You were at the code signing machine.
What did you do?
We need to let today happen.
They're blowing up a building.
Yes, I know.
[DARK, INTENSE CHORDS]
And you're okay with that?
♪ ♪
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING]
How long have you been
working with Tyrell?
- What did he tell you?
- None of that matters
right now.
This whole time... I
thought you were helping me,
but you've been...
You've been manipulating me!
[DOORS OPEN, ANGRY CHATTER]
[MUTTERING, OVERLAPPING SHOUTING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
This is what you wanted.
After today, your revolution succeeds.
You just need the
courage to see it through.
You sound like him.
You, you mean.
♪ ♪
I need to stop this.
Today's work, what White Rose is doing,
is going to change
everything for the better.
You met White Rose?
[SOFTLY] What the fuck is happening?
She's going to save the
world, but we need to let her.
Save the world?
Angela, whatever White
Rose told you is a lie.
She's a fucking terrorist,
and if you let this happen...
Then we're going to look back
and see that these
consequences were necessary...
- People are going to die!
- No, they're going to be fine!
♪ ♪
Including your father and my mother.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You're not making any sense.
Angela...
[OMINOUS MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Listen to me.
Whatever you pulled off of that machine,
I need you to give it to me.
- Now.
- I can't.
- I don't have it anymore.
- Where is it?
Who did you give it to?
♪ ♪
Tell me what you know.
Where are they operating
from? Where's Tyrell?
♪ ♪
- Where the fuck is he?
- [WHIMPERS]
♪ ♪
I'm sorry, Mr. Alderson,
but are you even allowed
to be in this building?
I heard you were let go this morning.
[DARK, INTENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
BOTH: So much depends
upon a red wheelbarrow...
[EXHALES] Glazed with rain water...
BOTH: Beside the white chickens.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
♪ ♪
Should've put a wire on her.
- What did you say to him?
- What I had to.
Well, excuse me for doubting you,
but you never struck me as
a country-first type of gal.
- I don't like you very much.
- Ditto.
- What are you, six?
- [PHONE BUZZING]
[TENSE NOTES]
It's him.
♪ ♪
Pick it up.
Elliot, where are you? What's going on?
I texted you the address.
- Is that where Tyrell is?
- Yes.
We need confirmation.
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
Get the FBI there to stop him.
You gotta do it now.
Make him come to us. Find
out where he's headed.
- Where are you going?
- Just take care of Tyrell.
Push him. We can keep him safe.
Elliot, just please don't
do anything stupid, okay?
- Just come meet me...
- I gotta go.
Elliot, wait.
Everything I said this morning
and everything I've done...
I'm sorry.
Call ended. Got the location.
It's a restaurant
called Red Wheelbarrow.
Let's move.
Dom, you heard him. He
said the info was good.
Let's go.
What aren't you telling me?
Dom...
♪ ♪
[DOOR THUDS CLOSED]
Between the rioters
and the police at E Corp's headquarters,
I can't connect there.
I can't access my back-doored machine,
but I need to log in to that UPS,
or everything's fucked.
Fastest way of connecting
is to go into the
Recovery building myself.
I heard the conversation myself.
Our CHS has confirmation.
- So she had eyes on him?
- No, not exactly, but...
The intel seems credible, sir.
We gotta act before Wellick disappears
for another five months.
[DARK, EDGY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Here's what we'll do:
I'll put surveillance on the location
until we have visual confirmation.
Surveillance? Santiago,
the lead is solid.
This is coming from Darlene.
This is why we have her.
I can't move on the word of a CHS
who has basically, so
far, given us jack shit,
and then disappeared
on us for almost a week,
without so much as a word.
I need something more concrete.
If Wellick is there, we have time.
He's not going anywhere.
Before we send SWAT bashing down doors,
let me coordinate with S.O. teams
to get eyes on the place.
Ask the S.O. ASAC to
get aviation in the air.
We get confirmation, we go
in, we take down Wellick.
Dom...
we may only get one shot at this.
I wanna make sure we do it right.
♪ ♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
[INTENSE, DARK CHORDS]
♪ ♪
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[MUZAK VERSION OF "THE GIRL FROM IPANEMA"]
♪ ♪
I suppose congratulations are in order.
After all our tit-for-tat,
you finally got your U.N. vote.
Quite the frenetic day
for the 24-hour newshounds.
I wondered if you'd make it today,
given everything going on at E Corp.
An eventful morning indeed. [CHUCKLES]
But something told me I
shouldn't miss our little...
soirée,
not for the world.
Speaking of my dear little,
wounded E Corp,
I'll be expecting China to
sign that economic accord.
All will be done by end of day.
You have my word.
Oh... thank God that's settled.
- [GLASSES CLINK]
- For now, let's...
break from our usual brinksmanship.
No need to spoil this afternoon.
We both won, as intended.
It's time to drink and be merry.
Good point.
["GIRL FROM IPANEMA" CONTINUES]
♪ ♪
Another fine choice of venue by Sergey.
- Utterly tasteless.
- [CHUCKLES]
I passed that buffoon
of an owner in the lobby.
You're gonna take him up on his offer
- to go boating tomorrow?
- Oh, please, don't remind me.
Those swim trunks he
insists upon wearing,
a bit too snug...
and a bit too short, wouldn't you say?
Mm. I believe the appropriate
term is "hanging brain."
[BOTH LAUGH]
♪ ♪
Good.
["GIRL FROM IPANEMA" CONTINUES]
[PHONE BUZZES]
[BUZZING]
[OMINOUS NOTES]
Sir, it's about Mr. Wellick.
Our contact says his location
has been compromised.
Well, that doesn't change anything.
You know what to do.
♪ ♪
[OMINOUS SWELLING MUSIC]
Kill process:
when an unwanted process is running
and you need to terminate it.
I need to kill Stage 2
before it kills anyone else.
Wrap it up. False alarm.
We're outta here.
Back it up! Let's go.
False alarm, folks. It's
safe to go back to work.
What are they doing? What
about my bomb threat?
False alarm. Go ahead, go up.
[RESCUE RADIO CHATTER]
Why is everyone going back in?
Everything's fine. False alarm.
No, it's not safe.
You gotta get them out of there.
ESU swept the floor. All's clear.
Uh, it's, uh... [EXHALES]
It's... it's safe to go back to work.
[TENSE MUSIC]
I called in a bomb threat
with no bomb for them to find.
There's no tangible explosive.
They had no idea what
they were looking for.
- But I do.
- Folks, you need E Corp I.D.
to re-enter the building.
Please have them out
where we can see them.
[BEEPS]
Keep it moving. Keep it moving.
Have your badges out and ready.
Let's go. One at a time.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[WALKIE-TALKIE STATIC]
Can you give us a status
update on the seventh floor?
Seventh floor clear.
Heading back down to you.
[TENSE PERCUSSIVE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[BEEP, CLICK]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
I was right.
Angela helped them get around my patch
and sign their own
malware with a cloned HSM.
If I can roll it back, the clean version
will overwrite Tyrell
and Mr. Robot's malware
and buy me some time to
revoke the stolen keys.
♪ ♪
A couple of minutes, and we'll be...
[OMINOUS CHORDS]
Why can't I do this?
Why can't I start the restore?
♪ ♪
[GASPS] Ohh!
[STATIC BUZZING]
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[STIRRING ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
Names are Fattie, Fattina, and Georgie.
Georgie was named after my aunt.
Lovely woman. Fat fingers, though.
What the fuck is going on?
Anyway, it's nice to have
a customer flag me down.
Since 5/9, we haven't had
a whole lot of customers.
Hey... [KNOCKS ON SCREEN] Stop, stop.
What's the problem?
You told me Houston on Avenue A.
- When did I say that?
- 20 seconds ago.
Mr. Robot.
I lost time. We know that.
But how much did he take?
15 minutes. I can't spare 15 minutes.
Stop the goddamn car.
Pull over now!
[TIRES SCREECH, HEAD SMACKS]
♪ ♪
If the malware's already loaded,
hydrogen is filling up the
battery room right now.
There are too many factors
to predict when it's going to blow.
Could be two hours,
or it could explode at any second.
Why do we always cut these
things so damn close?
[PHONE BUZZES]
Agent DiPierro.
Tell me you have something, Dom.
I am sitting here,
fucking pins and needles,
losing my shit.
You know I can't share
any information, Darlene.
Have you heard anything
more from Elliot?
No, I've been trying to call him,
- but he's not answering.
- Unless you've got more intel
that can further this
case, I'm hanging up.
We gave you this lead.
You wouldn't have shit without us.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Don't think for a
second that I don't know
that you're keeping something from me.
Given what's at stake,
whoever you're protecting,
I sure as shit hope they're worth it.
♪ ♪
[CHEERY MUSIC PLAYING]
Wrong fucking day, girls.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[SLOW, REVERBERANT GUITAR MUSIC]
♪ ♪
You hungry?
Yeah, I could eat.
♪ ♪
No, I mean, do you wanna go get lunch?
I can get lunch if you wanna get lunch.
♪ ♪
I'd be up for it.
All right then, I guess
we're going to lunch.
[SLOW ROCK MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I don't understand.
Why is everyone leaving?
They should be monitoring the fallout.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Where are Joanna and my son?
What time is our flight to Kiev?
♪ ♪
What is this?
What's going on?
[SLOW CASCADING SYNTH MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Everything's gone.
Motherfucker.
Is Mr. Robot gaining control,
or am I losing control?
If he has the power to switch,
does that mean I do too?
Is this a matter of who
wants to win the most?
Yeah, I agree,
this is fucking confusing.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[BEEP, CLICK]
Your trip to the Ukraine,
it's not gonna work out
the way we discussed it.
♪ ♪
I've got 14 customers,
four cooks behind the line,
two girls working checkout.
No sign of Wellick.
We had a deal.
I... I found a solution.
You... you said you'd
bring my family to me.
- What's going on out front?
- I've got eyes on the door.
Nothing unusual there or nearby.
♪ ♪
You fucking promised!
The plan is happening because of me,
and this is how you repay me?
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
I'm afraid the situation
is more nuanced than that.
♪ ♪
Shit, there it is
again, his presence.
Do you feel it too?
♪ ♪
No, I need more time.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[MUZAK PLAYING]
♪ ♪
At least he didn't get too far this time.
Five minutes.
I'm narrowing the gap, but still,
this isn't one of our bullshit
- stalemate prison chess games.
- [BEEPS]
In this case, a stalemate
means Mr. Robot wins.
[TEARFULLY] So, this is it?
This is how it's going to end?
[WHIMPERING]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Bathroom's in use.
Make that 15 customers.
[EERIE PERCUSSIVE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Follow the instructions inside,
and then burn them.
Well, unless Tyrell's taking
a leak, what do you wanna do?
I'm gonna eat.
♪ ♪
You're not going to kill me?
Tyrell...
I'm sorry.
[TENSE BASS CHORDS]
[BEEPS, DOOR OPENS]
[PANTING]
♪ ♪
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Stay focused. Stay focused.
♪ ♪
The stronger I am, the
better chance I have of...
[STATIC BUZZES]
[ERRATIC WHIRRING]
♪ ♪
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Three more minutes gone.
Who knows how many I have to spare?
I'm running out of options.
Instead of fighting,
maybe it's time we talk.
♪ ♪
The soda fountain's behind you there.
Have a seat, and we'll call
your number when it's ready.
Oh, and here's our loyalty card.
Ten wheelbarrows punched,
and you get a free milkshake on us.
You know, I... I don't get to
this neighborhood too often.
How long have you been open?
A little over six weeks,
but if you're talking about
the grand opening special, that's over.
Just curious. Thanks, hon.
♪ ♪
[THUDDING, CLATTERING]
I guess he didn't like my note.
[SLOW CASCADING SYNTH MUSIC]
[GARBAGE CAN THUDS]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
I need to get to the battery room.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DOOR OPENS]
Enjoy your meal, ma'am.
♪ ♪
I got a worker exiting now, red apron.
Keep an eye on him.
10-4.
♪ ♪
Mom, it's me.
Listen, I don't have a lot of time.
I need you to stay home
for the rest of the day.
Don't go out.
♪ ♪
I'll ship you some
Ensure. Just don't go...
♪ ♪
I'll have it delivered today.
Yes, yes, they have
same-day delivery now.
I promise. Just stay home.
[STAMMERS]
I love you too.
[PHONE CLICKS]
So, I'm going to move in with
my oldest daughter, Louise.
We agreed it's best to pool
our resources these days,
but... [SIGHS]... I
don't wanna be a burden.
Don't think like that.
You know it's the best thing to do.
And it doesn't make sense for
you to be living all alone.
You're probably right.
And my... my ulcerated
colitis is kicking in again,
so it'd be nice to have family around,
you know, in case anything happens.
You can never be too safe.
Did you hear about the
melee at E Corp this morning?
The whole world's going
to hell in a hand basket.
Give me your purses, now!
- [WOMEN SCREAMING]
- Oh!
Give it!
[WOMEN WHIMPERING]
Ecoin wallet, where is it?
[SOBBING] Please, please don't hurt me!
Please!
The fuck you waiting on?
Hand over your purse!
[DARK, PERCUSSIVE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[PANS SIZZLING, UTENSILS CLINKING]
What's going on? What's in there?
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
There's a fire. I've got
smoke coming from the backroom.
I'm looking at the floor plan
now, and there is no backroom.
♪ ♪
Last time I ask bitch!
Do it!
Cred 22958 to Op Center.
Emergency transmission.
Go with your message, 22958.
I've got a fire coming from
Red Wheelbarrow restaurant,
1197 Broadway.
Notify ASAC Santiago and 5/9 task force
- of a possible Wellick sighting.
- Copy that.
♪ ♪
[DOOR RATTLING]
What are you doing? Give him your purse!
[GUN CLICKS]
Norm, I'm going in. Get
around to the backdoor now,
in case Tyrell's in
there and tries to run.
♪ ♪
[MECHANICAL DOOR HISSES]
You could've died.
No.
No one's gonna die.
[THUD]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[COUGHING]
[FOOTSTEPS THUDDING, WOOD CREAKING]
[TENSE, EERIE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[ITEMS CLATTER, PINGING]
[CRACKLING]
♪ ♪
[SHAKY BREATHING]
[CREAKS]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[CREAKING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
[DOOR RUMBLES, CREAKS]
[DOM BREATHING HARD]
The battery room has a halocarbon
fire suppression system.
If I can activate it,
it'll suck all the oxygen
out of the room in 30 seconds,
seal all the doors,
and create a vacuum,
making it impossible to
create any kind of spark,
- which would prevent...
- [STATIC]
[GRUNTING]
[STATIC TRANSMUTES]
[GROANING]
[STATIC SCRATCHING]
[DARK, INTENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[BEEPS]
[GROANS] The kill command.
Here I am, trying to use
it to stop this attack
while Mr. Robot is
trying to use it on me.
Does that just mean we
cancel each other out,
fighting so hard, we end
up standing in place?
Fuck that. I gotta keep moving.
♪ ♪
Dude, you okay?
[WHISPERS] Yeah.
You disobeyed a direct
order. I told you, flat out...
I already told you it was a site survey.
Report me if you want.
Then why am I standing
in a goddamn basement
- with the door kicked in?
- There were signs of a fire.
I did my job.
I'd do it again, if
given the opportunity.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Anything else?
All right.
Look...
despite your blatant
disregard for chain of command,
this was still a win.
Wellick was here.
The evidence ERT pulls
out of this shit hole
can only bring us
closer to capturing him.
Now, we've got task force
canvassing the tunnels.
If Tyrell is in there, we'll get him.
Why don't you head back to the office?
When the evidence comes in,
you start sorting through it.
[LOW BACKGROUND CHATTER]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
[POUNDING]
I can see your big ass eye. Open up.
- What do you want?
- Open the goddamn door.
♪ ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSICAL STING]
[ELLIOT BREATHING HARD]
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
- Small coffee, black.
- You got it.
I'm gonna head up to the office.
- You gonna be okay?
- I'll be up in a minute.
You fucked us,
bent us over the sink and went to town.
You're not making any sense.
We're on the same side.
[BEEPING]
- No... Fuck!
- [DOOR RATTLING]
Oh, come on, please! Fuck!
Fuck!
[DARK CHORDS]
[PHONE BUZZES]
I saw you
manipulating my brother,
turning his condition against him.
Taking down E Corp was
your plan. Remember?
[GROANING]
[INTENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hey... hey!
- [WOMEN SCREAMING]
- No! Stop the attack!
- You have to stop the attack!
- Get on the ground!
- Listen to me,
- you have to stop the attack!
- On the ground!
[GROWING COMMOTION]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
You're the ones who
dragged me into this.
We didn't ask you to
blow up a goddamn building
full of people.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
They're evacuating the building.
[DARK, PERCUSSIVE
MUSIC CONTINUES]
♪ ♪
It's gonna happen any second.
Please, listen to me, I can help you!
Let's go! Go, go, go!
Tell me why I shouldn't
call the FBI and turn you in.
What is it that you
really want, Darlene?
With all their paper
records consolidated there,
this is going to mark the
official end of E Corp.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Folks, get back! Please stop.
You can lie to yourself all you want...
But when you're alone at
night, this shit will haunt you.
Trust me on that.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
♪ ♪
- Move... move.
- You don't understand!
No, no, no, listen to me,
you have to stop the attack!
Now, I can have you
in handcuffs right now,
so I'm giving you one last chance.
Convince me not to.
♪ ♪
People are gonna die!
Stop the attack!
♪ ♪
Go ahead and turn me in.
What attack?
I know what I'm doing is right...
[PHONE ALARM BLARING]
♪ ♪
What attack?
[PHONE ALARMS BLARING]
♪ ♪
[STATIC]
[HINGES CREAKING]
Holy shit...
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
He did it.
[GAS HISSING]
♪ ♪
We did it.
So what now?
Am I forever in limbo,
not knowing which side I'm really on?
And what about Mr. Robot?
Does he now understand that
Tyrell and the Dark Army
have corrupted his alleged revolution?
Does he have any fight left?
[UPLIFTING MUSIC CONTINUES]
♪ ♪
If so, who's he gonna fight?
Them or me?
[SIRENS WAILING, COMMOTION]
[PHONE BUZZES]
There were no paper
records in the building,
and the Dark Army knew that,
so why did they try to go today?
What was White Rose's real plan?
♪ ♪
Does she know something I don't?
Does everybody know something I don't?
♪ ♪
[SIRENS WAILING]
Reports are still coming in
from across the country...
[STATIC SCRATCHES]
[HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
I fought so hard to protect
the New York facility
that I couldn't see the bigger picture.
It wasn't a single point of failure.
I was.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
In a series of seemingly
orchestrated strikes across the country,
a reported 71 buildings
owned by E Corp
exploded or caught fire.
There has been no official confirmation,
or even speculation, as to what caused
the explosions and fires to occur.
Officials with knowledge of the attacks
have stated that the death toll
is expected to be well
into the thousands.
Meanwhile, first responders
continue to fight fires
and sort through the rubble,
with the hope of finding survivors.
President Obama is scheduled to hold
an emergency press conference
later this afternoon
to address the American public.
As of now, no one has...