My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in Hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city,
but I couldn't honor that
commitment
and honor the promise I made
to the mother of my son,
so I asked the best man I know
to help.
His name is John Diggle,
and he is the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Pollard--
she's using last night's disaster
as a pretext to
introduce her
anti-vigilante legislation
to the council.
I am invoking chapter 9
of the city charter.
That will convert
councilwoman Pollard's bill
to a citywide
referendum.
What do you want?
To operate
without interference.
So you can keep
killing people?
You don't seem to know
that this is a war.
The Intel that you
gave me on my son Joe panned out,
so I'm heading
to Calgary.
Good luck, Slade.
Ms. Pollard.
Captain wanted you to
see the latest CompStat.
Thanks, Lieutenant.
Sniper!
Aah!
Officer down.
Code 3.
All units respond.
♪ Arrow 6x05 ♪
Deathstroke Returns
Original Air Date on November 9, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Well, I'm just glad
no one was seriously hurt.
How do you want
to handle this?
I'd like you to
issue a statement on my behalf.
On your behalf?
I have an old friend
in town
that needs my help,
and I might not be back
in the office
for a few hours.
Do we have any idea
who the shooter was targeting?
We're working on it.
Good. Um, be the mayor
until I get back.
For real?
No. It's
a figure of speech,
but j--just don't make any laws
while I'm out of the office, ok?
Fine.
And don't worry
about the shooter.
We're gonna nail
his ass.
I know you will.
Sorry.
That was work.
Don't apologize.
I appreciate
the meeting.
You helped me find my son.
Least I can is help
you find Joe.
He doesn't go
by that name anymore.
Changed his name?
It was his
mother's idea.
Her maiden name.
He goes by Kane now.
What happened
to him?
I tracked him
to Calgary,
but by then, he'd gone,
so I followed him
to Ibiza--heh--
and then Mombassa.
Mombassa?
The kid took
after his father.
While we were stuck
on Lian Yu,
he went out and joined
the Australian Intelligence Service.
Then a week ago
in Kasnia,
a mission
went south.
He was dealing in arms.
Some locals caught him.
Supposedly, he didn't
have a fair trial,
and now he's...
serving a life sentence
like a rat in a cage.
Ok, Slade.
What do you need?
I need you to help me
find my son.
Last we met,
you told me
that I couldn't live
in two worlds.
I'm not asking you
to come back in.
Strangely enough, what
I need is diplomacy,
which means I don't
want Green Arrow.
I need Oliver Queen.
For what?
Can I ask you
just to trust me
on this one, kid?
I've organized transport
to Kasnia.
Wheels up at 2200.
I'll understand
if you
don't want to join me...
But if you do,
I'll meet you out front
at 2100, ok, kid?
Ok. Bring the stuff over here.
Sorry.
Hey. Don't worry.
It's only tent poles.
It's not like we're gonna stick around
long enough to use them.
Why do you say that?
You're always leaving.
Can't believe we
even made it this far.
Listen. You know that I work
for Australian Airlines
and I have to travel,
but I promise you
this weekend
it's just about
you and me,
father and son
out in the wild.
Come on. Go find
some flat land
and pitch your tent.
Got him. Well, I didn't
get him-get him,
but I identified him.
- Identified who?
- Our sniper.
Thought your T-spheres
could track his visor.
Well, that was then.
This is apparently now.
He must have hacked
the tracer.
Or got a new visor.
It's not like they sell
them at Walmart, Felicity.
Guys, update time.
I think our vigilante's back in town.
He's the shooter?
I saw him coming out
of the sniper's nest.
CSU's here.
Don't know how much evidence
we'll be able
to pull.
Well, why don't
we work with what we have,
mainly the vigilante
seemed to be targeting
councilwoman Pollard.
"Seemed to be" being
the operative word.
Well, Pollard's the one
who's championing
the anti-vigilante bill.
Seems like a guy named
vigilante wouldn't like her much.
Yeah, but martyr her?
That would get this bill
passed faster than you
could say "obstruction."
If it passes,
I'm gonna have to consider
arresting myself.
Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
You're not SCPD.
No, he's not,
and this is not a federal case.
Still doesn't explain
what John Diggle,
who works personal security
for the mayor,
is doing
at a crime scene.
I have relevant
experience,
and the mayor thought
this could use a fresh set of eyes.
What type
of experience?
Sniper.
I don't recall reading that in
your military file.
I'm sorry.
Tell me again why
you're reviewing
my service jacket.
Mayor Queen didn't
mention he was under investigation.
Of course he did.
It has nothing to do with that.
But you've been
working with him
for the past
6 years,
which makes us
overdo for a chat.
I could wait for
a subpoena if you'd prefer.
No. I'm an open book.
Step into my office.
Uh-uh! Private
conversation.
Hey, William.
Hi.
How are those quadratic
equations going?
I hate them.
Yeah. Those were
the days.
Where's your dad?
In his room.
Ah. Do you remember
when our biggest problem in life
was solving
a quadratic equation?
Uh-uh. I mean, I never really worried
about them, but no.
Well, now we have metas
crashing bachelorette parties, so--wow.
Slade invited you
on a romantic getaway?
- Something like that.
- Where?
Don't say Aruba.
That's our spot.
Kasnia.
Wow!
His son is
in some trouble.
The kind of trouble you need
to get in more trouble to fix it?
Well, Slade says that
he has a diplomatic solution
that requires my name
and not me in a mask.
I'm worried that
if I don't go,
he'll take a more
aggressive approach.
So the empty bag,
is that second thoughts
or can't decide what
t-shirt to pack?
Because I'm out.
I made a promise
to my son,
and I'm out.
It sounds like you
made a promise to Slade, too.
You think I should go?
It's not like you're
going back to your old life.
I wanted you to tell me
not to go.
Look. Slade is not
my favorite person,
but, I mean, it's not
about Slade.
- It's about his son.
- Yeah.
If you don't go, you're just gonna beat
yourself up about it.
If--when it veers
from diplomacy
and I have to break
my promise to William,
I will beat myself up
over that, too.
Don't tell William
what you're doing.
- What?
- Spare him the details
of, you know,
Slade being...Slade
and tell him that
you're helping a friend.
He'll understand that.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
He's his father's son.
How long's
this flight?
It's about 12 hours.
Thanks for coming, kid.
Let's go get your boy.
SCPD!
Hey!
Stay down.
It's you.
Got your 911.
Is everything ok?
Look at her face.
That is not an ok face.
Dinah?
Vigilante
made another move
on councilwoman Pollard
tonight.
I almost got him.
It's cool, D.
We'll nail that bastard.
I hit him
with my cry.
I shattered
his visor,
and he--he took off
his mask.
I saw his face.
Can you I.D. him?
His name is
Vincent Sobel.
He's my old partner.
I'm sorry.
When you say partner,
do you mean partner,
or do you mean "partner"?
- Both.
- Now I'm confused.
Dinah, I thought you said
your partner died in the line.
He was shot in the head right
in front of me.
Ok. Well, I know you believe you saw
what you saw tonight,
but it was night
and probably dark.
It was him,
Felicity.
It was Vincent.
I know it.
I know it sounds
crazy.
Dinah, this doesn't
change anything.
We have to find him
before he hurts anyone else.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
Where are you
with, the, uh,
shell casing
John found?
The casing appears
to be magnetized.
- Bullets aren't magnetic.
- They can be if they're
stored in an environment
with a strong
magnetic field.
You think it's something
you can trace?
I like your optimism.
It's not optimism,
Felicity.
It's faith.
Dinah said that you
had a chat
with our FBI BFF.
Oh, yes.
She was tough,
but I pushed back
pretty hard.
Think we put
that to bed.
Good.
Hello?
Special agent Watson.
Yes. Sure. I can come by tomorrow.
No problem.
All right.
See you then.
Definitely not
put to bed.
So where's your
point of contact?
I don't know.
His name's Nylander.
Foreign associate of mine from back
in the service days.
He's a bit of a jackass
and never on time.
He's not
that bad.
Ha ha! Slade Wilson,
the Terminator.
I haven't heard
that name in a while.
See you're running
later than usual.
Yeah. I was
with a girl.
Forget about it.
Look at you.
Mirakuru did
you wonders, huh?
Oh, what? You're
not sensitive
about that skit,
are you?
You were quite
the madman, I hear.
You promised me something.
Did you bring it,
or did I waste my time
traveling 7,000 miles
for you to screw with me?
Truth be told,
I'm glad you got
your marbles back.
So who's this?
He's a friend of mine.
Don't worry about him.
With you,
I always worry.
This should work. Thank you.
That's it?
Just "thank you"?
No extravagant
dinner, no pints?
Maybe next time
when my son isn't rotting
in a third-world prison.
He's lucky to have
you as a father.
My son wouldn't be
in this mess
if anybody else was
his father.
Just be careful,
Kamrat.
Your boy was snooping
around some private-op mercenaries,
um, not so nice
guys.
Under certain circumstances,
I'm not so nice a guy.
Eh. Not so big
into decoration, are you?
I'm less enthusiastic
for people wasting my time.
Ok.
You're seeing
Oliver Queen again.
Yeah. These new
prescription glasses
are really working
wonders. Heh heh.
It was just a little...
FBI interrogation
humor, you know?
Your Mr. Queen's alibi
for certain evenings
where the Green Arrow
was active.
If you say so.
My point is are you
prepared to testify under oath
under the pains
and penalties of perjury
in support
of those alibis?
Yeah, absolutely.
100%. Super-ready.
Everything
all right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. I'm just late
for a coffee date,
so I'd like to...
- Go?
- Go.
Thank you.
This was pleasant.
I call this play
Liberty watch.
A famous American mayor
comes to small, war-torn Kasnia
to fight for the release of a man
who has been wrongfully accused.
That's very clever.
Like I said, it's
a diplomatic solution.
Well, Slade, still,
I don't think that
they're gonna free your son just because
I give them a photo op.
Well, the photo op
is just to gain entry.
Of course they'll need
a reason to release him,
and here are 50,000.
Assuming this works,
where do we meet?
When you pick up Joe,
go straight to the airport.
Here is an alias
passport for him
and tickets
for you both to London.
You're not
even gonna see him?
I need you to
promise me
that you won't tell
him I helped.
No. I'm not gonna lie
to your son.
It's better this way.
For him or for you?
Wait. Are you--
are you afraid that
he's gonna see you
as Deathstroke
and not the man you were,
the--the man I think
you are now?
I gave up my right
to be his father
when I stepped out
of the light into the shadows
and became
this monster.
Your son will forgive you
the way that my son
forgave me.
Joe knew that I was
coming to look for him,
so he contacted
his mother,
and she sent me
a message to stay away.
You got your
second chance, kid,
and I'm happy for you.
Some fathers aren't
that lucky.
So tell me this is not
the freshest fish
that somebody's
cooked for you.
I don't even like
fish.
Not all fish are
the same.
Trust me, kid.
Are you really
a pilot?
- Of course I am.
- Stop lying.
Why are you being
like this?
We never get
free trips.
My friend Nick's dad
flies for Ferris Air.
They get free trips
all the time.
Unfortunately, I work
for a cheaper airline
that doesn't allow
for free vacations.
Whatever.
I'm not hungry.
Don't walk too far.
This place used
to house MRI machines.
We're in
the right place.
That's all
that matters.
Hey, guys.
Sorry I'm late.
- How was it with Watson?
- Terrifying.
We knew she was planning
a case against Oliver,
but I'm starting to think her
net is widening to include us.
She hasn't contacted
me yet.
Wait. Why hasn't she?
How about we not
worry about this
while we're in the lair
of a psycho killer? Sorry.
Here.
There's enough ordnance here
for a small war.
You don't need this many bullets
for one councilwoman.
When you called Vince
a psycho killer,
you weren't wrong.
Mr. Queen.
Thank you for taking
the time.
It is not every day
I meet celebrity.
- I'm not famous.
- I saw you on news once.
You punched man
with camera. Heh.
Yeah. I sure did.
They also say you are quite good
with bow and arrow.
Oh, don't believe
everything that you see on TV.
Ok, ok.
I understand you're
with organization in hopes--
To request the release of one
of your prisoners--
Kane Wolfman.
I wish you'd come
earlier.
What are you doing
back here?
Where is my son?
Uh...There was
a--a fight
in the prison yard that
Joe tried to break up.
Someone pushed,
and he hit his head.
He's gone.
He never knew.
Never knew what?
That I loved him.
Sure he did, Slade.
I don't remember
the last time...
When I told him.
Well, you were
his father.
Trust me, he knew.
I should have come
with you to the prison.
I know it wouldn't
have made any difference,
but...at least I could
have seen him,
said good-bye.
We still can.
You can still
say good-bye.
Joe!
Good catch.
Come on. We're not
here to mope around.
Ha ha!
Excuse me.
Could you take a photo
of my son and I?
Sure.
- I'm Slade.
- Darryl. Nice to meet you.
- This is my son Joe.
- Hey, Joe.
Nice to meet you.
Come on.
Don't burn
yourself out, Dinah.
We need you for
the long haul, remember?
There is no long haul.
We're putting
this bastard down.
Dinah, this bastard was
your partner
and your boyfriend.
I don't need you to
remind me of that, thanks.
No, you don't need me
to remind you of that,
but you do need someone
to point out the fact
that perhaps a part of you
should be happy
to have him back.
John, when
Vince died, I did
my absolute best
to kill myself.
I became somebody I
didn't even recognize--
to avenge somebody
who I don't even
recognize anymore,
somebody who kills
innocent people.
You and Vince went
through something horrific.
You did some things
you regret.
Maybe there's a part of you
that's putting that on him.
John, he's
a psychopath.
Doesn't change the fact
that he's someone
who needs help, Dinah,
just like you did.
Sorry to interrupt,
but we've got two new problems.
Pollard's headed over to
do a sit-down at channel 52
to talk about
the anti-vigilante referendum.
Wait. No. That
station's not secure.
SCPD cannot
protect her there.
That's why I said
we've got a problem.
What's the second one?
Agent Watson
subpoenaed me.
I got to go, right?
Yeah. That's usually
what a subpoena means--
you have to go.
Well, I'm gonna
head to the news station,
see if I can give Pollard
some extra protection.
Dinah, if Vince
tries anything--
I know, John.
I've got it.
Mr. Queen, I was not
expecting a return visit.
Uh, warden, this
is Kane Wolfman's father.
He wishes to see
his son's body.
I am afraid that
won't be possible.
Why? You said
he passed only days ago.
- Yes, but--
- Warden, where's the body?
It is no longer
in my possession.
Then where is
my son's body?
Hey, hey.
Easy, easy.
He's lying.
Do you want me to contact
Liberty watch?
Do you want me to cause
an international incident?
Because I am prepared
to do both.
The situation is
complicated.
- Then uncomplicate it!
- Hey.
Trust me on this one.
Don't make
this man angry.
They are called
the Jackals,
the men your son
investigated.
When they discovered
his arrest,
which was merely him
being in wrong place at wrong time,
they broke into prison,
take him.
Why did they
take him?
Torture.
Your son is spy.
In his head, secrets
worth millions.
They threatened reprisal
on my family
if I spoke about it.
Slade, Slade.
When the Jackals
took my son,
they didn't count
on who his father was.
Ok. Every single person
in that line is I.D.ed twice.
You got it? I don't care
if it's your mother,
and I want two officers
at every emergency exit,
and I need somebody
to move this car.
Lieutenant Drake,
good to see you again.
All right.
We're nearly ready to move
on the news station.
Dinah's already
on site.
Coffee date.
E-mailing Oliver?
Yeah. I'm just sending
Oliver some info he asked me for,
you know, for his
adventures with Slade.
Are you having as much
trouble with Oliver
working with Slade
as I am?
No. I'm having
a lot more.
Rationally, I know that it
was the Mirakuru
that make him
a jerk, but...
But he wasn't
on Mirakuru
when he left us
on Lian Yu.
- Exactly.
- It's ironic that Oliver
has more honor than
the man he's helping.
"Ironic" isn't
the word I would use.
Guys, we got
a problem.
If I had a nickel
for every time I heard that--
Listen. I'm gonna
need you to stand down, ok?
Do not come here.
Dinah, we're not
standing down.
We're not leaving you
out there alone.
Well, I'm not alone.
Agent Watson is here,
and she brought friends.
She's hoping the Green Arrow
will show up.
Look. You guys
stay put, ok?
I got this.
I asked Felicity
for any Intel
she could find
on the Jackals.
She hacked the databases
of every major intelligence agency
in the world.
And what did she find?
Nothing. These guys
are ghosts.
Well, that's no help.
This is. Using
closed circuit cameras
in the prison
and surrounding areas,
she got their
escape route,
the license plates,
and then using
keyhole satellite
technology...
She tracked them
to one location.
- Yes, she's did.
- She's brilliant,
so how did you
get her?
Ask myself that
every day.
What's in there
for me?
Nothing. I promised you
your only part in this was talking.
Circumstances
have changed.
Not for you.
You've got your feet
planted in one world,
and you should
keep them there.
Slade, these Jackals are the best
of the worst,
all right?
They are
stone-cold killers.
What do you think
I am?
I think that you're
outnumbered,
and quite frankly,
I think that you're
out of practice,
and I am not letting
you do this alo--no.
Alone is what
I do best, kid.
Go ahead.
Tell me the truth.
Not bad.
Heh heh heh.
I have to go
to the bathroom.
I'll be back soon.
You are Xien Ming,
an agent
for the ministry of defense,
People's Republic.
I am looking for an agent
who you black bagged
called Yao Fei.
You have 10 seconds
to tell me where he is.
Purgatory.
Hey. He's with me.
Excuse me. He is with me.
Let him through.
You guys make sure
that perimeter is secure
over on the side there.
I thought I told you
to stand down.
Well, don't worry.
I left the hoodie at home.
Well, then what are
you doing here, John?
I told you I got it.
Then I realized
you're not exactly
in your right head.
My head is fine,
thank you.
Your little pep talk
really got through to me.
Dinah, you're
a lousy liar.
He didn't always
make bullets.
Vince. He used to make
this matchbox art
with a tiny, little
paper rose on the inside.
He made me one
the morning Sonos found out
we were undercover.
There is nothing left
of that man anymore, John.
Dinah, earlier this year when he
attacked Oliver's limo,
he had the chance
to kill you, and he didn't.
- Your point?
- My point is that maybe
there's something left
of the man you used to love.
If there isn't,
I'm gonna put him down,
and this time,
he'll stay dead.
Dinah, will you just--
You better get out of here
before Watson sees you.
3, 2...
Good evening.
I'm Jane Woods,
sitting tonight
with Ms. Emily Pollard.
Welcome,
councilwoman Pollard.
It's my pleasure.
Status?
Pretty quiet,
Lieutenant.
Place is locked
tight.
He's not getting
in here.
What we need is
legislation to deter
others from joining
this vigilante movement in the future.
We need to take
those vigilantes off the streets.
You don't think
they serve a role?
Cops serve that
role.
Department's been full
of corrupt cops in the past,
and on top of that,
we're short-handed.
All I know, Lieutenant,
is that if people
take the law
into their own hands,
we've got anarchy.
Don't move,
and it'll be quick.
Killing me won't
prevent the referendum from passing.
If anything, it will
make sure it does.
But there will be
one less corrupt politician.
Run!
Let's talk, Vince.
Just talk.
Freeze!
Get down on the floor!
You have 3 seconds.
Easy.
1...2...
Put the gun down.
3.
Call an ambulance.
Do it now!
Ugh.
How?
You're not the only one
dark matter did something to.
Everything heals now.
I thought you
were dead.
You let me believe it
for 4 years, Vince.
I'm sorry. I couldn't
let myself be--
Human?
Distracted.
Distracted?
From what?
My mission.
We were cops
for 10 years.
What did we ever
accomplish?
A lot.
Not enough,
not nearly enough.
This is
the only way.
You've lost
your mind.
I'm not the only one
wearing a mask.
The police are coming
and the FBI.
You should go.
Black Canary,
what's happening?
- We're getting reports that--
- Pollard's safe. She's secure.
What about vigilante?
He got away.
Ugh. Ohh.
Hey, buddy.
I just wanted to
check in.
Is this a bad time?
It's never a bad time.
Are you coming home?
As a matter of fact,
I am.
Good. I wish you were
here already.
Raisa's been making me
eat granola all weekend.
Heh. Raisa knows
her stuff.
Granola's good for you.
Were you able to
help your friend?
No, I wasn't.
I really hope he
finds his son.
Yeah. I do, too.
Is there anything else
you can do for him?
War.
Who's in charge?
Unh!
Stop it. Stop.
Damn it, Slade. You're going to
ruin my new shoes,
and I just bought
them, brother.
Nylander.
This man is a legend,
so no pulling
triggers...Yet.
Truce?
Let me explain.
I knew you'd been
involved, Nylander,
but you're too stupid to run this
organization.
So where's the boss?
You know, I had really
hoped prison
would be your dead end,
but no.
You just had to keep
on coming, didn't you?
We've got a great
thing going here, Slade,
lots of killing,
lots of money,
and your son,
what he knows...
Priceless.
You like burning Bridges.
Ha ha ha!
So says the man
who nearly burnt down
a whole city.
You're smarter
than that, Kamrat.
Where...is my son?
Why do you ask, hmm?
Do you wish to join him?
Did you have
a good time?
Yeah.
Just close this up.
Busy night.
Yeah. Guess we're lucky
you and your agents
were there to provide
backup.
Councilwoman Pollard
says she was saved
by the new Black Canary.
Hmm. Yeah,
I heard that.
Hell of a thing.
Pollard saved
by one of the vigilantes
she's gunning for.
From what I understand,
it didn't change
her position.
What about you?
Try to stay out
of politics.
No. I mean, where
were you tonight?
What do you mean?
I was right there.
Not when the lights
went out.
When it went dark,
you were gone,
and the Black Canary
was there.
You think I'm
the Black Canary?
I think a lot
of things,
but I focus on what
I can prove.
Have a good night.
Unh!
I'm curious, Slade.
What was your plan?
Kill us all and save
your boy?
Kind of reductive, no?
I like to keep
things simple.
Ahh. Things rarely
are, brother.
Well, this is.
I will join the Jackals
as long as you let
my boy go.
It's like
I said.
Things aren't
so simple.
We need your son.
After all,
he's our boss.
Hello, father.
It's been
a long time.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.