He was dealing in arms.
Some locals caught him.
Supposedly, he didn't
have a fair trial,
and now he's...
serving a life sentence
like a rat in a cage.
Ok, Slade.
What do you need?
I need you to help me
find my son.
Last we met,
you told me
that I couldn't live
in two worlds.
I'm not asking you
to come back in.
Strangely enough, what
I need is diplomacy,
which means I don't
want Green Arrow.
I need Oliver Queen.
For what?
Can I ask you
just to trust me
on this one, kid?
I've organized transport
to Kasnia.
Wheels up at 2200.
Slade: I'll understand
if you
don't want to join me...
But if you do,
I'll meet you out front
at 2100, ok, kid?
Ok. Bring the stuff over here.
Sorry.
Hey. Don't worry.
It's only tent poles.
It's not like we're gonna stick around
long enough to use them.
Why do you say that?
You're always leaving.
Can't believe we
even made it this far.
Listen. You know that I work
for Australian Airlines
and I have to travel,
but I promise you
this weekend
it's just about
you and me,
father and son
out in the wild.
Come on. Go find
some flat land
and pitch your tent.
Got him. Well, I didn't
get him-get him,
but I identified him.
- Identified who?
- Our sniper.
Thought your T-spheres
could track his visor.
Well, that was then.
This is apparently now.
He must have hacked
the tracer.
Or got a new visor.
It's not like they sell
them at Walmart, Felicity.
Guys, update time.
I think our vigilante's back in town.
He's the shooter?
I saw him coming out
of the sniper's nest.
CSU's here.
Don't know how much evidence
we'll be able
to pull.
Curtis: Well, why don't
we work with what we have,
mainly the vigilante
seemed to be targeting
councilwoman Pollard.
"Seemed to be" being
the operative word.
Well, Pollard's the one
who's championing
the anti-vigilante bill.
Seems like a guy named
vigilante wouldn't like her much.
John: Yeah, but martyr her?
That would get this bill
passed faster than you
could say "obstruction."
Dinah: If it passes,
I'm gonna have to consider
arresting myself.