who works personal security
for the mayor,
is doing
at a crime scene.
I have relevant
experience,
and the mayor thought
this could use a fresh set of eyes.
What type
of experience?
Sniper.
I don't recall reading that in
your military file.
I'm sorry.
Tell me again why
you're reviewing
my service jacket.
Mayor Queen didn't
mention he was under investigation.
Of course he did.
It has nothing to do with that.
But you've been
working with him
for the past
6 years,
which makes us
overdo for a chat.
I could wait for
a subpoena if you'd prefer.
No. I'm an open book.
Step into my office.
Uh-uh! Private
conversation.
Hey, William.
Hi.
How are those quadratic
equations going?
I hate them.
Yeah. Those were
the days.
Where's your dad?
In his room.
Ah. Do you remember
when our biggest problem in life
was solving
a quadratic equation?
Uh-uh. I mean, I never really worried
about them, but no.
Well, now we have metas
crashing bachelorette parties, so--wow.
Slade invited you
on a romantic getaway?
- Something like that.
- Where?
Don't say Aruba.
That's our spot.
Kasnia.
Wow!
His son is
in some trouble.
The kind of trouble you need
to get in more trouble to fix it?
Well, Slade says that
he has a diplomatic solution
that requires my name
and not me in a mask.
I'm worried that
if I don't go,
he'll take a more
aggressive approach.
So the empty bag,
is that second thoughts
or can't decide what
t-shirt to pack?
Because I'm out.
I made a promise
to my son,
and I'm out.
It sounds like you
made a promise to Slade, too.
You think I should go?
It's not like you're
going back to your old life.
I wanted you to tell me
not to go.
Look. Slade is not
my favorite person,
but, I mean, it's not
about Slade.
- It's about his son.
- Yeah.
If you don't go, you're just gonna beat
yourself up about it.
If--when it veers
from diplomacy
and I have to break
my promise to William,
I will beat myself up
over that, too.
Don't tell William
what you're doing.
- What?
- Spare him the details
of, you know,
Slade being...Slade
and tell him that
you're helping a friend.
He'll understand that.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
He's his father's son.