so I asked the best man I know
to help.
His name is John Diggle,
and he is the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Quentin: Pollard--
she's using last night's disaster
as a pretext to
introduce her
anti-vigilante legislation
to the council.
I am invoking chapter 9
of the city charter.
That will convert
councilwoman Pollard's bill
to a citywide
referendum.
What do you want?
To operate
without interference.
So you can keep
killing people?
You don't seem to know
that this is a war.
The Intel that you
gave me on my son Joe panned out,
so I'm heading
to Calgary.
Good luck, Slade.
Dinah: Ms. Pollard.
Captain wanted you to
see the latest CompStat.
Thanks, Lieutenant.
Sniper!
[Gunshot]
Aah!
[Gunfire, people screaming]
Officer down.
Code 3.
All units respond.
[Sirens]
♪ Arrow 6x05 ♪
Deathstroke Returns
Original Air Date on November 9, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Well, I'm just glad
no one was seriously hurt.
How do you want
to handle this?
I'd like you to
issue a statement on my behalf.
On your behalf?
I have an old friend
in town
that needs my help,
and I might not be back
in the office
for a few hours.
Do we have any idea
who the shooter was targeting?
We're working on it.
Good. Um, be the mayor
until I get back.
For real?
No. It's
a figure of speech,
but j--just don't make any laws
while I'm out of the office, ok?
Fine.
And don't worry
about the shooter.
We're gonna nail
his ass.
I know you will.
Sorry.
That was work.
Slade: Don't apologize.
I appreciate
the meeting.
You helped me find my son.
Least I can is help
you find Joe.
He doesn't go
by that name anymore.
Changed his name?
It was his
mother's idea.
Her maiden name.
He goes by Kane now.
What happened
to him?
I tracked him
to Calgary,
but by then, he'd gone,
so I followed him
to Ibiza--heh--
and then Mombassa.
Mombassa?
The kid took
after his father.
While we were stuck
on Lian Yu,