It's not optimism,
Felicity.
It's faith.
Dinah said that you
had a chat
with our FBI BFF.
Oh, yes.
She was tough,
but I pushed back
pretty hard.
Think we put
that to bed.
Good.
[Cell phone
vibrates and rings]
Hello?
Special agent Watson.
Yes. Sure. I can come by tomorrow.
No problem.
All right.
See you then.
Definitely not
put to bed.
So where's your
point of contact?
I don't know.
His name's Nylander.
Foreign associate of mine from back
in the service days.
He's a bit of a jackass
and never on time.
Man: He's not
that bad.
Ha ha! Slade Wilson,
the Terminator.
I haven't heard
that name in a while.
See you're running
later than usual.
Yeah. I was
with a girl.
Forget about it.
Look at you.
Mirakuru did
you wonders, huh?
Oh, what? You're
not sensitive
about that skit,
are you?
You were quite
the madman, I hear.
You promised me something.
Did you bring it,
or did I waste my time
traveling 7,000 miles
for you to screw with me?
Truth be told,
I'm glad you got
your marbles back.
So who's this?
He's a friend of mine.
Don't worry about him.
With you,
I always worry.
This should work. Thank you.
That's it?
Just "thank you"?
No extravagant
dinner, no pints?
Maybe next time
when my son isn't rotting
in a third-world prison.
He's lucky to have
you as a father.
My son wouldn't be
in this mess
if anybody else was
his father.
Just be careful,
Kamrat.
Your boy was snooping
around some private-op mercenaries,
um, not so nice
guys.
Under certain circumstances,
I'm not so nice a guy.
Eh. Not so big
into decoration, are you?
I'm less enthusiastic
for people wasting my time.
Ok.
You're seeing
Oliver Queen again.
Yeah. These new
prescription glasses
are really working
wonders. Heh heh.
It was just a little...
FBI interrogation
humor, you know?
Your Mr. Queen's alibi
for certain evenings
where the Green Arrow
was active.
If you say so.
My point is are you
prepared to testify under oath
under the pains
and penalties of perjury
in support
of those alibis?
Yeah, absolutely.
100%. Super-ready.
[Cell phone chimes
and vibrates]
Everything
all right?
Mm-hmm.