It's about 12 hours.
Thanks for coming, kid.
Let's go get your boy.
[Beep]
SCPD!
Hey!
[Canary cry]
Stay down.
It's you.
Got your 911.
Is everything ok?
Curtis: Look at her face.
That is not an ok face.
Dinah?
Vigilante
made another move
on councilwoman Pollard
tonight.
I almost got him.
Rene: It's cool, D.
We'll nail that bastard.
I hit him
with my cry.
I shattered
his visor,
and he--he took off
his mask.
I saw his face.
Can you I.D. him?
His name is
Vincent Sobel.
He's my old partner.
Curtis: I'm sorry.
When you say partner,
do you mean partner,
or do you mean "partner"?
- Both.
- Now I'm confused.
Dinah, I thought you said
your partner died in the line.
He was shot in the head right
in front of me.
[Gunshot]
[Dinah screaming]
[Canary cry]
Ok. Well, I know you believe you saw
what you saw tonight,
but it was night
and probably dark.
It was him,
Felicity.
It was Vincent.
I know it.
I know it sounds
crazy.
John: Dinah, this doesn't
change anything.
We have to find him
before he hurts anyone else.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
Where are you
with, the, uh,
shell casing
John found?
The casing appears
to be magnetized.
- Bullets aren't magnetic.
- They can be if they're
stored in an environment