How will we be remembered?
Will it be for saving the world twice?
Nope.
We're the team who broke time.
That's right.
History has been torn to shreds,
which means it's up to us
to put it back together
again piece by piece,
fixing these so-called Anachronisms
before we get torn to shreds.
So, please, don't call us heroes.
We're legends.
Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
I would kill you, but I'd
just be killing myself.
I want to break up Firestorm
so that you can you go home.
When do we start?
Please allow me to introduce
Madame Eleanor.
We have to stop Damien Darhk
from coming back to life.
Stop this abomination.
You're too late.
[WEAPONS CLATTERING]
[GRUNTS]
I remember everything.
Let's go.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- [SOFT ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
- _
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[GROANS]
♪ ♪
[YELPS]
[BICYCLE BELL RINGS]
♪ ♪
You. You there.
Yeah, you don't belong here.
You're supposed to be on Stage 12.
We're about to roll, and Mr.
Coleson's already in a real mood.
We already have one actress
gumming the works.
I can't have extras wandering off, too.
We should've been rolling
half an hour ago.
Where the hell's my star?
Ms. LaMarr is still in makeup.
You got to be kidding me.
How long does it take a tomato
like that to put her face on?
She's playing Helen of Troy,
not Marie Antoinette.
♪ ♪
[ROMANTIC MUSIC]
Holy cannoli, who is that?
♪ ♪
That's it.
That look right there.
Can you do that on cue?
[WIND WHOOSHES]
Forget Hedy...
This is our star.
What's your name, sweetheart?
I'm Helen.
Helen of Troy.
You are now, toots.
"The face that sold a million tickets."
All right, people, let's roll!
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
Oh, hey, Sara.
Sara, I've been searching
for more outliers
in the hopes of finding Darhk
and his witchy friend.
You think having a
supercomputer would helpful.
Watch yourself, Mr. Heywood.
Anyways, there's no sign
of them in the timeline.
What is that smell?
Okay, full disclosure,
I haven't left the library
in seven days, I think.
Is it Tuesday? I'm not really sure.
It's hard for me to keep track
of time in a temporal zone.
Shower. Now.
Okay. I'll shower after I find Darhk.
I know how much it means
to you to find him.
Look, we're gonna put Darhk
back in the ground
where he belongs, but not like this.
- Not like what?
- Not like Rip.
He lost perspective,
and he got his team killed.
I'm not going to be
that kind of captain.
But I am the kind
of captain that tells you
to clean yourself up.
Okay?
Aye, aye.
Thanks to your research, Marty,
the nanites I injected
into your bloodstreams
should be locking
onto your respective halves
of the Firestorm Matrix.
I'm only hoping that
the polymer I constructed
is strong enough to transfer...
your half...
from you to him.
Well, a little too much
"should" and "hoping"
for my comfort, but then...
What is science if not the
exploration of the unknown?
Ray, I'm telling you
right now, if you kill me,
I'm gonna haunt you forever.
Well, just remember, this was your idea.
If you guys are getting cold feet,
- we can call the whole thing off.
- Absolutely not.
We proceed with courage and confidence.
It's time for Jefferson to claim
the power of Firestorm for himself.
I appreciate that, man.
But come on, admit it, you're
gonna miss this a little.
- I mean, being a superhero, saving time.
- Not at all.
Were it not for this affliction,
my adventuring days would
be long behind me by now.
Time travel is a young man's game.
I'm eager to close this
chapter and embrace the next.
Well, let's set this old man free.
Uh, Ray, let's do it.
All right.
Here goes.
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[GRUNTS] Whoa. Hey,
what's... what's going on?
The system seems to be overheating.
There's too much power.
Shut... shut it down quickly.
[EXTINGUISHER HISSES]
Marty. Marty, you okay?
A little bruised, Doctor
Palmer, but I'll live.
- Wait, what?
- [GROANS] Everything...
hurts.
Whoa!
Look at my hands.
They're white.
And mine appear to be African-American.
You can just say "black," Grey.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
BOTH: You're me, and I'm you?
Oh, pancakes.
Attention, Legends.
Captain Lance requests
that all personnel
report to the bridge immediately.
I guess we know where
the explosion came from.
- What happened?
- Yes.
Pray tell, Dr. Palmer.
What exactly happened to us?
Because it seems we are in a
particularly precarious situation
that I, for one, have
no idea how to remedy.
- Why don't we just merge?
- Out of the question.
Absolutely not. We have switched bodies.
Who knows what else may have shifted?
Merging now could cause a meltdown
of insurmountable proportions.
We just... we just
can't afford the risk.
[LAUGHING]
You're the Professor,
and you're Jax.
[LAUGHS] Switched.
[DOOR OPENS]
Must be Tuesday.
What's going on?
Well, we seem to have a bit
of a "Freaky Friday" situation.
- I'm Jax.
- And I'm Martin.
Cool.
- So this is why we've been summoned?
- No, actually.
- Okay.
- Tell them.
[CLEARS THROAT] 1937,
Hollywood, California.
A beautiful woman mysteriously appeared
and threw the entire
film industry into chaos.
She apparently was so beautiful
that both Warner Brothers
and K&G Pictures went to war over her,
and it got ugly, fast.
Literal backs were stabbed. People died.
Those Hollywood idiots
probably had it coming.
Maybe, but this wasn't
supposed to happen,
so we are going to fix it.
It will be a nice, easy mission,
and we'll get our mojo back.
Awesome, maybe now I might actually
get to meet some celebrities.
And how would you even know?
The oldest movie you've ever watched
is some ridiculous farce
called "Police Academy."
Don't knock the "Academy," Grey.
Doesn't matter because you
two are a liability like this,
and you are staying on the ship.
- Wait, what?
- Oh, fantastic.
Gideon, plot a course for Tinseltown.
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- _
♪
You're sad.
Paris has gone off to fight Menelaus.
He may die.
How could you live with
yourself if you lost him?
[SOBS SOFTLY]
Cut!
That was aces!
Check the gate. Moving on.
- [BELL RINGS]
- All right, everybody. You heard the man.
Got a movie to make.
- Let's go, people!
- I got eyes on her.
All right, remember,
We're doing recon only.
Nobody moves on her.
Let's see what we're dealing with.
What can you tell us?
She's... really, really pretty.
[CLEARS THROAT] She looks familiar,
like I've seen her somewhere.
I'm sure she's never
heard that one before.
The gossip I'm hearing is that
this woman is seriously Method.
She hasn't broken character
since she got here.
I'm going in.
- Maybe I can talk to her.
- Negative. Recon only.
I don't want to spook
her. She's out of her time.
I am so sorry, miss.
- Are you all right?
- It's nothing. I'm fine.
Hey, watch what you're doing.
You almost took her head off.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, it's really nothing.
- Hey!
- Get lost, you twit.
- I asked the lady a question.
- She doesn't want to talk to you.
Oh, try stopping me, tough guy.
That escalated quickly.
W... what's going on?
- [MEN GRUNTING]
- There's only one woman in history
who has this effect on men.
[SCOFFS]
She really is Helen of Troy.
[BLOWS LANDING]
- She's on the move.
- Follow her.
[SIGHS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪
What's she doing now?
She's alone now.
She looks upset.
What are we waiting for? Let's grab her.
A kidnapping in broad daylight?
Even we shouldn't be so careless.
Jack... I mean Martin... is right.
We have to wait.
What the hell is going on here?
Where's Helen?
Well, find her! Now!
Z, you got incoming.
Studio boss is looking for his new face.
Yeah, so is someone else...
My, oh, my...
Now, the rumors I've been
hearing could not do you justice.
You really are something special.
The name's Eddie.
- Eddie Rothberg, K&G Pictures.
- I'm Helen.
That's right, honey. Don't do it.
Someone taught you not to get
into cars with strangers, right?
Hop in.
Or not.
[DOOR OPENS]
Rothberg. Helen! Wait!
Stop! Rothberg, you son of a bitch!
I'll kill you myself, you rat bastard!
[GUNSHOTS]
Aah!
♪
- Did that just happen?
- [SIGHS]
"Paris stole Helen from Menelaus.
And the war began..."
♪
I thought the Helen of Troy
story was just a myth.
Well, we've found that myths tend
to have some truth about them...
this one more than most.
Helen and her lover, Paris,
set off a ten-year war
that launched thousands of ships
and sent tens of thousands
of men off to their death,
all in the name of her beauty.
You make it sound like it's her fault.
Men always find a reason to fight.
- That's not on her.
- Depends.
- How hot is she?
- I mean, she's all right.
- [WHISPERING] She's really hot.
- Seems kind of little league, right?
I mean, what's the
big deal if this chick
gets to make a bunch of movies?
What's the big deal?
Helen is taking over the
classics like an infestation.
What's... what's "Casablanca"
without Ingrid Bergman?
The "Philadelphia Story"
without Katherine Hepburn?
It's... it's inconceivable.
And now this upstart
steals the career-making
role of Hedy LaMarr...
my boyhood crush.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Sorry, I'm still adjusting. Look...
I've seen the chaos that
she causes with my own eyes.
We need to get Helen
out of the movie business
before anybody else gets hurt.
Gideon, where's Helen now?
I checked the tabloid
archives, and it so happens
Edward Rothberg of K&G Pictures
is throwing a gala this afternoon
to show off his latest star.
Which would be the one
and only Helen of Troy.
Well, everybody go put your best digs on
because we are going to save Hollywood.
Yeah...
- until the Kardashians destroy it.
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
Finally, a positive side
effect to our predicament.
I'm absolutely giddy at the notion
of attending a 1930s Hollywood gala.
Maybe I'll rub elbows with Clark Gable
or dance with Ginger Rogers.
You have a little
extra fun for me, Grey.
I'm sitting this one out.
- W... why? What's... what's wrong?
- I'm wasted, man.
[SIGHS] My joints ache. I feel
like I'm walking under water,
and I have to use the
bathroom, like, all the time.
I assure you,
the moment we get Helen
back to her proper time,
we will fix this.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Damn, I look good.
[SWINGING JAZZ MUSIC]
[GIGGLES]
♪
[GROANS]
What's wrong? Are you all right?
Can we please go back in time and
murder whoever invented stockings?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- Any sign of Helen?
- No.
But Ray's becoming friends
with Cecil B. DeMille.
That is one remarkable mug, young man.
And you've never been in a picture?
Uh, no, not that I recall.
Well, I'm shooting one next month.
Cary Grant backed out,
but this profile of yours
- might just have him outdone.
- Huh.
Stick with me, and they'll
be saying "Cary who?"
Ray is ready for his close-up,
Mr. DeMille.
- There she is.
- You found Helen?
No. Hedy LaMarr.
The most beautiful woman in the world.
Not only is she a talented
actress, but she is a genius.
Brilliant and beautiful.
- I'd do her.
- Trust you, Mr. Rory,
to take something
precious and debase it.
She's also an inventor. Her
patent on frequency hopping alone
revolutionized the world.
Tuck in your shirt.
♪
Ms. LaMarr.
Uh, I just wanted to say I am
one of your biggest admirers.
You are a remarkable actress.
How would you know?
I haven't acted in any American films.
Now I probably never will.
I came here today to take one last shot
at making my dreams come
true and meet Mr. DeMille.
But the closest I'll get to Mr. DeMille
is transferring his
calls at Warner Brothers.
"Operator, how may I direct your call?"
But surely someone with your talent
will find work as an actress.
Tough luck finding work
when she's in the room.
Who?
[APPLAUSE]
♪
[SWEEPING ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
Any girl can look glamorous.
She just has to stand
still and look stupid.
Is everyone in position?
- [APPLAUSE]
- Yes.
Thank you.
♪
[APPLAUSE CONTINUES]
- Sandwich?
- Uh, no.
Ray? Nate?
Rory?
Holy Helen of Troy.
Yeah. That spells hot.
[BOTH SCOFF]
Guys, snap out of it.
We got a job to do.
Hey, check out her security detail.
- The woman's a prisoner.
- Not for long.
We just need to get her alone.
Z?
[GASPS] Oh.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Please excuse me.
- Of course.
Nice.
Ray, suit up and meet us at
the balcony for extraction.
Helen, you have to come with us.
You don't belong here, and you know it.
[CHUCKLES] You must be
from Warner Brothers.
Tell Arnold that I'm sorry,
but I left him for a better opportunity.
Oh, you actually are a good actress.
Yeah, I hear they have a
decent theater scene in Troy.
We should go check it out.
No.
No, the Gods have answered my
prayers by bringing me here.
This place is strange,
but I'm learning its rules.
And the first rule of Hollywood is...
never discuss business
without your agent present.
[SCOFFS] I guess she's
not just a pretty face.
Everybody get ready to
move. We got to go fast.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Helen, darling, why don't you
run along and find Mr. Rothberg?
[CHUCKLES] Gladly.
[KNIFE CLINKS]
[WHOOSHING]
- What the hell are you doing here?
- Aside from collecting my 15%?
You're her agent.
You know that I have the killer
instinct that this job requires.
♪
I didn't come here to fight.
[KNIFE CLATTERS]
I came to talk.
And I didn't come alone.
♪
If you don't take me up
on my offer for parlay,
things could get ugly for you,
your team, and Hollywood's elite.
♪
All right.
Everybody stand down. Darhk and
I have some catching up to do.
Thank you.
♪
Don't worry.
Poison is a coward's weapon.
And our conflict is
at a brief standstill.
_
You're from Zambesi?
And your powers...
Where do they come from?
I would have thought
you would have been able
to sense one of your own.
You're a totem bearer.
You wanted to talk, so talk.
Ah. You know for someone who died,
you don't appreciate the
simple things in life.
Me? I'm a changed man,
which is why I'm trying to
do this the civilized way.
- Do what?
- Convince you and your friends
to pack up and ship out.
You want Helen to stay.
What can I say? Anachronisms
are good for business.
- You wield the Water Totem.
- In a matter of speaking.
- The totem is now part of me.
- And you've perverted it.
Totem bearers must protect the innocent,
not use it for selfish gain.
You dare lecture me on selfishness?
You're the one who's turned
her back on her own people
in favor of these bungling idiots.
You know nothing about me.
You really do look lovely.
That color always suited you.
[GLASSES CLINK]
♪
- So are you an actor?
- Yes, um...
Well, maybe. My name's Ray.
- And...
- Haircut!
It's time to leave.
Didn't you hear us on the comms?
No, my... my comms aren't working.
Um, just ignore them.
They're being rude.
Let's get back to our
private conversation.
- [GROWLS]
- [WOMAN SCREAMS]
What are you doing?
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
- [GRUNTING]
- Get your mitts off me!
Unhand the lady!
[PEOPLE SCREAM]
Are you all right?
I am now.
[LAUGHING]
How convenient.
Here I was, thinking I was
going to have to convince you
what a mess your team makes of things
and that you'd all be better off
if you just went back
to your old lives...
which brings me to my offer.
I will let you all walk...
Unharmed, if you all leave now
and go back to 2017.
Or what?
Or...
I will kill your merry band of idiots
one-by-one, saving you for last.
And then you will die knowing
you could have saved them all
if you'd only made the right choice.
[SHOUTING CONTINUES]
♪
[SIGHS]
- What were you guys thinking?
- They weren't.
Like every man in the room, they
were just captivated by Helen.
Okay, in our defense,
she was very, very,
very... very attractive.
Yeah, I was just
admiring her personality.
So you jackasses decided to
impress her by having a fight?
- Wha... Mick started it.
- All right, enough finger pointing.
- We need to focus on the real issue here.
- Damien Darhk.
Wait, Darhk was there,
and you're still alive?
He didn't want to
fight. He wanted to talk.
And he made us an "offer."
We stop doing what we're doing.
No more Waverider. No
more fixing Anachronisms.
Wait, what does Darhk care
if we fix Anachronisms or not?
I don't know. We didn't have
time to get into his evil agenda.
Well, we've seen what Darhk
can do. Can we even fight him?
Yeah, especially now that he's walking
- with the time caddy and the water witch.
- She's not a witch.
Her name is Kuasa.
And she possesses one of
the lost totems of Zambesi.
- Kuasa...
- Darhk massacred those Time Bureau agents
in Victorian London without
even batting an eyelid.
What if we can't take them?
This might be our best offer.
You don't offer a deal unless
you want something in return.
Besides, if he lets us walk,
he's just going to
take us out one by one.
That's right. We're stronger
together. We know that.
Darhk knows that.
All right. Let's get Helen on the ship.
Nope.
After that party, you
three are grounded.
And I need you and the professor
to figure out why our
comms aren't working.
- You mean me and the professor?
- Whatever.
Uh, Amaya...
What's up?
Um, I just wanted to wish you
guys, uh, good luck out there.
Thank you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Not too shabby. As far as prisons go.
It's the same security
detail from the party.
I guess Helen's still inside.
You really think they'll
fall for this stunt?
Have men gotten smarter in
the past few thousand years?
- [CHUCKLES]
- Nope.
♪
[ENGINE ROARING]
[SCOFFS] Dude, this is impossible.
I can barely get my
hands inside this console,
let alone handle the wiring.
How am I supposed to fix
something if my fingers don't work?
It's called arthritis.
And just so you know,
I don't enjoy being inside you any
more than you enjoy being inside me.
- [LAUGHS]
- What did I...
- Don't be so puerile.
- Come on, Grey!
Don't pretend like you weren't having
the time of your life at that party.
I don't catch your meaning.
Telepathic link.
Let's just say I can tell
if you weren't married,
you and Ms. LaMarr would be
doing the nasty in the past-y.
Nasty in the...
I'll have you know that
Ms. LaMarr is my hall pass.
Clarissa gave you a freebie?
It was her idea. Something
to spice up our marriage.
She picked Jean-Claude Van Damme,
and thinking the whole
exercise ridiculous,
I chose Hedy LaMarr,
never thinking I'd
actually get the chance.
Why, 'cause she's dead?
She's not dead here, you dog.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
No deliveries tonight.
Really?
'Cause I got Mr. Rothberg's
prized horse back there.
Nothin' here about no horse.
Well, I don't know what to tell you.
[SIGHS] Fine.
Just gonna need to check the back.
♪
[DOOR UNLOCKS]
Oh, you mean his prize whores.
- Did he just call us...
- Yeah.
- Please don't scream.
- [GASPS]
She said "please." You gonna behave?
Please don't take me away.
I'm sorry, but this
isn't your home, Helen.
Do you have any idea what it's
like on the plains of Troy?
This land of Hollywood
is far from perfect,
but at least men aren't
killing one another in my name.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Not yet anyway. We got incoming.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- [GUNS COCKING]
- Rothberg!
You think you can poach my
talent, you no good son of a bitch!
I dare you to come at
me, you dumb bastard!
Why does this always
happen? I truly am cursed.
Hey, this isn't your fault,
but you can make it stop.
Come with us.
♪
Ugh, we can't let those
idiots kill each other.
Protect them. I'll
get Helen out of here.
♪
Hey!
What do you think you're
doing with Rothberg's girl?
Just renegotiating her deal.
♪
[ROARS]
Great Zeus.
They're warriors.
♪
Sorry, fellas.
Your new starlet decided
she's better off a free agent.
♪
This vessel... it's remarkable.
Wait till you see her fly.
Gideon, show her what you can do.
Gideon?
What's going on?
Have you figured it out yet?
Socket wrench, Grey.
Does this look like a
socket wrench to you?
I specialize in subatomic
particles, not...
- hand tools.
- That's obvious.
Anyway, it doesn't matter. Comms
weren't the only thing affected.
Half the ship's systems
are down... Aw, crap.
Please tell me we're not stuck in 1937.
Gideon and other vital
systems are offline.
How is that even possible?
Could be Damien Darhk.
What better way to catch us
than to shut down the Waverider?
It's like parts of the ship
are straight-up vanishing.
Of course they are, Jefferson,
because in this version of history,
those technologies no longer exist.
Wait, what are you talking about Jax?
I mean... Marty.
Can't you see? This is
all because of Hedy LaMarr.
As you know, Dr. Palmer,
technological advances are cumulative.
They build over time,
and it seems her patent...
Is the backbone for half
the Waverider's systems.
And without it, we're
essentially, well...
Screwed. Where's Hedy now?
She said she was starting a new job
as an operator for Warner Brothers.
Shouldn't be hard to get her
re-signed with Mr. Coleson
- now that his "It girl" is gone.
- Where are you going?
To get Ms. LaMarr's
career back on track.
You better not just be calling
in your hall pass, Grey.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
I don't want to
overstep, but may I ask...
What Gods gave you
such incredible powers?
Uh, the Gods didn't give us powers.
Well, maybe they kind
of did for Amaya and me,
but the captain's a self-made woman.
Sara trains every day.
She's a total badass.
- She's a captain, too?
- Yeah.
It gives me hope knowing
that you come from a time
where women have the
same opportunities as men.
Yeah, I wouldn't say that.
Anywhere must be better
than where I came from.
I spent the last five years
alone, locked up in a tower.
My only view was a distant
battle waging below...
men killing each other.
For what?
Me?
And now you want to send me
back to that hellish place.
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪
- [TELEPHONES RINGING]
- Warner Brothers, how may I direct your call?
Warner Brothers, please hold.
How may I help you? One moment, please.
Ms. LaMarr.
- What are you doing here?
- Mr. Coleson is in the commissary.
You have to talk to him
and get your contract back.
- Why do you care so much?
- [TELEPHONE RINGING]
Warner Brothers, how
may I direct your call?
There must be a better
way of switching signals.
There is. You're meant
for better things.
You have no idea the
adventures you'll miss out on
- if you don't follow me out that door.
- You're crazy.
Sometimes you have to be
if you want to burn bright.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪
[DOOR OPENS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
♪
Oh, no.
This is our lucky day.
Wait, you're that talent
agent from the party.
- Ms. LaMarr...
- [WHOOSHING]
Oh, I assure you...
I am something far more
ruthless than a Hollywood agent..
[WHISPERING] If that's possible.
Okay, I didn't actually think
you'd take me up on my offer,
but after my warning,
I thought you people
would at least use the buddy system.
But here you are, all alone,
without your better half
to give you at least a fighting chance.
[STRUGGLING] You and your
insufferable pontificating...
Wait, wait, wait, excuse me.
Either someone got
themselves a thesaurus, or...
[WHOOSHING]
He isn't who he appears to be.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
He's the old one.
No, no. [LAUGHING]
You guys switched bodies.
Oh, that is rich.
[LAUGHING]
- You need a minute?
- No, I'm good. I'm good.
[SIGHS] Let's kill them.
Grey's scared to death. I can feel it.
Darhk must have found him.
- We're going in.
- I'm coming with you.
You sure you're up for this, Jax?
- Save Grey? Damn right I am.
- You may want to pee first.
We're not gonna stop to
help you find a bathroom.
Good point.
Me too.
Just don't make it a deuce, Mick.
Yeah, and if you do, flush.
What did he mean about your other half?
- Are you married?
- Oh, you mean Jefferson.
Yes, I suppose in a
way we are married, too.
- It's hard to explain.
- You're a homosexual.
No, I'm one half of a
nuclear-powered superhero...
except the two of us
accidentally switched bodies.
They're here.
- I can feel them.
- Hide, hide.
What is going on?
The captain asked us to keep
you safe until the ship's fixed.
And the only way we can do
that is by saving Hedy LaMarr.
[CHUCKLING] I... don't
understand any of this.
That's okay. Time travel is...
It's very, very confusing.
With the power out, we're going to have
to lock the outside doors manually.
- Right.
- You're leaving me on my own?
Defenseless?
Here.
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
Now you're not defenseless.
♪
It appears they have us boxed in.
- On my signal, run.
- W... what about you?
Look, just focus on
getting yourself to safety
and don't give up on your dream.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [WHOOSHING]
- [CHOKING]
♪
Oh, goodie.
The cavalry has arrived.
Oh, how I missed those
whimsical outfits of yours.
Your beef is with me, Damien.
So let's fight. You and me...
League style.
Two swords...
zero magic.
A duel. How quaint.
- Grey!
- But you do realize...
I don't need magic to kill you.
Funny...
that's what Oliver Queen said
right before he killed you.
[GROWLS]
♪
Foolish girl. I extended
my hand to you in kindness.
- Now you've left me no choice.
- [CHOKING]
Let her go.
♪
If it isn't the great protectress.
[ROARING]
[THRILLING MUSIC]
♪
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
Whatever you're doing, don't.
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY] Bring it.
- What the...
- ♪
[DISTANT GRUNTING]
Ugh.
- Grey, Grey, you all right?
- [GRUNTS] I'll live.
It seems your body's youthful
resilience has its advantages.
- Hedy, I told you to run.
- And I didn't listen.
You must be his other half.
You two need to use your powers.
We can't. It could cause a
catastrophic nuclear reaction.
Everybody could die.
[LAUGHING EVILLY]
I got this.
♪
You have to become the Nuclear Man.
It's Firestorm, not Nuclear Man,
and we'd have to be crazy to
attempt a "Freaky Friday" merge.
Yes, but yours could be the
case of quantum entanglement,
which means the particles
in your body are mirrored
by those of your atomic
companion, which also means...
That if we merge, we could still
maintain a stable nuclear reaction.
Sometimes you have to be crazy
if you wish to burn bright.
♪
What do you say, Jefferson?
Not bad.
- You want those to be your last words?
- [CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS, EXHALES SHARPLY]
We agreed no magic.
Oh, no, I agreed that I
wouldn't use my magic.
I couldn't make that
same promise for her.
[GROANING]
That's the thing about daughters.
When they see you die at the
hands of one self-righteous hero,
they really don't want
to see it happen again.
[GRUNTS] Your daughter?
The apple of my eye.
[CHUCKLES]
This is the famous White Canary?
Hmm.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Bye-bye, birdie.
[SARA GRUNTING]
That's what I'm talking about, Grey!
♪
Come on, drive her back, Grey!
Jefferson, I don't think I can do this.
In case you haven't
noticed, I'm an old man.
Yeah, true, but you got this, Grey.
♪
Come on, Grey! Let's get them, baby!
Nora, darling, I think
it's time we take our leave.
Please tell me Firestein's a thing.
- Oh, my God.
- What's wrong?
I have to pee.
- And I do not.
- You did it.
You're a genius.
Forming Firestorm has restored
us to our rightful bodies.
Guys!
Guys, we've got to get
her back to the ship.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
You're a disgrace to every totem
bearer who's come before you.
- You have no right to wield its power.
- I have every right...
- to this totem and yours.
- This totem is my family's.
- Only my blood may bear it.
- And they do.
You gave it to your daughter,
and she was supposed to give it to me.
But instead, it rests on
my little sister's throat.
- That's impossible.
- That I am your granddaughter?
What do you know of the future?
I told you I couldn't kill
you without killing myself.
But how?
- [KNIFE PLUNGES]
- [GRUNTS]
♪
- Kuasa, wait.
- [KNIFE CLATTERS]
♪
I see great things for you,
Ms. LaMarr, and Warner Brothers.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
♪
[CHUCKLES] It appears that went well.
Arnold wants me to
star in his next film.
The man was so desperate
after the Greek disaster,
I was able to negotiate a pay
bump out of the whole thing.
Brilliant and beautiful.
Thank you.
I couldn't have done that
or survived without you.
Oh, it... it was nothing,
really. Just doing our job...
setting history back on course.
- Can you guys hear me?
- Loud and clear.
And the ship's purring like a kitten.
[SIGHS] Okay, time to go.
Yes. Yes, we... we must be off.
Well, good-bye.
[SOFT ROMANTIC MUSIC]
♪
I actually prefer older men.
Well, I'll be...
You old fox. [CHUCKLES]
Come on, man.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey.
How's Sara?
Gideon has placed her in a
coma so that she can heal fully.
We'll be without a captain
for a few days, but...
thankfully she'll make it.
Um...
there's something I need to tell you.
It's something I shouldn't tell you,
but it's something you should know.
That Kuasa is Mari's
sister and my granddaughter.
- How'd you know?
- She told me. [SCOFFS]
I never knew that she even existed.
I don't blame you for
not saying anything.
You were just protecting the timeline.
I would have done the same thing.
Thank you for understanding.
I can tell you everything I know,
but it... it is more
complicated than you think.
No.
We are the protectors of history,
not its editors.
So the less I know, the better.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪
- [GASPS]
- Whoa, there, killer.
Oh, my gods. I'm terribly sorry.
I got a bit carried away.
You're pretty good with that
thing. You should keep it.
But this belongs to your comrade.
Yeah, I think she'd be
cool with you having it.
Any of those Trojans get
handsy with you back home,
you show 'em what's what.
Troy is hardly a home.
I don't want to return there.
How can you claim to be heroes,
claim to do good in the world
and yet force somebody back
into a horrible existence?
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪
Okay.
According to the historical record,
you disappeared halfway through the war,
but that didn't affect the war itself.
So I found you a loophole.
Same time that you're from,
just a different place.
Huh, I hacked history.
Hmm.
This isn't Troy.
Nope, it's an island
full of warrior women.
It's cool, right?
[CHUCKLES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Won't your comrades be mad at you?
Yeah, yeah, they would be.
But they knew what they were
getting when they brought me on.
[LAUGHS, SNIFFLES]
Oh, thank you.
You've changed my destiny.
♪
Best thing about this place...
No boys allowed.
You'll finally have
some peace and quiet.
- ♪
- _
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -- www.Addic7ed.com --
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44